<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2013 Task Coach developers <developers@taskcoach.org> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.taskcoach.TaskCoach</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">>org.taskcoach.TaskCoach.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Task Coach</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Task Coach</name>
  <summary>Your Friendly Task Manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Your Friendly Task Manager</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Task Coach is an open source todo manager to manage personal tasks and todo lists. It supports composite tasks, i.e. tasks within tasks. In addition, Task Coach allows you to categorize your tasks, track efforts against a budget per task, and much more. Task Coach is available for Windows, Mac OS X, BSD, Linux, iPhone and iPad.</p>
    <p>Your database may be synchronized across these platforms. If espeak is installed, reminders can be spoken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Task Coach est un gestionnaire de tâches libre pour gérer vos tâches et listes de choses à faire. Il supporte les tâches composites, càd les tâches faisant partie d'une autre. De plus, Task Coach vous permet de catégoriser vos tâches, suivre le temps passé par rapport à un budget associé à chaque tâche, et bien plus. Task Coach est disponible pour Windows, Mac OS X, BSD, Linux, iPhone et iPad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Votre base de données peut être synchronisée à travers toutes ces plate-formes. Si espeak est installé, les rappels peuvent être énoncés.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" width="1280" height="748">http://www.taskcoach.org/screenshots/Appdata-01.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot width="1280" height="748">http://www.taskcoach.org/screenshots/Appdata-02.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.taskcoach.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">http://sourceforge.net/p/taskcoach/bugs</url>
  <url type="faq">https://answers.launchpad.net/taskcoach/+faqs</url>
  <url type="help">http://taskcoach.wikispaces.com/Task+Coach+Manual</url>
  <url type="donation">http://www.taskcoach.org/givesupport.html</url>
  <update_contact>developers@taskcoach.org</update_contact>
  <releases>
		<release version="1.4.4" date="2018-12-02">
			<description>
				<p>Bugs fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>TaskCoach would not start on Fedora 23 using LXDE. This probably concerns other distributions as well.</li>
          <li>Reminders would fire randomly or not at all.</li>
        </ul>
				<p>Features added:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Per-task effort total time consolidation, patch provided by rogerdc@gmail.com</li>
          <li>Add a viewer for task dependencies based on igraph (contributed by Matthias Tafelmeier). Not available on all platforms.</li>
        </ul>
			</description>
		</release>
  </releases>
  <developer_name>Frank Niessink, Jérôme Laheurte &amp; Aaron Wolf</developer_name>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"></content_rating>
</component>
