<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles</id>

  <name>BlueBubbles</name>
  <summary>BlueBubbles client for Linux</summary>

  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>

  <developer_name>BlueBubbles</developer_name>

  <url type="homepage">https://bluebubbles.app/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/BlueBubblesApp/bluebubbles-app/issues</url>
  <url type="faq">https://bluebubbles.app/faq/</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.bluebubbles.app/landing-page/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://bluebubbles.app/donate/</url>
  <url type="contact">https://discord.gg/6nrGRHT</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/BlueBubblesApp/bluebubbles-app</url>
  <url type="contribute">https://docs.bluebubbles.app/client/build-yourself-contribution-guide</url>

  <recommends>
    <display_length compare="ge">300</display_length>
  </recommends>
  <supports>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </supports>

  <description>
    <p>
      BlueBubbles is an open-source and cross-platform ecosystem of apps aimed to bring iMessage to Android, Windows,
      Linux, and the Web! With BlueBubbles, you&apos;ll be able to send messages, media, and much more to your friends
      and family.
    </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://bluebubbles.app/assets/devices.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release date="2023-12-04" version="1.12.7.0">
      <description>
        <p>Implements (experimental) ability to answer FaceTime calls</p>
        <ul>
          <li>This requires macOS Monterey and the Private API to be enabled for FaceTime.</li>
          <li>This also requires the BlueBubbles Server v1.9.2 update</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes some issues parsing mentions in messages</p>
        <p>Adds button to open a FindMy Friends location in Google Maps</p>
        <p>Adds notice when the Private API is enabled on the server, but not on the client side</p>
        <p>Fixes to FaceTime call notifications</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-12-02" version="1.12.6.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixes issue with detecting and showing FaceTime notifications.</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where images would be pixelated when zooming in.</li>
          <li>Removes blurred background for message popups when on High Performance Mode.</li>
          <li>Adds ngrok-skip-browser-warning header and custom User-Agent to fix Ngrok Tunnel compatibility issues.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-12-01" version="1.12.5.0">
      <description>
        <p>Enhancements</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved send/receive sound UI &amp; added volume setting</li>
          <li>Added ability to check if an address is iMessage capable in the chat creator</li>
          <li>Reworked &quot;jump to last unread&quot; logic to prevent lagging/freezing chats</li>
          <li>Added ability to jump to a message when tapping on it from the reply thread view</li>
          <li>Added better clarity to group member count text in conversation details</li>
          <li>&quot;Always show avatar&quot; now functions as expected [Material skin]</li>
          <li>Chat avatar now shows in conversation header [Material skin]</li>
          <li>Message content detection prioritizes the longest detected string in the message</li>
          <li>Improved Google Sign In UI</li>
          <li>Added ability to schedule messages on an hourly basis (Don&#39;t abuse this!)</li>
          <li>Added audio player seek bar [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Added ability to change user color even if colorful avatar is off</li>
          <li>Check if chat exists on server before creating a chat, in case it exists on the app but not on the
            server
          </li>
          <li>Added ability to sign in via Google in connection settings</li>
          <li>Ctrl + tab switches to the next chat even if the text field is focused [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Brand new FaceTime notification (aaaaaand maybe some extra new features if you&#39;re brave enough to try
            them)
          </li>
          <li>Added FindMy friends &amp; redesigned FindMy screen</li>
          <li>Refocus main text field after editing a message</li>
          <li>Added up arrow shortcut setting to edit the last sent message</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added better error handling to localhost detection</li>
          <li>Dispose video players properly [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed non-functional send/receive sound [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed text field losing focus if mouse moved outside [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed issue where the app searches a chat called &quot;minimized&quot; when starting the app minimized
            [Desktop]
          </li>
          <li>Fixed text field focus when iMessage replying</li>
          <li>Fixed issues loading settings backups</li>
          <li>Fixed window sizing with multiple monitors [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed issues with window not coming to front when clicking a notification [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed right click not functioning on conversation tile [Desktop, Material / Samsung skin]</li>
          <li>Fixed video player controls [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed whitespace getting saved as message drafts</li>
          <li>Fixed gesture interference preventing moving cursor when editing a message</li>
          <li>Fixed status indicators not updating for delivered or read messages in the chat list</li>
          <li>Fixed middle click scroll reversed and glitchy [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed firebase error when project / configuration changes</li>
          <li>Fixed shared vCards without a contact photo using your personal avatar</li>
        </ul>
        <p>For Developers</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Upgraded to Flutter 3.13</li>
          <li>Updated dependencies</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-09-03" version="1.12.4.1">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes issues with notifications.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-08-28" version="1.12.4.0" />
    <release date="2023-08-24" version="1.12.3.0" />
    <release date="2023-04-22" version="1.12.2.1" />
    <release date="2023-04-18" version="1.12.2.0" />
    <release date="2023-04-17" version="1.12.0.1" />
    <release date="2023-04-16" version="1.12.0.0" />
    <release date="2023-04-12" version="1.11.100.1" />
    <release date="2023-04-09" version="1.11.100.0" />
    <release date="2023-02-07" version="1.10.100.0" />
    <release date="2022-11-27" version="1.10.1.1" />
    <release date="2022-11-27" version="1.10.1.0" />
    <release date="2022-11-22" version="1.10.0.0" />
    <release date="2022-07-14" version="1.9.102.0" />
    <release date="2022-06-23" version="1.9.7.0" />
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
