<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles</id>

  <name>BlueBubbles</name>
  <summary>BlueBubbles client for Linux</summary>

  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>

  <developer id="app.bluebubbles">
    <name>BlueBubbles</name>
  </developer>

  <url type="homepage">https://bluebubbles.app/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/BlueBubblesApp/bluebubbles-app/issues</url>
  <url type="faq">https://bluebubbles.app/faq/</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.bluebubbles.app/landing-page/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://bluebubbles.app/donate/</url>
  <url type="contact">https://discord.gg/6nrGRHT</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/BlueBubblesApp/bluebubbles-app</url>
  <url type="contribute">https://docs.bluebubbles.app/client/build-yourself-contribution-guide</url>

  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#8ab7ff</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#24315d</color>
  </branding>

  <recommends>
    <display_length compare="ge">300</display_length>
  </recommends>
  <supports>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </supports>

  <description>
    <p>
      Open-source and cross-platform ecosystem of apps aimed to bring iMessage to Android, Windows, Linux, and the Web!
    </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" xml:lang="en">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles/931c0db62212394509edbdc15814baca65e94e9f/screenshots/Ios%20Skin.png</image>
      <caption>Chat with friends and family</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot xml:lang="en">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles/931c0db62212394509edbdc15814baca65e94e9f/screenshots/Dark.png</image>
      <caption>Dark Mode</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot xml:lang="en">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles/931c0db62212394509edbdc15814baca65e94e9f/screenshots/Settings.png</image>
      <caption>Extensive Customization</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot xml:lang="en">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles/931c0db62212394509edbdc15814baca65e94e9f/screenshots/Material%20Skin.png</image>
      <caption>Material Skin</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot xml:lang="en">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/app.bluebubbles.BlueBubbles/931c0db62212394509edbdc15814baca65e94e9f/screenshots/Samsung%20Skin.png</image>
      <caption>Samsung Skin</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release date="2024-11-18" version="1.15.0.0">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/BlueBubblesApp/bluebubbles-app/releases/tag/v1.15.0%2B70</url>
      <description>
        <p>Enhancements</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Editing a message is disabled for messages more than 15 minutes old (this didn't actually work)</li>
          <li>Adds the ability for the app to remember the reply-state for chats</li>
          <li>Adds support for setting custom headers during the setup process</li>
          <li>Adds support for using custom headers when connecting to the server's websocket via the background service</li>
          <li>Switches from GIPHY to Tenor as a GIF provider</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixes messages not syncing if app reconnects to server while not in the foreground</li>
          <li>Fixes issue sending links with server on macOS Sonoma or higher</li>
          <li>Fixes issue loading FindMy devices from the server</li>
          <li>Fixes not showing Profile section in settings on iOS Skin</li>
          <li>Fixes 24-hr time setting not being applied to scheduled messages view</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2024-11-06" version="1.14.0.0">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/BlueBubblesApp/bluebubbles-app/releases/tag/v1.14.0%2B69</url>
      <description>
        <p>Enhancements</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Spellcheck has been added. You can disable it or change the spellcheck language in Settings > Misc. &amp; Advanced.</li>
          <li>You can now customize the order of items in the menu displayed when right-clicking a message.</li>
          <li>Added an Emoji picker</li>
          <li>Settings redesign</li>
          <li>Ability to re-order message details context menu</li>
          <li>Changed FindMy to open exact coordinates in Maps app rather than the address</li>
          <li>FindMy Friends shows last location update</li>
          <li>FindMy Friends shows location status</li>
          <li>Faster FindMy load and refresh</li>
          <li>Added tooltip to manual mark unread/read button to make it more clear</li>
          <li>Allow adding newlines in text when creating a scheduled message</li>
          <li>Notification when phone number deregisters</li>
          <li>New profile screen to view/manage all iMessage account related tasks</li>
          <li>You can now filter searches based on chat, sender, and date</li>
          <li>We've also fixed consistency issues when searching your server vs. your local device.</li>
          <li>Updates iOS emoji pack to iOS 17.4</li>
          <li>Hiding the full screen image viewer controls will now also hide the app bar</li>
          <li>App startup time is now slightly quicker</li>
          <li>Location widgets now show the Apple Maps preview</li>
          <li>Adds ability to switch linked Google Firebase projects</li>
          <li>Dynamically show only the "show app" or "hide app" options based on whether the window is visible</li>
          <li>Hovering over mistakes now shows the suggested fixes, which can be applied directly to a message.</li>
          <li>Spellcheck is available in the chat creator, message and subject text fields, and when editing a message.</li>
          <li>Spellcheck language can now be selected in settings</li>
          <li>Spellcheck can be disabled in settings</li>
          <li>Allow more customization of iOS pin layout</li>
          <li>Add reset button to api timeout duration</li>
          <li>Make pinned order panel design more consistent to other pages</li>
          <li>Settings restoring handles errors gracefully now</li>
          <li>Tons of UI tweaks for iOS, Material, and Samsung</li>
          <li>Slightly new send animation</li>
          <li>Improvements to how smooth the app runs</li>
          <li>Lowers average battery utilization by fixing some possible leaks</li>
          <li>Audio transcripts (when available)</li>
          <li>Video player UX improvements</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed legacy URL preview titles showing just "www"</li>
          <li>Fixed URL previews too condensed in tablet mode</li>
          <li>Fixed app not accepting URLs with port in manual entry</li>
          <li>Fixed send and receive sound volume not following the preference set in settings</li>
          <li>Fixed custom themes with long names not uploading to server</li>
          <li>Fixed issue displaying URL previews</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where a custom landing page for the server would break the detect localhost feature</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where non-US phone numbers would be formatted incorrectly</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where a new chat would not show up in the chat list until a full app restart (sometimes two)</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where the search would return case-sensitive results from the server. The search is now case-insensitive</li>
          <li>Fixes issues where the unread indicators would not update in a timely manner</li>
          <li>Fixes issue using the universal back button when viewing archived chats</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where the date picker would not close properly when time selection was disabled</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where selecting a group chat in the new chat creator would append participants rather than replace the existing selection</li>
          <li>Fixes rendering issues on a handful of pages</li>
          <li>Fixes issues displaying URL previews</li>
          <li>Fixes issue showing digital touch messages in the message view</li>
        </ul>
        <p>For Developers</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Upgraded to Flutter 3.24.4</li>
          <li>Updated dependencies</li>
          <li>iOS emoji pack now always links to the latest release</li>
          <li>Unified logging across the codebae</li>
          <li>Adds indexes to the ObjectBox database to improve read speeds</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2024-10-29" version="1.13.100.0" />
    <release date="2024-05-31" version="1.12.101.0" />
    <release date="2024-02-22" version="1.12.100.0" />
    <release date="2023-12-04" version="1.12.7.0">
      <description>
        <p>Implements (experimental) ability to answer FaceTime calls</p>
        <ul>
          <li>This requires macOS Monterey and the Private API to be enabled for FaceTime.</li>
          <li>This also requires the BlueBubbles Server v1.9.2 update</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes some issues parsing mentions in messages</p>
        <p>Adds button to open a FindMy Friends location in Google Maps</p>
        <p>Adds notice when the Private API is enabled on the server, but not on the client side</p>
        <p>Fixes to FaceTime call notifications</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-12-02" version="1.12.6.0">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixes issue with detecting and showing FaceTime notifications.</li>
          <li>Fixes issue where images would be pixelated when zooming in.</li>
          <li>Removes blurred background for message popups when on High Performance Mode.</li>
          <li>Adds ngrok-skip-browser-warning header and custom User-Agent to fix Ngrok Tunnel compatibility issues.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-12-01" version="1.12.5.0">
      <description>
        <p>Enhancements</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved send/receive sound UI &amp; added volume setting</li>
          <li>Added ability to check if an address is iMessage capable in the chat creator</li>
          <li>Reworked &quot;jump to last unread&quot; logic to prevent lagging/freezing chats</li>
          <li>Added ability to jump to a message when tapping on it from the reply thread view</li>
          <li>Added better clarity to group member count text in conversation details</li>
          <li>&quot;Always show avatar&quot; now functions as expected [Material skin]</li>
          <li>Chat avatar now shows in conversation header [Material skin]</li>
          <li>Message content detection prioritizes the longest detected string in the message</li>
          <li>Improved Google Sign In UI</li>
          <li>Added ability to schedule messages on an hourly basis (Don&#39;t abuse this!)</li>
          <li>Added audio player seek bar [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Added ability to change user color even if colorful avatar is off</li>
          <li>Check if chat exists on server before creating a chat, in case it exists on the app but not on the server</li>
          <li>Added ability to sign in via Google in connection settings</li>
          <li>Ctrl + tab switches to the next chat even if the text field is focused [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Brand new FaceTime notification (aaaaaand maybe some extra new features if you&#39;re brave enough to try them)</li>
          <li>Added FindMy friends &amp; redesigned FindMy screen</li>
          <li>Refocus main text field after editing a message</li>
          <li>Added up arrow shortcut setting to edit the last sent message</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added better error handling to localhost detection</li>
          <li>Dispose video players properly [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed non-functional send/receive sound [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed text field losing focus if mouse moved outside [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed issue where the app searches a chat called &quot;minimized&quot; when starting the app minimized [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed text field focus when iMessage replying</li>
          <li>Fixed issues loading settings backups</li>
          <li>Fixed window sizing with multiple monitors [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed issues with window not coming to front when clicking a notification [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed right click not functioning on conversation tile [Desktop, Material / Samsung skin]</li>
          <li>Fixed video player controls [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed whitespace getting saved as message drafts</li>
          <li>Fixed gesture interference preventing moving cursor when editing a message</li>
          <li>Fixed status indicators not updating for delivered or read messages in the chat list</li>
          <li>Fixed middle click scroll reversed and glitchy [Desktop]</li>
          <li>Fixed firebase error when project / configuration changes</li>
          <li>Fixed shared vCards without a contact photo using your personal avatar</li>
        </ul>
        <p>For Developers</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Upgraded to Flutter 3.13</li>
          <li>Updated dependencies</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-09-03" version="1.12.4.1">
      <description>
        <p>This release fixes issues with notifications.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release date="2023-08-28" version="1.12.4.0" />
    <release date="2023-08-24" version="1.12.3.0" />
    <release date="2023-04-22" version="1.12.2.1" />
    <release date="2023-04-18" version="1.12.2.0" />
    <release date="2023-04-17" version="1.12.0.1" />
    <release date="2023-04-16" version="1.12.0.0" />
    <release date="2023-04-12" version="1.11.100.1" />
    <release date="2023-04-09" version="1.11.100.0" />
    <release date="2023-02-07" version="1.10.100.0" />
    <release date="2022-11-27" version="1.10.1.1" />
    <release date="2022-11-27" version="1.10.1.0" />
    <release date="2022-11-22" version="1.10.0.0" />
    <release date="2022-07-14" version="1.9.102.0" />
    <release date="2022-06-23" version="1.9.7.0" />
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
