<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>org.robomongo.Robo3T</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">org.robomongo.Robo3T.desktop</launchable>
    <name>Robo 3T</name>

    <metadata_license>GPL-3.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef=https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Studio3T/robomongo/master/LICENSE</project_license>

    <developer_name>3T Software Labs</developer_name>
    <summary>Free lightweight GUI for MongoDB enthusiasts</summary>

    <url type="homepage">https://robomongo.org/</url>

    <description>
        <p>
            Robo 3T (formerly Robomongo) is a shell-centric cross-platform MongoDB management tool.
            Unlike most other MongoDB admin UI tools, Robo 3T embeds the actual mongo shell in a tabbed interface
            with access to a shell command line as well as GUI interaction.
        </p>
    </description>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://robomongo.org/static/screens-transparent-6e2a44fd.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <categories>
        <category>Development</category>
    </categories>

    <releases>
        <release date="2019-03-22" version="1.3.1">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>New Features:</li>
                    <li>* Biggest change in this version is mongo shell version upgrade from 3.4 to 4.0</li>
                    <li>* Support for importing from MongoDB SRV connection strings</li>
                    <li>* Query results window now supports tabbed output</li>
                    <li>* New feature: Adding support for SCRAM-SHA-256 auth mechanism</li>
                    <li>* Encrypted passwords are used instead of clear text passwords</li>
                    <li>* Support for Ubuntu 18.04 and Mac 10.14</li>
                    <li>* Support for creating version 4 UUID</li>
                    <li>Bug Fixes:</li>
                    <li>* Create/View/Drop User features are fixed and updated</li>
                    <li>* Pagination does not work when the aggregation queries have dotted fields</li>
                    <li>* Attempt to fix: Crash when right click on existing results plus a new long running query</li>
                    <li>* Fix for application crash when adding index with invalid JSON</li>
                    <li>* 'Repair Database' in Robo3T needs a confirm dialog box!</li>
                    <li>* Robo 3T the input space causes connection failure</li>
                    <li>* Crash when loading results + right click</li>
                    <li>* Attempt to fix major connection problems seen with the second edit/add/remove doc. operation after MongoDB 4.0 upgrade</li>
                    <li>* Attempt to fix: For CRUD ops showing progress bar and disabling context menu while waiting for edit op to finish</li>
                    <li>* Showing much better error reason string from Mongo drivers for connection failures</li>
                    <li>* Fixing UI issue where Functions folder freezing with "Functions..." when fails to refresh</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
</component>
