<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>club.haroohie.SerialLoops</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Serial Loops</name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">club.haroohie.SerialLoops.desktop</launchable>
  <summary>Editor for Suzumiya Haruhi no Chokuretsu</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Serial Loops is a full-fledged editor for the Nintendo DS game Suzumiya Haruhi no Chokuretsu (The Series of Haruhi Suzumiya).
      In its current state, it allows you to edit nearly everything about the game, and more is planned for the future. Please check
      our documentation on our website for more information on how to use it!
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Fully edit the game's scripts, completely rewriting your own Haruhi visual novel with a powerful preview feature!</li>
      <li>Completely change the game's scenario, moving events around in the order you'd like them to occur!</li>
      <li>Replace the game's graphics, including backgrounds, CGs, character sprites, chibis, and more!</li>
      <li>Edit the game's soundtrack, swapping out background music and voice lines! (SFX coming in a future release!)</li>
      <li>Edit character nameplates, topics, UI text, tutorial mappings, and dialogue colors!</li>
      <li>Apply pre-written assembly hacks for even greater control of the game!</li>
      <li>Partial editing of group selections, puzzles, and chess puzzles, and viewable maps!</li>
      <li>A full save editor for editing save games as well!</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#9accfe</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#042058</color>
  </branding>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <screenshot type="default">
        <caption>Serial Loops script editor</caption>
        <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/haroohie-club/SerialLoops/0.3.3/install/linux/flatpak/screenshots/script_editor.png</image>
      </screenshot>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Serial Loops startup screen</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/haroohie-club/SerialLoops/0.3.3/install/linux/flatpak/screenshots/main_screen.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <screenshot type="default">
        <caption>Serial Loops map editor</caption>
        <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/haroohie-club/SerialLoops/0.3.3/install/linux/flatpak/screenshots/map_editor.png</image>
      </screenshot>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <developer_name>The Haroohie Translation Club</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://haroohie.club/chokuretsu/serial-loops</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="v0.3.3" date="2025-08-20">
      <description>
        <p>
          We removed our dependencies on devkitARM and make and have switched to using LLVM and ninja. This makes it easier
          to use Serial Loops on all platforms as it significantly easier to install and use these dependencies.
        </p>
        <p>This is also our initial release on Flathub!</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>