<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.streetwriters.notesnook</id>
    <name>Notesnook</name>
    <summary>A fully open source &amp; end-to-end encrypted note taking alternative to Evernote</summary>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
    <developer_name>Streetwriters</developer_name>
    <description>
        <p>Notesnook is a life changing notes app. With privacy at it's core, all your notes are end-to-end encrypted by default. Keep notes and save ideas with freedom. Unlike other privacy focused productivity apps, our online notepad app has great note taking features while being 100% private.</p>
        <p>
            A notes app with no spying or tracking
        </p>
        <p>Great and simple note taking experience. Be focused and productive by boosting your workflow. Keep tasks, ideas &amp; lists in one place.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Zero trackers or ads</li>
            <li>100% cross platform notes app</li>
            <li>Encryption and privacy friendly note taking</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Take notes on any device
        </p>
        <p>Access your notes from anywhere. Keep your notes app on any device. Make notes, outlines &amp; task lists. Your private digital notepad makes your workflow productive &amp; organized.</p>
        <p>
            Monographs: Encrypted note sharing
        </p>
        <p>Sharing notes is easier than ever with our online notes app. You can lock important notes with password before sharing as a public link with anyone.</p>
        <p>
            Todo lists and tasks
        </p>
        <p>Manage your day-to-day tasks and stay organized. Use Notesnook to make todo lists, shopping lists, outlines and record notes. Share lists with your friends, family or colleagues. Make lists for any purpose.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Shopping list</li>
            <li>Task management</li>
            <li>Take notes</li>
            <li>Make lists for ideas and tasks</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Rich note taking experience
        </p>
        <p>Write notes with full control. Keep notes simple or add images, tables, embeds, lists and even embeds and files. Take notes with math and chemistry formulas. Personalise your note taking by configuring the toolbar.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Images, embeds &amp; videos</li>
            <li>Make notes with file attachments</li>
            <li>Tables, task lists &amp; outline lists</li>
            <li>Full Math and Chemistry Formula support.</li>
            <li>Full markdown editor - Most markdown shortcuts are supported</li>
            <li>Code blocks with support for all programming languages</li>
            <li>Written Notes history</li>
            <li>Powerful search in notes</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Notepad with offline support
        </p>
        <p>Write notes offline. Jot down your ideas anytime even without internet. Sync your written notes when you open the notepad online instantly.</p>
        <p>
            Organize notes with Notebooks
        </p>
        <p>Create multiple notebooks in our notepad. Organize &amp; make notes and task lists in topics. Create shortcuts for Notebooks to access them quickly.</p>
        <p>Color notes and add tags
        </p>
        <p>Make your Notesnook colorful. Color notes and add tags to quickly find similar or related ideas in one place. Color notes also appear in side menu so they are easy to access.</p>
        <p>Protect notes with privacy lock
        </p>
        <p>Lock your online notepad with privacy lock. No one can open the notes app even if your phone is left unlocked. Take notes with complete privacy. You can also lock notes with password.</p>
        <p>Say yes to private note taking
        </p>
        <p>A good notes app is one that doesn&#39;t spy on you. It&#39;s as simple as, &quot;No one should be able to read my notes, even the possibility that someone can open my online notepad is scary&quot;.</p>
        <p>Open source notes app
        </p>
        <p>
            Any privacy respecting service should be open source. Notesnook is no different. All our code is available in
            our GitHub repository (https://github.com/streetwriters/notesnook)
            for anyone to check.
        </p>
        <p>Export your notes anytime
        </p>
        <p>Export your data from our online notepad as PDF, HTML, markdown or plain text. We have a zero lock-in policy. You can take your data anywhere, anytime.</p>
        <p>Say yes to privacy
        </p>
        <p>Choose privacy today for your notes and never look back. Notesnook is here. The online notepad that protects you and your data. Stay safe and take notes with freedom.</p>
    </description>
    <url type="homepage">https://notesnook.com/</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/streetwriters/notesnook/issues</url>
    <url type="help">https://docs.notesnook.com/</url>
    <url type="donation">https://opencollective.com/notesnook</url>
    <url type="contribute">https://github.com/streetwriters/notesnook/blob/master/CONTRIBUTING.md</url>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.streetwriters.notesnook.desktop</launchable>
    <provides>
        <binary>notesnook</binary>
    </provides>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://notesnook.com/screenshots/desktop/1.jpg</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://notesnook.com/screenshots/desktop/2.jpg</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <categories>
        <category>Education</category>
        <category>Office</category>
    </categories>
    <keywords>
        <keyword>notepad</keyword>
        <keyword>note taking app</keyword>
        <keyword>note taking</keyword>
        <keyword>end-to-end encrypted</keyword>
        <keyword>notebook</keyword>
    </keywords>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
        <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
    <supports>
        <internet>offline-only</internet>
    </supports>
    <releases>
        <release version="2.2.1" date="2022-09-29" urgency="high" type="stable">
            <url type="details">https://github.com/streetwriters/notesnook/releases/tag/v2.2.1</url>
            <description>
                <p>Features &amp; new stuff</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Removed limit on number of pins</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Fixes &amp; improvements:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Open all links in release notes in a new tab/window</li>
                    <li>Fixed issue where right click on selected items deselects them</li>
                    <li>Fixed issue where menus/dropdowns wouldn&#39;t open on desktop/web</li>
                    <li>Minor improvements in editor performance</li>
                    <li>Fixed issue where onboarding is shown to everyone on startup</li>
                    <li>Fixed &quot;Unknown content type&quot; error on backup restore</li>
                    <li>Fixed issue where typing really fast in title input caused jank</li>
                    <li>Fixed issue with snap desktop integration</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
</component>