<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.jetbrains.Toolbox</id>
  <name>Jetbrains Toolbox App</name>
  <summary>Manage your IDEs the easy way</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>
      Update quickly and easily
    </p>
    <p>
      Manage your JetBrains tools easily
    </p>
    <p>
      Install Update automatically Update the plugins together with IDE Roll back and downgrade
    </p>
    <p>
      Save time and effort maintaining your IDEs, by downloading a patch or a set of patches instead of the full package download. Everything updates in the background while you never stop coding.
    </p>
    <p>
      See what’s new JetBrains Toolbox App lets you read all about the latest features and bug-fixes introduced into your IDE, before you update it.
    </p>
    <p>
      Maintain multiple versions side by side Handle several versions of the same tool easily. Be the first to try out the Early Access Programs (EAP) for JetBrains IDEs, and Google’s Android Studio releases and Canary builds, which can also be installed and updated through the JetBrains Toolbox App.
    </p>
    <p>
      Open projects instantly All of your projects are at your fingertips with your favorites pinned to the top. Find them quickly using the Search field, and open them instantly inside the correct IDE with a single click.
    </p>
    <p>
      Remote IDE management Install, update, and manage your JetBrains IDEs on remote machines just as easily as on your local setup. Work across Linux, Windows, and macOS with secure, flexible connections using built-in remote development support.
    </p>
    <p>
      Integrate with GitHub, GitLab, or Bitbucket Install the extension for Google Chrome or Firefox and you will be able to clone and open your GitHub, GitLab, or Bitbucket repositories right from your browser.
    </p>
    <p>
      NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by JetBrains s.r.o.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.jetbrains.Toolbox.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.jetbrains.com/toolbox-app/img/1_en-us.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>