<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.ntrack.n-track</id>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://ntrack.com/help/manual.html?platform=linux#license</project_license>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.ntrack.n-track.desktop</launchable>
  <name>n-Track Studio</name>
  <summary>Creative Music Making (DAW)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Kreative Musikproduktion (DAW)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Libera la tua creatività musicale (DAW)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Libérez votre créativité musicale (STAN)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Producción Musical Creativa (DAW)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Desperte sua criatividade musical (DAW)</summary>
  <description>
    <p>n-Track Studio is the powerful digital audio workstation (DAW) designed for musicians, producers, and creators of all levels. Record, edit, mix, and master audio and MIDI with ease.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">n-Track Studio ist eine leistungsstarke digitale Audio-Workstation (DAW) für Musiker, Produzenten und Kreative aller Erfahrungsstufen. Nimm Audio und MIDI ganz einfach auf, bearbeite, mische und mastere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">n-Track Studio è la potente workstation audio digitale (DAW) pensata per musicisti, produttori e creativi di ogni livello. Registra, modifica, mixa e masterizza audio e MIDI con facilità.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">n-Track Studio est une station audionumérique (STAN) puissante conçue pour les musiciens, producteurs et créateurs de tous niveaux. Enregistrez, éditez, mixez et masterisez l’audio et le MIDI facilement.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">n-Track Studio es una potente estación de trabajo de audio digital (DAW) diseñada para músicos, productores y creadores de todos los niveles. Graba, edita, mezcla y masteriza audio y MIDI con facilidad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">n-Track Studio é uma poderosa estação de trabalho de áudio digital (DAW) projetada para músicos, produtores e criadores de todos os níveis. Grave, edite, misture e masterize áudio e MIDI com facilidade.</p>
    <p>Produce professional-quality tracks using built-in tools like the Step Sequencer, Piano Roll, Drum and Pad interfaces. Add creative polish with effects such as VocalTune, Amps, EQ, Reverb, and the Lookahead Limiter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Erstelle professionelle Tracks mit integrierten Tools wie Step-Sequencer, Pianoroll sowie Drum- und Pad-Interfaces. Verleihe deinen Produktionen kreativen Feinschliff mit Effekten wie VocalTune, Amps, EQ, Reverb und dem Lookahead Limiter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Produci tracce di qualità professionale usando strumenti integrati come Step Sequencer, Piano Roll, Drum e Pad. Aggiungi un tocco creativo con effetti come VocalTune, Amps, EQ, Riverbero e Lookahead Limiter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Créez des morceaux professionnels avec des outils intégrés comme le séquenceur pas à pas, le piano roll, les interfaces Drum et Pad. Apportez une touche créative grâce à des effets comme VocalTune, Amps, EQ, Reverb et le Lookahead Limiter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Crea pistas profesionales usando herramientas integradas como el secuenciador por pasos, el piano roll, y las interfaces de batería y pads. Añade un toque creativo con efectos como VocalTune, Amps, EQ, Reverb y el Lookahead Limiter.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Produza faixas de qualidade profissional com ferramentas integradas como o Step Sequencer, Piano Roll e interfaces de Bateria e Pads. Adicione um toque criativo com efeitos como VocalTune, Amps, EQ, Reverb e o Lookahead Limiter.</p>
    <p>Compose with 400+ virtual instruments and over 15GB of royalty-free sounds, or design your own using the n-Track Sampler. With AI-powered MixSplit, you can separate full songs into individual tracks.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Komponiere mit über 400 virtuellen Instrumenten und mehr als 15 GB lizenzfreien Sounds - oder gestalte eigene Klänge mit dem n-Track Sampler. Mit der KI-gestützten MixSplit-Funktion kannst du komplette Songs in einzelne Spuren aufteilen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Componi con oltre 400 strumenti virtuali e più di 15 GB di suoni royalty-free, oppure crea i tuoi suoni con il campionatore di n-Track. Con MixSplit basato su AI puoi separare brani completi in tracce individuali.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Composez avec plus de 400 instruments virtuels et plus de 15 Go de sons libres de droits, ou créez les vôtres avec le Sampler de n-Track. Avec MixSplit, alimenté par l’IA, séparez des morceaux entiers en pistes distinctes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Compón con más de 400 instrumentos virtuales y más de 15 GB de sonidos libres de derechos, o diseña los tuyos con el Sampler de n-Track. Con MixSplit impulsado por IA, puedes dividir canciones completas en pistas individuales.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Crie com mais de 400 instrumentos virtuais e mais de 15 GB de sons royalty-free, ou desenhe seus próprios usando o Sampler do n-Track. Com o MixSplit com tecnologia de IA, você pode separar músicas completas em faixas individuais.</p>
    <p>Record, share, and collab with musicians worldwide via the integrated Songtree community. Whether you're recording a solo vocal or a full band, n-Track supports multi-channel audio devices and third-party plugins (VST2, VST3, CLAP).</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Nimm auf, teile und arbeite mit Musikern weltweit über die integrierte Songtree-Community zusammen. Ob Solo-Vocal oder komplette Band – n-Track unterstützt Mehrkanal-Audiogeräte und Drittanbieter-Plugins (VST2, VST3, CLAP).</p>  
    <p xml:lang="it">Registra, condividi e collabora con musicisti di tutto il mondo tramite la community integrata di Songtree. Che tu stia registrando una voce solista o un’intera band, n-Track supporta dispositivi audio multicanale e plugin di terze parti (VST2, VST3, CLAP).</p>  
    <p xml:lang="fr">Enregistrez, partagez et collaborez avec des musiciens du monde entier via la communauté intégrée Songtree. Que vous enregistriez une voix solo ou un groupe complet, n-Track prend en charge les périphériques audio multicanaux et les plugins tiers (VST2, VST3, CLAP).</p>  
    <p xml:lang="es">Graba, comparte y colabora con músicos de todo el mundo gracias a la comunidad integrada Songtree. Ya sea una voz solista o una banda completa, n-Track es compatible con dispositivos de audio multicanal y plugins de terceros (VST2, VST3, CLAP).</p>  
    <p xml:lang="pt">Grave, compartilhe e colabore com músicos do mundo inteiro através da comunidade integrada do Songtree. Seja gravando um vocal solo ou uma banda completa, o n-Track é compatível com dispositivos de áudio multicanal e plugins de terceiros (VST2, VST3, CLAP).</p>  
  </description>
  <categories>
    <category>Audio</category>
    <category>AudioVideo</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <url type="homepage">https://www.ntrack.com</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://ntrack.com/support.php</url>
  <url type="faq">https://ntrack.com/faq.php</url>
  <url type="help">https://ntrack.com/help/manual.html</url>
 
<releases>
  <release version="10.2.2" date="2025-05-30">
    <url type="details">https://ntrack.com/changelog.php?platform=Linux</url>
    <description>
      <p>New in version 10.2.2:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Effects and Instruments plugins added to Loop Browser - drag them straight into your song [New Feature]</li>
          <li>Vocal Harmonizer - harmonize live or pre-recorded audio tracks via MIDI input [New Feature]</li>
          <li>Vocal Harmonizer - advanced voice modes [New Feature]</li>
          <li>Vocal Harmonizer - new set of dynamic presets [New Feature]</li>
        </ul>
    </description>
  </release>
</releases>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default">
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_ntrackstudio.png</image>
        <caption>n-Track Studio</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_recordedit.png</image>
        <caption>Record, Edit, Mix, Master</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Aufnehmen, Bearbeiten, Mischen, Mastern</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Registra, Modifica, Mixa, Masterizza</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Enregistrer, Éditer, Mixer, Masteriser</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Graba, Edita, Mezcla, Masteriza</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Grave, Edite, Misture, Masterize</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_stepsequencer.png</image>
        <caption>Use Step Sequencer, Pianoroll, Drums and Pads</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Verwende Step-Sequencer, Pianoroll, Drums und Pads</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Usa Step Sequencer, Pianoroll, Batterie e Pad</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Utilisez le séquenceur pas à pas, le piano roll, les batteries et les pads</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Usa el secuenciador por pasos, el piano roll, la batería y los pads</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Use o sequenciador por passos, pianoroll, bateria e pads</caption>
  </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_builtineffects.png</image>
        <caption>35+ n-Track built-in effects, like VocalTune, Amps and Lookahead Limiter</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Über 35 integrierte Effekte von n-Track, wie VocalTune, Amps und Lookahead Limiter</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Oltre 35 effetti integrati n-Track, come VocalTune, Amplificatori e Lookahead Limiter</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Plus de 35 effets intégrés n-Track, comme VocalTune, Amps et Lookahead Limiter</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Más de 35 efectos integrados de n-Track, como VocalTune, Amps y Lookahead Limiter</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Mais de 35 efeitos integrados n-Track, como VocalTune, Amps e Lookahead Limiter</caption>
  </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_aimixsplit.png</image>
        <caption>Split full songs into separate tracks with AI MixSplit</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Teile komplette Songs in separate Spuren mit AI MixSplit auf</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Dividi brani completi in tracce separate con AI MixSplit</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Séparez des morceaux complets en pistes distinctes avec AI MixSplit</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Divide canciones completas en pistas separadas con AI MixSplit</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Divida músicas completas em faixas separadas com o AI MixSplit</caption>
  </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_songtree.png</image>
        <caption>Collab and upload with the n-Track Songtree community</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Kollaboriere und lade hoch mit der n-Track Songtree-Community</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Collabora e carica con la community Songtree di n-Track</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Collaborez et téléversez avec la communauté Songtree de n-Track</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Colabora y sube tus pistas con la comunidad Songtree de n-Track</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Colabore e envie com a comunidade Songtree do n-Track</caption>
  </screenshot>
      <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_soundsinstruments.png</image>
        <caption>15GB+ n-Track Sounds and over 400 instruments</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Über 15 GB n-Track Sounds und mehr als 400 Instrumente</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Oltre 15GB di suoni n-Track e più di 400 strumenti</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Plus de 15 Go de sons n-Track et plus de 400 instruments</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Más de 15GB de sonidos n-Track y más de 400 instrumentos</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Mais de 15GB de sons do n-Track e mais de 400 instrumentos</caption>
  </screenshot>
          <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_thirdpartyplugins.png</image>
        <caption>Support for third-party plugins, VST2, VST3 and CLAP</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Drittanbieter-Plugins, VST2, VST3 und CLAP</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Supporto per plugin di terze parti, VST2, VST3 e CLAP</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge des plugins tiers, VST2, VST3 et CLAP</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Compatibilidad con plugins de terceros, VST2, VST3 y CLAP</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Suporte a plugins de terceiros, VST2, VST3 e CLAP</caption>
  </screenshot>

    <screenshot>
    <image>https://ntrack.com/img/flathub_multichannelaudiodevices.png</image>
        <caption>Audio support for multichannel audio devices</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="de">Audio-Unterstützung für mehrkanalige Audiogeräte</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="it">Supporto audio per dispositivi audio multicanale</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge audio pour les périphériques audio multicanaux</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="es">Soporte de audio para dispositivos de audio multicanal</caption>
    <caption xml:lang="pt">Suporte de áudio para dispositivos de áudio multicanal</caption>
  </screenshot>
</screenshots>
<keywords>
    <keyword>daw</keyword>
    <keyword>ntrack</keyword>
    <keyword>audio</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="de">Audio</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="it">audio</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="fr">audio</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="es">audio</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="pt">áudio</keyword>
    <keyword>midi</keyword>
    <keyword>linux</keyword>
    <keyword>flatpak</keyword>
    <keyword>mixing</keyword>
    <keyword>mastering</keyword>
    <keyword>music production</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="de">Musikproduktion</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="it">produzione musicale</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="fr">production musicale</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="es">producción musical</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="pt">produção musical</keyword>
      <keyword>digital audio workstation</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="de">digitale Audio-Workstation</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="it">workstation audio digitale</keyword>
  <keyword xml:lang="fr">station audionumérique</keyword>
</keywords>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <developer id="com.ntrack">
       <name translate="no">n-Track S.r.l.</name>
  </developer>
</component>


