<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.zettlr.Zettlr</id>
  
  <name>Zettlr</name>
  <summary>A Markdown editor for the 21st century</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <url type="homepage">https://www.zettlr.com</url>
  
  <description>
    <p>Writing is an essential part of our everyday life. Why make it complicated? Zettlr redefines what writing means. It is slim, fast, and versatile. Focus on what matters to you. Publish, not perish.</p>
    
    <p>In modern times, getting a hold of the flood of information is almost as hard as inserting a USB drive the right way on the first attempt. Zettlr allows you to connect pieces of information using state of the art Zettelkasten methodology. Links? Check. File IDs? Check. File tagging? Also check. And the best is: Unlike many competitors, Zettlr never locks you in. Zettlr supports almost every conceivable way to create links and identify your files. In other words: No matter where you come from — all Zettelkästen are beautiful and supported by Zettlr. Out of the box.</p>
    
    <p>Zettlr integrates well with reference managers such as Zotero, JabRef, or Juris-M. Simply load your library into Zettlr, and begin to cite. Zettlr strictly adheres to established standards and does not reinvent the wheel. Citations can be loaded using CSL-JSON or BibTex and the citation processor only uses Citation Style Language, the de-facto industry standard for citations. This enables you to use one of over 9,000 different styles from the official Zotero repository!</p>
    
    <p>Due to its designing flexibility, Zettlr supports dark mode out of the box, as well as many different themes, suited to your needs. Switching is as easy as pressing a button. Not satisfied with the provided themes? No problem: Zettlr allows full customization of every single element; you can even create completely new themes using Custom CSS!</p>

    <p>No matter whether you work with a lot of notes, such as a Zettelkasten, or simply have a lot of files with different important contents: Zettlr's revolutionary heatmap search lets you find every single note you've ever written. No more confusion over where that one citation was!</p>

    <p>Twitter invented them and, since then, everybody adopted them: Hashtags! Zettlr goes one step further, not only allowing you to link and categorize your notes using tags, but using its tag-manager you can assign colors to tags to visualize your notes immediately!</p>

    <p>Zettlr scales well with your aspirations. From the first texts in university to your dissertation thesis: Using the advanced features of Zettlr tailored to researchers, journalists, and novelists writing whole books is as easy as creating a new project. Zettlr will never stand in your way, just like a good app should.</p>

    <p>Note: In order to be able to export to PDF via LaTeX you need to additionally install the extension org.freedesktop.Sdk.Extension.texlive</p>

</description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.zettlr.Zettlr.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://zettlr.com/storage/app/media/img/frontpage_zettlr_dark.png</image>
      <caption>Zettlr's frontpage in dark mode</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.zettlr.com/themes/zettlr/assets/features/themes.png</image>
      <caption>Theme's supported by Zettlr</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.zettlr.com/themes/zettlr/assets/features/search.png</image>
      <caption>The search functionality presenet in zettlr</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
        <release version="v2.2.3" date="2021-12-18">
            <description>
                <p>Today comes a smaller update that fixes a few annoying bugs that came up after the last release, and it contains improvements to the graph view. Most notably, it should rebuild less frequently and much faster. Also, we finally fixed a bug that was around for a little bit longer and that prevented exports of reveal.js presentations in stylesheets other than black.</p>
                <p>GUI and Functionality</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>The graph view now only updates when the underlying link structure has in fact changed</li>
                    <li>Fixed an issue that would break project exports since we accidentally passed not just Markdown and code files, but also everything else in that directory to pandoc (including, but not limited to, PDFs, HTMLs, images, etc.)</li>
                    <li>The graph view now supports displaying labels permanently; useful for smaller graphs</li>
                    <li>Better graph sizing</li>
                    <li>You can now highlight specific vertices based on text matching on its path</li>
                    <li>The graph view scrolling has now been replaced by moving zoom, i.e. wherever your mouse cursor is when you zoom, the graph will zoom in ever so slightly onto that position</li>
                    <li>Tags/keywords in a YAML frontmatter are now properly lowercased</li>
                    <li>Massively improve the speed of graph building</li>
                    <li>Fixed an error that would prevent the creation of new directories</li>
                    <li>Fixed a bug that would always export a revealJS presentation using the black stylesheet</li>
                    <li>Fixed commented entries in the YAML frontmatter being detected as headings</li>
                    <li>The file tree now remembers which directories are opened for longer</li>
                    <li>Make the emphasis rendering plugin less aggressive</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Under the Hood</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Remove the dependency on the LinkProvider within the FSAL</li>
                    <li>The LinkProvider now only updates when necessary; easing the load on the graph</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases> 
</component>
