<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>dudetronics.nostar.DroidStar</id>
    <name>DroidStar</name>
    <provides>
        <id>DroidStar.desktop</id>
    </provides>
    <summary>DroidStar (Connects to M17, Fusion (YSF/FCS), DMR, P25, NXDN, D-STAR (REF/XRF/DCS)
        reflectors and AllStar nodes)</summary>
    <developer_name>dudetronics.com/</developer_name>
    <description>
        <p>
            <![CDATA[This software connects to M17, Fusion (YSF/FCS, DN and VW modes are supported), DMR,]]>
            <![CDATA[P25, NXDN, D-STAR (REF/XRF/DCS) reflectors and AllStar nodes (as an IAX2 client)]]>
            <![CDATA[over UDP. It is compatible with all of the AMBE USB devices]]>
            <![CDATA[out there (ThumbDV, DVstick 30, DVSI, etc). It also supports MMDVM modems and can be]]>
            <![CDATA[used as a hotspot, or as a stand-alone transceiver via direct mode to the MMDVM device.]]>
            <![CDATA[]]>
            <![CDATA[A vocoder plugin can be downloaded from a URL, which will place the vocoder into the]]>
            <![CDATA[correct location for the platform. Add a full http url, including the filename, to the]]>
            <![CDATA[Vocoder URL option on the settings tab, and click the Download vocoder button.]]>
            <![CDATA[]]>
            <![CDATA[For Android and iOS devices, the vocoder URL download method is the only way to load a]]>
            <![CDATA[vocoder plugin.]]>
            <![CDATA[]]>
            <![CDATA[For Linux/MacOS/Windows, a vocoder can also be manually placed.]]>
            <![CDATA[Copy the plugin to the system settings file location.]]>
            <![CDATA[]]>
            <![CDATA[On Linux, this is ~/.config/dudetronics. It is the same place where the]]>
            <![CDATA[host and id files are located (DMRHosts.txt, DMRIDs.data, etc).]]>
            <![CDATA[]]>
            <![CDATA[The vocoder plugin filename must be named vocoder_plugin.platform.arch where platform]]>
            <![CDATA[and arch can be any of the following: platform: linux, darwin, winnt,]]>
            <![CDATA[android, ios arch: x86_64, arm, arm64]]>
            <![CDATA[The platform and arch for your device are identified on the About tab.]]>
            <![CDATA[Download from : https://ke0zvd.com/installing-the-software-vocoder/]]>
        </p>
    </description>
    <category>HamRadio</category>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
    <url type="homepage">http://www.dudetronics.com/</url>
    <project_group>none</project_group>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Main JTDX window</caption>
            <image>
                https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FsjXl18X0AAm5O9?format=png
            </image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
        <release version="git 2f695e6" date="2023-03-15" />
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
    <update_contact>castilloeduardo@outlook.com.ar</update_contact>
</component>
