<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.google.EarthPro</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>Google Earth Pro</name>
  <summary>3D planet viewer</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Create maps with advanced tools: Google Earth Pro on desktop is free for users with advanced feature needs. Import and export GIS data, and go back in time with historical imagery</p>
    <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by Google</p>
  </description>

  <url type="homepage">https://www.google.com/earth/versions/</url>
  <update_contact>g.abdallah.ibrahim@gmail.com</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <developer_name>Google</developer_name>
  <url type="help">https://support.google.com/earth</url>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Google Earth Pro Desktop</caption>
      <image>https://www.google.com/intl/en_us/earth/assets/static/images/versions/versions__pro__desktop-image.v2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
  <release version="7.3.6" date="2022-10-26">
    <url type="details">https://support.google.com/earth/answer/40901</url>
    <description>
      <ul>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: Hardware-accelerated video encoding for faster processing and better image quality.</li>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: HEVC (H.265) codec support.</li>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: Full navigation controls, including Historical Imagery and Street View, available in live recording mode.</li>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: Better responsiveness during live recording.</li>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: Can defer video encoding until after live recording is finished.</li>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: In live recording mode, less obtrusive recording status dialog.</li>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: Live recordings accurately show the timing of user actions during the recording session.</li>
        <li>Movie Maker tool: Save video frames in QOI image format.</li>
        <li>Break apart a Multi Geometry place mark into individual place marks.</li>
        <li>Combine multiple selected place marks into a single Multi Geometry place mark.</li>
        <li>Import GeoJSON files.</li>
        <li>Improved printing tool quality.</li>
        <li>Save Image tool: Increased maximum image size.</li>
        <li>Save Image tool: PNG format support.</li>
        <li>Adjusted Google Earth logo size in main view, saved images, and printouts.</li>
        <li>Windows: Automatically support high-DPI displays.</li>
        <li>macOS: Fix illegible dialog tabs on macOS 11+.</li>
        <li>macOS: Cosmetic refinements to My Places and Layers panels.</li>
        <li>Regionate tool supports KML Schema extended data.</li>
        <li>Consistently save KML files with no changes from session to session.</li>
        <li>Correctly import CSV files with values that contain quotation marks.</li>
        <li>Edit KML LinearRing place mark line style.</li>
        <li>Other minor fixes and improvements.</li>
      </ul>
    </description>
  </release>
  </releases>
</component>
