<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.todesk.ToDesk</id>
  <update_contact>help@todesk.com</update_contact>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>ToDesk</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-Hans">ToDesk</name>
  <summary>A remote control software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-Hans">一款安全免费不限速的远程控制软件</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      ToDesk as a safe and free unlimited remote control software, through the leading network technology to build and operate their own network system, with global coverage of multi-node, multi-service, milliseconds latency application layer routing system, bringing the user like the use of local computers like the sense of experience. Support in any scenario at any time remotely connected to the company or personal off-site equipment, not only with file transfer, remote printing, remote control camera, privacy screen, security verification of confidentiality and many other features, but also to achieve the management of unattended equipment, operation and maintenance, while enterprise business personnel can be ToDesk remote support for external partners, external equipment, customer SOS services.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-Hans">
      ToDesk作为一款安全免费不限速的远程控制软件，通过领先的网络技术搭建并运营自己的网络系统，拥有覆盖全球的多节点、多业务，毫秒级延时应用层路由系统，带给用户像使用本地电脑一样的体验感。支持在任何场景下随时远程连接公司或个人异地设备，不仅具有文件传输、远程打印、远控摄像头、隐私屏、安全验证密保等众多功能，还可以实现对无人值守设备的管理、运维，同时企业业务人员可通过ToDesk远程支持外部合作伙伴、外部设备、客户SOS服务等。
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.todesk.com/</url>
  <developer_name>海南有趣科技有限公司</developer_name>
  <releases>
    <release version="4.7.2.0" date="2024-02-27">
      <url type="details">https://update.todesk.com/linux/uplog.html</url>
      <description>
        <p>
          全新游戏版，性能版VIP上线；增加一对一语音通话功能；优化设备登录安全性；优化设备列表搜索功能；优化远控工具栏编解码设置；优化剪贴板及文件传输功能；优化弹窗提示；修复一些已知bug。
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.todesk.ToDesk.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.todesk.com/userRights.html</project_license>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://todeskcdnspeed.todesk.com/202303161406305f6fe4304d7990.png</image>
      <caption>ToDesk</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
