<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Kevin Degeling -->

<component type="desktop">
  <id></id>
  <name>ET: Legacy</name>
  <summary>Enemy Territory: Legacy is an open source project based on the code of Wolfenstein: Enemy Territory which was released in 2010 under the terms of GPLv3 license</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>

  <developer_name>ET:Legacy team</developer_name>
  
  <url type="homepage">https://www.etlegacy.com//</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://dev.etlegacy.com/projects/etlegacy</url>
  <url type="help">https://dev.etlegacy.com/projects/etlegacy/wiki</url>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.etlegacy.ETL.desktop</launchable>

  <description>
    <p>Wolfenstein: Enemy Territory is a free multiplayer first-person shooter. Set during World War II and heavily focused on team work, it was initially released in 2003 by Splash Damage and id Software. More than a decade after its release, after spending countless hours of escorting tanks and trucks, stealing gold and radar parts and transmitting confidential documents, it was time to dust off the game which consistently refused to go down.</p>
    <p>Enemy Territory: Legacy is an open source project based on the code of Wolfenstein: Enemy Territory which was released in 2010 under the terms of GPLv3 license. The main goal of this project is to fix bugs, remove old dependencies and make it playable on all major operating systems while still remaining compatible with the ET 2.60b version and as many of its mods as possible. We do appreciate any contribution to the project such as patches, suggestions or comments. </p>
    <p>Many thanks to Splash Damage for their release of the source code, raedwulf-et (especially Ralph Eastwood) &amp; Unvanquished for our code base and ioQuake3 for their patches (especially /dev/humancontroller). Kudos! Also thanks to JetBrains for providing licences for their products.</p>
    <p> Ready to go listen servers with omni-bot support. Install it. Run it. Have fun! The ET:Legacy engine aims to provide modern features in a stable and secure code. The default mod shipped with ET: Legacy, Legacy mod, aims to add many useful features and improvements while staying close to the original gameplay. </p>
    <ul>     
      <li>Many bug and security fixesof the GPL code release (f.e. DDOS protection)</li>
      <li>New useful >cvarsand functions</li>
      <li>Client now based on SDL2, a cross-platform multimedia library</li>
      <li>Compatibility with almost every 2.60b mod</li>
      <li>Fast client built-in minimizer</li>
      <li>Integrated IRC client</li>
      <li>SQL dbms support</li>
      <li>Raw mouse input support</li>
      <li>Linux client sound without any hacks</li>
      <li>Speed optimizations</li>
      <li>Deprecated code removed (codebase is lighter by 33%!)</li>
      <li>Updated ancient dependencies</li>
      <li>OGG Vorbis client support</li>
      <li>JPEG-Turbo client support</li>
      <li>Translation support of clients</li>
      <li>Generated client GUIDs</li>
      <li>128 MB com_hunkmegs default value</li>
      <li>Expanded et:// protocol</li>
      <li>Client auto updates</li>
      <li>Coloured output in the system console</li>
      <li>Separate install and user data paths</li>
      <li>No admin priviledges needed after install</li>
      <li>Separated install and download folder</li>
      <li>Clean command to polish the download folder and getting rid of unwanted menu and pk3 files</li>
      <li>Easy to run installer to get you in battle in no time</li>
      <li>... and many more features!</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.etlegacy.com/images/slider/slider_1.jpg</image>
      <caption>US soldiers attacking a bunker complex</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.etlegacy.com/images/slider/slider_2.jpg</image>
      <caption>US soldiers in a beach landing, taking mortar fire</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.etlegacy.com/images/slider/slider_3.jpg</image>
      <caption>US soldiers trying to blow up a power generator</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="2.76.0" date="2019-09-27">
      <description>
        <p>First release of ET:Legacy on Flathub.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

</component>



