<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.surfshark.Surfshark</id>

    <name>Surfshark</name>
    <summary>Connect to secure, private web!</summary>
    <url type="homepage">https://surfshark.com/</url>
    <url type="contact">https://support.surfshark.com/</url>

    <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://surfshark.com/terms-of-service</project_license>
    <developer id="com.surfshark">
        <name>Surfshark B.V</name>
    </developer>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Surfshark interface</caption>
            <image type="source">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.surfshark.Surfshark/master/screenshots/screenshot_main.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Static locations</caption>
            <image type="source">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.surfshark.Surfshark/master/screenshots/screenshot_static_locations.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Multihop locations</caption>
            <image type="source">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.surfshark.Surfshark/master/screenshots/screenshot_multihop_locations.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <description>
        <p><em>Protect yourself with Surfshark VPN for Linux!</em></p>
        <p>Surfshark VPN app will protect you on both public and home Wi-Fi. It offers a VPN with global server infrastructure, ad blocker, and double 	VPN (MultiHop) servers.</p>
        <p>Independently audited by Deloitte, Surfshark VPN doesn't track your activity. Surfshark has 3200+ RAM-only servers with speeds of up to 10Gbit/s in over 100 countries. That guarantees that your browsing is seamless, safe, and private.</p>
        <p><em>Secure the entire household:</em></p>
        <p>Forget counting devices. With a single subscription, you'll get unlimited simultaneous connections. Connect &amp; protect all your devices with Surfshark VPN.</p>
        <p><em>Safeguard your data &amp; privacy:</em></p>
        <p>Your ISP can see the websites you visit and the products you look for. With a VPN and its end-to-end encryption, your browsing remains private.</p>
        <p><em>Surf with blazing speeds:</em></p>
        <p>Surfshark offers 3200+ servers in over 100 countries. Use your favorite apps or browse websites lag-free with a secure and fast VPN connection.</p>
        <p><em>Keep your data private, even from us:</em></p>
        <p>Surfshark has a no-activity-logs policy, proven by audits, which ensures we don't see or collect your personal information, online activity, or location.</p>
        <p><em>Stay safe on public Wi-Fi:</em></p>
        <p>Public Wi-Fi is a safe space for hackers. And even more dangers might hide in these networks. A VPN connection protects your data &amp; ensures that it's safe.</p>
        <p><em>Access internet without censorship:</em></p>
        <p>Censorship might stand between you and your favorite things online. That's where a secure VPN steps in &amp; helps you regain your internet freedom.</p>
        <p><em>Block ads &amp; trackers:</em></p>
        <p>Websites collect info about you &amp; display ads based on your online habits. Surfshark stops those annoying ads and protects you from malware attacks.</p>
        <ul>
            <li><em>Discover more Surfshark Linux app features:</em></li>
            <li><em>Global server network</em> - travel the world without leaving your room with more than 3200 VPN servers in over 100 countries.</li>
            <li><em>CleanWeb</em> - block ads, trackers, malware, and phishing attempts.</li>
            <li><em>MultiHop</em> - select two different servers to connect through simultaneously</li>
            <li><em>Camouflage mode</em> - connect to obfuscated servers and make the VPN connection look like regular browsing.</li>
            <li><em>24/7 customer support</em> - get help via live chat, email, or social media. You can also check our Blog and Help Center.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>If you have any questions, contact us directly at <em>support@surfshark.com</em> or via live chat.</p>
    </description>
    <categories>
        <category>Utility</category>
    </categories>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.surfshark.Surfshark.desktop</launchable>
    <branding>
        <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#FFFFFF</color>
        <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#16191C</color>
    </branding>
    <releases>
        <release version="3.0.4" date="2024-08-12" />
    </releases>
</component>
