<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.snipaste.Snipaste</id>
  <name>Snipaste</name>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.snipaste.com/eula.html</project_license>
  <developer_name>Snipaste</developer_name>
  <summary>Snipaste is not just a snipping tool. It will boost your productivity if you get used to its 'paste'!</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.snipaste.Snipaste.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.snipaste.com</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.snipaste.com/support.html</url>
  <description>
    <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by Snipaste.</p>
    <p>Snipaste consists of three major functionalities: Snip, Image Annotation and Paste.</p>
    <p>Snipaste is a versatile and user-friendly application designed to enhance productivity through its core features: snipping, pasting, and image annotation. It’s a powerful yet simple tool that lets you capture screenshots, pin them back onto your screen as floating windows, and annotate them with ease.</p>
    <p>With its snipping functionality, you can take precise screenshots of specific areas, windows, or even full screens. It stands out by automatically detecting UI elements and offering pixel-level control for accuracy, making it great for detailed work. You can also revisit past snips through a snipping history feature.</p>
    <p>The pasting feature is unique—it takes whatever’s in your clipboard (like images, text, or color data) and turns it into a floating window that stays on top of other applications. These windows can be resized, rotated, flipped, made translucent, or even set to allow mouse clicks to pass through, which is handy for reference while working. </p>
    <p>For annotation, Snipaste provides tools to mark up your captures with lines, shapes, text, and more, all customizable to suit your needs. It’s intuitive to use with mouse controls, but it also offers keyboard shortcuts for efficiency—perfect for power users like programmers or designers.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/flathub/a349920bdf6aa67f904cb53f0b35cfb2238ed689/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/flathub/a349920bdf6aa67f904cb53f0b35cfb2238ed689/screenshot-about.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="v2.10.5" date="2025-01-01">
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <update_contact>snipaste.app@gmail.com</update_contact>
</component>
