<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022 Laurin Neff -->
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.gitlab.KRypt0n_.an-anime-game-launcher</id>
    <name>An Anime Game Launcher</name>
    <summary>Play your favorite anime game on Linux</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="de">Spielen Sie Ihr Lieblings-Anime-Spiel auf Linux</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ru">Играйте в вашу любимую аниме-игру на линуксе</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="es">Juega a tu juego favorito de anime en Linux</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="it">Gioca al tuo gioco anime preferito su Linux</summary>
    <description>
        <p>An Anime Game Launcher is an unofficial launcher for a certain video game that handles setting up Wine, installing the game, and patching it to work on Linux.</p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="de">
        <p>An Anime Game Launcher ist ein inoffizieller Launcher für ein bestimmtes Videospiel, welcher die Einrichtung von Wine, die Installation des Spiels und das Patchen, dass es unter Linux läuft, übernimmt.</p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="ru">
        <p>An Anime Game Launcher - это неофициальный лаунчер для определённой видео-игры, который настраивает Wine, устанавливает игру и применяет дополнительные патчи для предоставления возможности её работы на линуксе.</p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="es">
        <p>Launcher de un Juego de Anime es un launcher no oficial para cierto videojuego. Se encarga de configurar Wine, instalar el juego, y parchearlo para que funcione en Linux.</p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="it">
        <p>An Anime Game Launcher è un launcher non ufficiale per un certo videogioco anime che gestisce e configura automaticamente Wine, l'installazione e patching del gioco per farlo funzionare su Linux.</p>
    </description>
    <developer_name>An Anime Team</developer_name>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://gitlab.com/KRypt0n_/an-anime-game-launcher/-/raw/main/repository/pics/launcher-main.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://gitlab.com/KRypt0n_/an-anime-game-launcher/-/raw/main/repository/pics/launcher-settings.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.gitlab.KRypt0n_.an-anime-game-launcher.desktop</launchable>
    <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.com/KRypt0n_/an-anime-game-launcher</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.com/KRypt0n_/an-anime-game-launcher/-/issues</url>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <categories>
        <category>Game</category>
    </categories>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">moderate</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">mild</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="money-gambling">moderate</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>

    <releases>
        <release version="2.0.0" date="2022-01-12">
            <p>For the last 20 days, we've made a lot of changes. This update contains 10,000 added lines of code, and more than 5,000 lines of code were deleted</p>
            <p>Our greatest achievement is that the launcher was moved to neutralino from the electron</p>
            <p>Neutralino is a platform that uses native system web components, while electron was bundling chromium binaries inside of the project build. As a result - the new launcher's build size was extremely decreased to an amazing 5 MB instead of more than 100 MB that we had with electron!</p>
            <p>The new launcher also has a new config files format, and that means that you'll have to move your previous configs manually</p>

            <h3>And what was changed?</h3>

            <h4>Core</h4>
            <p>Was totally reworked launcher's core. Well, it's better to say that we've made launcher's core. Now it has a lot of basic libraries, which, for example, launcher uses to download files or unpack archives. It also means that the development process was amazingly improved and now it'll be a lot easier to fix some issues or provide new functionality</p>

            <h4>Frontend</h4>
            <p>Instead of using cash-dom to manually manage launcher's components, we've moved all the frontend to the svelte library. Now everything will be a lot more smooth, and it also extremely simplified development process</p>

            <h4>Voice packages system</h4>
            <p>We've reworked the voice packages system. Now, instead of deleting already installed voice package, user can select which packages he wants to have installed, and launcher will properly update them when it will be required</p>

            <h4>By the way, updates...</h4>
            <p>Now launcher handles them a lot better! Instead of saving the currently installed game's information to the config file, launcher automatically parses this information from the game's files. It also means that it'll cause a lot lesser issues</p>
            <p>Also was extremely improved patches applying mechanism. Now launcher doing it a lot better</p>

            <h4>Logging</h4>
            <p>We've also made a new debugging system. Instead of looking for errors in chrome's console, now you can see everything that's happening in the launcher inside of the log files that saves in the logs folder</p>

            <h4>Increased performance</h4>
            <p>Thanks to the new platform, new frontend framework, and extremely improved core library now launcher work a lot faster than before</p>
            <p>Also now it caches some data which also increases its performance and decreases loading time</p>

            <h4>Of course, some things were changed</h4>
            <p>For example, redesigned Discord RPC settings, added AMD FSR option, redesigned wine version selection, changed recommended runners list...</p>
            <p>Also was made some QoL changes: new launcher properly downloads default wine version and DXVK, and when you're downloading some wine version or DXVK in settings - it'll be automatically selected. Wine versions lists now hide to not to show a lot of options</p>

            <h4>And was highly improved stability</h4>
            <p>For the beta versions testing period we had no one who had issues like "DXVK wasn't applied" or "wine wasn't installed". And thanks to the new debugging system we were able to extremely easy find the reason for some issues</p>
            <p>Thanks to everyone who participated in beta versions testing! Thanks to all of you we fixed a lot of things before this release!</p>
        </release>
    </releases>

    <update_contact>laurin at laurinneff dot ch</update_contact>
</component>