<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.redis.RedisInsight</id>

    <name>RedisInsight</name>
    <summary>The best Redis GUI</summary>

    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>SSPL-1.0</project_license>
    <developer_name>Redis, Inc</developer_name>

    <description>
        <p>Take your productivity to the next level when developing with Redis or Redis Stack! Use
            RedisInsight to visualize and optimize Redis data. A powerful desktop manager,
            RedisInsight provides an intuitive and efficient UI for Redis and Redis Stack and
            supports CLI interaction in a fully-featured desktop UI client.</p>
        <p>
            <b>Get a visual view of Redis data</b>
        </p>
        <p>The RedisInsight graphic user interface helps you visually browse and interact with Redis
            data.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Browse, filter, and visualize Redis keys, perform CRUD operations, or delete keys in
                bulk.</li>
            <li>Display data in pretty-print JSON, hexadecimal, MessagePack, and many other formats.
                Use friendly keyboard navigation.</li>
            <li>Use the Tree view to group data and enhance the navigation.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            <b>Intuitive CLI</b>
        </p>
        <p>Workbench, our advanced CLI, allows you to run Redis commands with the built-in Monaco
            Editor. It has syntax highlighting, developer shortcuts, and auto-completion.</p>
        <p>
            <b>Manage streams and consumer groups</b>
        </p>
        <p>Visualize Redis Streams and consumer groups, and set an automatic refresh to display new
            entries in real-time. Use a dedicated workspace for Redis Pub/Sub to publish and consume
            messages.</p>
        <p>
            <b>Log analysis and command profiling</b>
        </p>
        <p>Troubleshoot performance issues, trace and debug your Redis server by seeing commands
            processed in real-time and inspecting slow commands.</p>
    </description>

    <url type="homepage">https://redis.com/redis-enterprise/redis-insight/</url>
    <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/RedisInsight/RedisInsight</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/RedisInsight/RedisInsight/issues</url>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.redis.RedisInsight.desktop</launchable>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>
                https://github.com/RedisInsight/RedisInsight/raw/main/.github/redisinsight_browser.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

    <releases>
        <release version="2.14.0" date="2022-11-30" />
    </releases>
</component>