<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">

	<id>com.lunarclient.LunarClient</id>

	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>

	<name>Lunar Client</name>

	<summary>A modpack for all modern versions of Minecraft!</summary>

	<description>
		<p>Boosted frames, all the popular mods, multi OS support, and did we mention it’s
			completely free? So what are you waiting for - Download today!
		</p>
	</description>

	<categories>
		<category>Game</category>
	</categories>

	<url type="homepage">https://lunarclient.com</url>
	<url type="help">https://support.lunarclient.com</url>
	<url type="faq">https://www.lunarclient.com/faq</url>

	<launchable type="desktop-id">com.lunarclient.LunarClient.desktop</launchable>

	<releases>
		<release version="2.9.3" date="2021-12-03">
			<url>https://www.lunarclient.com/news/patch-notes-17/</url>
			<description>
				<p>
					Hey everyone, our primary focus these past few weeks has been to fix bugs,
					implement new mods, and add quality of life features!
				</p>

				<p>
					We finally have the much-requested Quickplay Mod. This mod allows you to switch
					games on the Hypixel Network seamlessly.
					We also added a new mod called “Snaplook” that will enable you to change/toggle
					your perspective by pressing a set key (no, this is not freelook).
					Lastly, we added the 3D Skins mod that allows you to add more details to your
					extra skin layers.
					Along with adding these new mods, we completely revamped the Crosshair Mod,
					fixed some much-needed bugs, and improved various aspects of our UI.
					Oh – we also have Discord linking! If you aren’t yet in our Discord, make sure
					to join!
				</p>

				<p>
					Also, we are aware of launching issues on Intel macOS on versions 1.7, 1.8, and
					1.12.
					We are actively working on a solution and should have an update for this soon,
					sorry for the inconvenience.
				</p>

				<p>
					If you have any suggestions to improve Lunar Client, make sure to interact with
					us on our social media accounts.
				</p>

				<p>
					We are still actively searching for new hires. Specifically, we are looking for
					new client developers to implement and create new Hypixel Skyblock mods.
					Visit our jobs page for all relevant information.
					Thank you all for the constant support; Lunar Client is made for the players, by
					the players.
				</p>

				<p>
					New mods
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<p>
							Quickplay Mod
						</p>
						<p>
							A mod that allows you to quickly play games on the Hypixel Network
						</p>
						<p>
							Original Creator: buggfroggy
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							3D Skins Mod
						</p>
						<p>
							A mod that allows you to add additional depth and detail to the extra
							layers on your skin.
						</p>
						<p>
							Original Creator: tr7zw
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Snaplook Mod
						</p>
						<p>
							A mod that allows you to change your perspective with a key pressed.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ul>

				<p>
					Features
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<p>
							Crosshair Mod 2.0
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Added a “Presets” tab to allow users to quickly select popular
								crosshairs
							</li>
							<li>Added a custom crosshair editor to allow users to make their own
								crosshairs
							</li>
							<li>Added the ability to save and share your custom crosshairs
								(LCCH-7-FMqas6ZQAA copy that to your clipboard and hit the import
								button!)
							</li>
							<li>Added a hover animation when previewing the crosshair</li>
							<li>Added a vanilla blending color option</li>
							<li>Completely reworked the UI and added radio buttons to switch between
								modes and colors
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Item Stitching Fix
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed a Vanilla Minecraft issue where item’s pixels were slightly
								off causing gaps

							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Hypixel Autocomplete
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Added a setting in “Hypixel Mods” that allows the user to tab
								complete useful commands such as /play, /party, /friend, /guild,
								etc.
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Discord Linking
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Added a button on the main menu to allow users to link their
								Minecraft username to their Discord
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
				</ul>

				<p>
					Improvements
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<p>
							Version 1.18
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Added Realms support</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Level Head
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Added a randomized level to nicked players</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Emotes
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Added an option to disable Emotes in Lunar Client settings</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Slider Improvements
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Clicking on the slider number allows you to edit it
							</li>
							<li>Integer sliders now show numbers as “X” instead of “X.0”</li>
							<li>Slider interpolation has been improved, should be less jerky while
								dragging it around
							</li>
							<li>Integer sliders now round to the nearest integer, instead of
								flooring the value
							</li>
							<li>Dragging a slider reveals the segments it rounds to
							</li>
							<li>Holding SHIFT while dragging rounds as follows, based on (max-min):
								<ul>
									<li>0-9.99 =&gt; roundTo = 0.1</li>
									<li>10-99.9 =&gt; roundTo = 1</li>
									<li>100-999.9 =&gt; roundTo = 10</li>
								</ul>
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							UI Improvements
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Dragging mods now switches the cursor to the MOVE pointer</li>
							<li>Hovering over a text input field switches the cursor to the IBEAM
								pointer
							</li>
							<li>Fixed mods failing to snap correctly sometimes after releasing the
								mouse button
							</li>
							<li>Fixed the center snap not actually snapping mods</li>
							<li>Mods now no longer snap to hidden mods (like Bedwars mod if you
								aren’t on Bedwars)
							</li>
							<li>It’s now easier to position mods on the edge of the screen</li>
							<li>The outline of mods positioned next to each other is now 1 pixel
								thick instead of 2 pixels
							</li>
							<li>Vertically centered the LC buttons (mods, cosmetics, logo, etc.)
							</li>
							<li>Added missing mod icons for a few mods</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Tab Logos
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Slightly improved the quality of the Lunar Client logos in tab</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>

						<p>
							Lunar Client Notifications
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Properly centered Lunar Client logo and text</li>
							<li>Use higher resolution Lunar Client logo</li>
							<li>Changed all mods/settings that used chat to tell its state to use
								Lunar Client notifications
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
				</ul>

				<p>
					Bug fixes
				</p>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<p>
							Xbox Game Pass
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue that disallowed users to play on Lunar Client if they
								were using an Xbox Game Pass account
							</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Color Saturation
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue where if you changed perspective the color saturation
								shader would get disabled
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Auto Text Hotkey
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue where typing in the text box would not update what
								you typed
							</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Item Physics
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue where Item Physics mod wasn’t overriding the “Dropped
								Items: Fast” option on 1.7.10 causing the items to render wrong
							</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Main Menu Panorama
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue where the main menu panorama looked pixelated and
								blurry on 1.17
							</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>

						<p>
							HUD Mods
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue with certain HUD mods that rendered items/blocks not
								having proper lighting
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>

						<p>
							Nick Hider
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue where the “Show Real Skin” option would not account
								for the Alex model causing skins to have black bars on their arms
							</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							Backpacks
						</p>

						<ul>
							<li>Fixed an issue causing backpacks to not render on 1.16+</li>
						</ul>

					</li>
				</ul>

			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="2.8.4" date="2021-9-26">
			<url>https://www.lunarclient.com/news/patch-notes-15/</url>
		</release>
		<release version="2.7.5" date="2021-8-29">
			<description>
				<p>Weather changer</p>
				<p>
					First flatpak release
				</p>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>

	<requires>
		<control>keyboard</control>
	</requires>

	<project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>

	<developer_name>Moonsworth</developer_name>

	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image>
				https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Doomsdayrs/flathub/com.lunarclient.LunarClient/screenshots/home.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image>
				https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Doomsdayrs/flathub/com.lunarclient.LunarClient/screenshots/servers.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image>
				https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Doomsdayrs/flathub/com.lunarclient.LunarClient/screenshots/settings.png
			</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>

	<content_rating type="oars-1.1">
		<content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">moderate</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">moderate</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="social-info">intense</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="money-advertising">moderate</content_attribute>
	</content_rating>

	<agreement type="eula" version_id="2021.05.26">
		<agreement_section id="0">
			<name>General Information</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					Welcome to the Lunar Client!
					These Terms governs your access to and use of the Services, as defined herein,
					and any associated content related updates, upgrades, and features.
					These Terms are a legally binding agreement between you and Moonsworth, LLC.
					Read these Terms carefully before using the Services.
					By accessing the Services, you hereby agree and assent to all terms, conditions,
					and obligations herein.
					IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS OR ANY PORTION THEREOF, YOU MAY NOT USE OR
					OTHERWISE ACCESS THE SERVICES.
				</p>

				<p>
					We may amend these Terms at any time by posting a revised version on the
					Website.
					Each revised version will state its effective date, which will be effective on
					or after the date in which it is posted or sent.
					Your continued use of the Services after the effective date constitutes your
					acceptance of the revised Terms.
				</p>

				<p>
					These Terms are, at all times, subject to our Privacy Policy
					(https://www.lunarclient.com/privacy/), as amended from time to time.
				</p>

				<p>
					By using the Services, you confirm that you are above the minimum age and are
					not barred from using the Services under applicable law.
				</p>

				<p>
					THE LUNAR CLIENT IS AN INDEPENDENT MINECRAFT MOD.
					NEITHER THE LUNAR CLIENT NOR MOONSWORTH LLC IS AFFILIATED WITH, ENDORSED BY, OR
					OTHERWISE CONNECTED TO MOJANG AB OR THE MICROSOFT CORPORATION.
					THE TERMS “MINECRAFT,” “MOJANG,” MICROSOFT, AND ANY OTHER PRODUCT MARKS,
					TRADEMARKS, LOGOS, WORD MARKS, OR SERVICE MARKS, ALONG WITH MINECRAFT AND
					UNDERLYING MATERIALS THEREIN ARE THE PROPERTY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE OWNERS.
					USE OF THE FOREGOING DOES NOT IMPLY ANY AFFILIATION WITH OR ENDORSEMENT MOJANG
					OR MICROSOFT.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="1">
			<name>Definitions</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					“Account” means, any individual User account that is automatically created when
					you use the Services and is linked Minecraft account.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Communication Services” means the chat function and any other related service
					that Lunar Client Users can use to communicate and interact with one another
				</p>

				<p>
					“Company” means Moonsworth, LLC. References to “us” “we,” or “our” means
					Company, including any and all subsidiaries, parent companies, joint ventures,
					and other corporate entities under common ownership and/or any of their agents,
					consultants, employees, oﬃcers, and directors.
					Company does not include affiliates or third parties (analytics or ad tech
					companies, or similar organizations).
				</p>

				<p>
					“Cosmetic Items” means those digital items for use in Minecraft that are
					produced and offered for sale by the Lunar Client.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Dispute” means any controversy related to this agreement, including without
					limitation claims arising out of or relating to any aspect of the relationship
					between you and Company, claims that arose before these Terms, and claims that
					may arise after the termination of these Terms; however, this does not include
					claims related to or arising from the enforcement or protection of Intellectual
					Property Rights, and is subject to any applicable statutory consumer rights laws
					in your local jurisdiction.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Intellectual Property Rights” means, any and all right, title, and interest of
					every kind whatsoever, whether now known or unknown, in and to patents, trade
					secret rights, copyrights, trademarks, service marks, trade dress and similar
					rights of any type under the laws of any governmental authority, including,
					without limitation, all applications and registrations relating to the
					foregoing.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Lunar Client” a Minecraft mod server that is owned and operated by Company and
					available via the Website.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Minecraft” means the computer game known as Minecraft, which is produced and
					operated by Mojang AB.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Notice” means a delivered writing by email, courier, or postal delivery to the
					other party at their respective address and will be eﬀective upon receipt.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Privacy Policy” means the Company policy regarding data privacy, which also
					governs your use of the Services and is incorporated herein by reference.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Protected Content” means all content, included as part of the Services and any
					compilation thereof including, without limitation, Cosmetic Items, the look and
					feel of the Services, the text, graphics, source code, sound recordings, musical
					composition, narrative, characters, images, literary works, and any other works
					of authorship or other materials contained therein, whether or not protectable
					by copyright, trademark, or other applicable law or legal theory.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Services” means the Lunar Client and the Website, inclusive of any associated
					services or materials thereon.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Terms” means these terms of service and end user license agreement and any
					terms, conditions, covenants, representations, warranties, obligations, and
					licenses contained herein.
				</p>

				<p>
					“User ,” “you” or “your” means any user of the Services, or any or owner,
					officer, employee, affiliate, or agent of the same that uses the Services or any
					portion thereof.
				</p>

				<p>
					“User Generated Content” means any photos, images, likenesses, logos, marks,
					literary works, sound recordings, musical composition, audiovisual works and
					programs, modes, animations, names, and any other content or materials posted or
					otherwise integrated into the Services via the User including, without
					limitation, user submitted info about parks and outdoor locations.
				</p>

				<p>
					“Website” means the online website “https://www.lunarclient.com/” including all
					sub-pages, sub-domains, and associated domains thereof.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="2">
			<name>License</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					The Services are licensed to you for your personal use and entertainment.
					Company hereby grants you a personal, limited, non-transferable, fully,
					revocable, and non-exclusive License to use the Services for your non-commercial
					use, subject to your compliance with these Terms.
					You may not access, copy, modify or distribute the Services, unless expressly
					authorized by Company or permitted by applicable law.
					You may not reverse engineer or attempt to extract or otherwise use source code
					or other data from the Services, unless expressly authorized by Company or
					permitted by law.
					Company or its licensors own and reserve all other rights, including all right,
					title and interest in the Services and all materials or content therein, and all
					associated Intellectual Property Rights.
				</p>
				<p>
					If you purchase any Cosmetic Items, Company hereby grants you a limited,
					non-exclusive, non-commercial license to use the Cosmetic Item within the Lunar
					Client.
					You acknowledge and agree that you may not reproduce, re-distribute, transmit,
					copy, publish, publicly perform or display, or create derivative works based on
					the Cosmetic Item or otherwise use or exploit the Cosmetic Item in any manner
					not authorized by these Terms.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="3">
			<name>License Restrictions and Prohibited Conduct</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					You may not do any of the following with respect to the Services or any
					components thereof:
				</p>
				<ol>
					<li>
						Use the Services commercially or for a promotional purpose, except as
						otherwise authorized herein;
					</li>
					<li>
						Copy, reproduce, distribute, display, publicly perform, publish, or use the
						Services or any portion or aspect thereof, in any way that is not expressly
						authorized in these Terms;
					</li>
					<li>
						Reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble or otherwise attempt to discover
						the source code of the Services or any part thereof, except and only to the
						extent that this activity is expressly permitted by the applicable law of
						your country of residence;
					</li>
					<li>
						Modify, adapt, translate or create derivative works based upon the Services
						or any part thereof, except and only to the extent that such activity is
						expressly permitted these Terms or by applicable law notwithstanding this
						limitation;
					</li>
					<li>
						Remove, circumvent, disable, damage or otherwise interfere with
						security-related features of the Services;
					</li>
					<li>
						Access the Services or any website, server, software application, or other
						computer resource owned, used and/or licensed by Company, by means of any
						robot, spider, scraper, crawler or other automated means for any purpose, or
						bypass any measures Company may use to prevent or restrict access to any
						website, server, software application, or other computer resource owned,
						used and/or licensed to Company;
					</li>
					<li>
						Interfere with or disrupt the Services or servers or networks connected to
						the Services, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or
						regulations of networks connected to the Services;
					</li>
					<li>
						Harvest or collect the email addresses or other contact information of other
						Users;
					</li>
					<li>
						Use the Services for any illegal purpose, or in violation of any local,
						state, national, or international law or regulation, including, without
						limitation, laws governing intellectual property and other proprietary
						rights, data protection and privacy.
					</li>
				</ol>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="4">
			<name>Children Under 18</name>
			<description>
				<ol>
					<li>
						By using the Services, you warrant and represent that you: 1) are at least
						18 years of age and otherwise legally competent to read, understand and
						accept the provisions of this agreement; or 2) are a minor who has been
						authorized under the provisions of Section 4(b) below.
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>
							If you are the legal guardian of a minor, you can choose to allow use of
							the Services by that minor instead of yourself subject to the following
							provisions:
						</p>
						<ol>
							<li>
								You acknowledge, and further agree that the aforementioned minor is
								entering into an agreement with your consent;
							</li>
							<li>
								You acknowledge, and further agree you are entirely responsible for
								all the provisions in these Terms;
							</li>
							<li>
								You acknowledge, and further agree, you are legally responsible for
								all actions of that minor, including but not limited to any
								payments, damages and/or liabilities related to the actions of that
								minor;
							</li>
							<li>
								In consideration of Company allowing access to the Services by a
								minor, and in addition to the indemnification provisions set forth
								herein, the foregoing adult hereby guarantees and agrees to pay for
								any and all liabilities of any nature whatsoever incurred under this
								agreement and to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Company with
								respect thereto.
							</li>
						</ol>
					</li>
				</ol>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="5">
			<name>Account</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					When use the Services, a unique Lunar Client Account will automatically generate
					for you that is linked to your personal Minecraft account.
					All Accounts are subject to these Terms.
					You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of
					your Account and password.
					Such security includes but is not limited to restricting access to your
					computer, laptop, tablet, or mobile device that you use to access the Services
					and/or where such password may be stored.
					You agree that you are solely responsible for all activities and actions that
					occur under the auspices of your Account.
					You agree not to assign or otherwise transfer your Account to or share your
					password with any other person or entity.
					You acknowledge and agree that Company is not responsible for third-party access
					to your Account that results from theft or misappropriation of your password or
					other Account credentials.
					You hereby acknowledge and agree that any action taken under your Account will
					be presumed to have been authorized by you.
				</p>
				<p>
					You further acknowledge and agree that by using Minecraft or setting up a
					Minecraft account, you may be subject to an agreement(s) with the Microsoft
					Corporation and/or Mojang AB.
					For your reference, Mojang’s terms and conditions are available
					(https://account.mojang.com/terms) and the Microsoft services agreement is
					available (https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/servicesagreement).
					You acknowledge and agree that Company is not a party to any of the foregoing
					agreements or any other agreements between you and Microsoft and/or Mojang and
					compliance with such agreements is not monitored, enforced, or controlled by
					Company.
					If Company receives notice that your activity violates any of the foregoing or
					any similar agreement between you and Microsoft, Mojang, or any other third
					party, Company may, in our sole discretion take action against your Account to
					bring you into compliance with such agreements.
					Such actions may include canceling a transaction and suspending or terminating
					your Account privileges and/or removing certain payment methods.
				</p>
				<p>
					You further acknowledge and agree that by signing up for an Account via your
					existing Minecraft account, you are providing Company with limited access any
					information including any personal information about you contained within in
					your Minecraft Account and associated credentials for the purpose of creating
					and interacting with your Account.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="6">
			<name>Electronic Communication</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					Each and every time you send an email or other electronic communication to
					Company, such communication will constitute an electronic communication.
					By using the Services, you consent to receive electronic communications and you
					agree that all agreements, Notices, disclosures and other communications that
					Company provides to you via electronic communication, individually and
					collectively, satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in
					writing.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="7">
			<name>Cosmetic Items</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					We may make available for purchase certain Cosmetic Items on the Company
					Website.
					Any information regarding Cosmetic Items (including pricing) and the
					availability of any Cosmetic Items (including the validity of any coupon or
					discount) are subject to change at any time without notice.
					We shall not be liable to you or to any third-party for any modification, price
					change, suspension or discontinuance of the Cosmetic Items, Website, or Service.
					We make reasonable efforts to accurately display the attributes of Cosmetic
					Items, including the applicable colors, however the actual colors you see will
					depend on your computer system, and we cannot guarantee that your computer will
					accurately display such colors.
				</p>
				<p>
					By making a transaction, you represent that the applicable Cosmetic Items will
					be used only in accordance with these Terms.
					You agree that you will not resell any Cosmetic Items obtained through a
					transaction, unless we have provided our express prior written consent for you
					to do so.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="8">
			<name>Transactions</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					If you wish to purchase a Cosmetic Item, you are required to pay the applicable
					purchase price.
					Unless otherwise indicated, all fees and other charges are in U.S. dollars, and
					all payments shall be in U.S. currency or the equivalent amount of
					cryptocurrency as excepted by Coinbase Commerce.
				</p>
				<ol>
					<li>
						Billing and Account Information.
						We partner with third-party payment processors including PayPal, Coinbase
						Commerce, and XSolla (each a “Payment Processor”) to facilitate credit card
						and other payments, in connection with your purchase of the Cosmetic Items.
						Payment processing time will vary depending on your location.
						You will receive a receipt from the applicable Payment Processor confirming
						payment. If your payment is rejected for any reason, including insufficient
						funds, Company reserves the right to contact you directly to seek payment.
						By using a Payment Processor, you may be subject to an agreement with such
						Payment Processor.
						If Company receives notice that your activity violates any agreement between
						you and or any other Payment Processor, Company may, in our sole discretion
						take action against your Account to bring you into compliance with such
						agreements.
						Such actions may include canceling a transaction, suspending your Account
						privileges and/or removing certain payment methods.
						You agree to provide current, complete, and accurate purchase information
						for all transactions conducted via Payment Processors.
					</li>
					<li>
						YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT COMPANY IS NOT A BROKER, FINANCIAL
						INSTITUTION, CREDITOR, INSURER OR CHARITABLE ORGANIZATION AND COMPANY HAS NO
						CONTROL OVER THE CONDUCT OF OR ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED BY ANY PAYMENT
						PROCESSOR, INCLUDING ANY TERMS, SERVICES, CONDITIONS, REPRESENTATIONS,
						COVENANTS, OR WARRANTIES SET FORTH IN ANY AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND SUCH
						PAYMENT PROCESSOR AND COMPANY HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY IN THIS REGARD
						TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.
					</li>
					<li>
						NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ANY COSMETIC
						ITEM SOLD BY COMPANY IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” BASIS AND EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE
						EXPRESSLY PROVIDED IN THESE TERMS, COMPANY DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND
						WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE COSMETIC ITEM, INCLUDING ANY
						IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR FITNESS FOR A
						PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES ARISING OUT OF A COURSE OF
						PERFORMANCE, DEALING OR TRADE USAGE.
					</li>
					<li>
						Refunds. Company may, in its sole discretion, issue refunds to users that
						purchase defective or otherwise unacceptable Cosmetic Items.
						To request a refund, please create a support ticket at
						https://support.lunarclient.com
					</li>
				</ol>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="9">
			<name>Intellectual Property Ownership</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					All Protected Content is the property of Company or its third-party
					suppliers/licensors and protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws that
					protect intellectual property and proprietary rights. You agree to observe and
					abide by all copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices, legends or
					other restrictions contained in any such content and will not make any changes
					thereto.
				</p>
				<p>
					You will not modify, publish, transmit, reverse engineer, participate in the
					transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit any of the
					Protected Content, in whole or in part, found within the Services. Your use of
					the Services does not entitle you to make any unauthorized use of any of the
					Protected Content, and in particular you shall not delete or alter any
					proprietary rights or attribution notices in any Protected Content. You shall
					use Protected Content solely for your personal use, as outlined in these Terms,
					and will make no other use of the Protected Content without the express written
					permission of Company and/or Protected Content’s third-party owner, if
					applicable. You acknowledge and agree that you do not acquire any ownership
					rights in any Protected Content. Except as provided for herein, these Terms do
					not grant any licenses, express or implied, to the Protected Content or any
					other intellectual property of Company, our licensors, or any third-party.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="10">
			<name>User Generated Content</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					By creating any User Generated Content, you hereby grant Company a nonexclusive,
					perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, paid-up, fully transferable and
					sublicensable license to reproduce, modify, host, copy, display, publicly
					perform, create derivative works of, publicly display, transfer, or otherwise
					use or exploit such User Generated Content, in whole or in part, including
					within the Services and for any commercial, promotional, publicity, and
					marketing purposes.
				</p>
				<p>
					You hereby represent that any User Generated Content you create is wholly
					original and you own all right, title, and interest to such User Generated
					Content or otherwise have the legal right and authority to integrate such User
					Generated Content into the Services and grant the license to Company as
					described herein. You further warrant that the authorized use or exploitation of
					the User Generated Content, will not violate any third-party rights including,
					without limitation, any copyright, trademarks or other intellectual property
					rights, privacy rights, or statutory or common law rights of publicity in any
					jurisdiction.
				</p>
				<p>
					Company reserves the right to remove any User Generated Content that does not
					comply with the Agreement. Company may also remove User Generated Content that
					violates someone else’s rights, including without limitation any trademarks,
					copyrights, patent rights or similar, as well as statutory and common law rights
					of publicity. Finally, Company may remove the following:
				</p>
				<ol>
					<li>
						User Generated Content that harasses, defames, or disparages any individual
						including any harassing or pejorative comments based on any individual’s
						sex, sexual orientation, sexual preference, transgender status, gender
						identity, race, ethnicity, religion, or other protected class; or
					</li>
					<li>
						User Generated Content that may be considered misleading, fraudulent, or
						otherwise unlawful or that is uploaded for an illegal or unauthorized
						purpose.
					</li>
				</ol>
				<p>
					You acknowledge and agree that a violation of this Section 10 will constitute a
					material breach of this Agreement and if Company discovers you violated the
					Section it may, in its sole discretion, revoke your access to the Services at
					any time without Notice or refund.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="11">
			<name>Use of Communications Services.</name>
			<description>
				<p>
					You agree to use the Communications Services only to post, send, and receive
					written communications that are proper and related to the Services. Materials
					uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on
					usage, content, reproduction and/or dissemination. You acknowledge and agree
					that materials you upload to a Communication Service shall be deemed User
					Generated Content.
				</p>
				<p>
					YOU MAY NOT UPLOAD ANY PHOTOGRAPHS, PICTURES OF DOCUMENTS, PDFS, OR OTHER
					DOCUMENTS TO THE COMMUNICATION SERVICES. You are responsible for adhering to any
					limitations on your use of the Communications Services set forth herein
					andCompany reserves the right to terminate your access to any or all the
					Communications Services at any time, without Notice, for any reason whatsoever.
				</p>
				<p>
					By way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree that when using a
					Communication Service, you will not: defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or
					otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of
					others; publish, post, upload, distribute or disseminate any inappropriate,
					profane, defamatory, infringing, pornographic, obscene, indecent or unlawful
					topic, name, material or information; upload files that contain software or
					other material protected by intellectual property laws (or by rights of privacy
					of publicity) unless you own or control the rights thereto or have received all
					necessary licenses, consents, and permissions therefor; upload files that
					contain viruses, malware, corrupted files, or any other similar software or
					programs that may damage the operation of another’s computer; advertise or offer
					to sell or buy any goods or services for any business purpose; conduct or
					forward surveys, contests, pyramid schemes, or chain letters; download any file
					uploaded by another user of a Communication Service that you know, or reasonably
					should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner; falsify or delete any
					author attributions, legal or other proper notices or proprietary designations
					or labels of the origin or source of software or other material contained in a
					file that is uploaded; restrict or inhibit any other user from using and
					enjoying the Communication Services; violate any code of conduct or other
					guidelines which may be applicable for any particular Communication Service;
					harvest or otherwise collect information about others, including email
					addresses, without their consent; violate any applicable laws or regulations.
				</p>
				<p>
					Company has no obligation to monitor the Communication Services. However,
					Company reserves the right to review any and all materials uploaded to a
					Communication Service and to remove any materials in its sole discretion.
				</p>
				<p>
					YOU SHOULD ALWAYS USE CAUTION WHEN GIVING OUT ANY PERSONAL IDENTIFYING
					INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF OR YOUR CHILDREN OR FAMILY IN ANY COMMUNICATION
					SERVICE. COMPANY DOES NOT CONTROL OR ENDORSE THE CONTENT, MESSAGES OR
					INFORMATION FOUND IN ANY COMMUNICATION SERVICE AND, THEREFORE, COMPANY
					SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY WITH REGARD TO THE COMMUNICATION SERVICES
					AND ANY ACTIONS RESULTING FROM YOUR PARTICIPATION IN ANY COMMUNICATION SERVICE.
				</p>
			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="12">
			<name>Service Availability and Termination</name>
			<description>
				<p>You acknowledge and agree that:</p>

				<ol>
					<li>
						<p>Company has the discretion to immediately terminate or restrict access to
							the Services or any portion thereof, at any time, for any reason,
							without Notice and without liability to you;
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>Access to the Services may be interrupted for reasons within or beyond
							the control of Company and that Company cannot and does not guarantee
							you will be able to use the Services whenever you wish to do so;
						</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p>The Services may not be offered in all countries or geographic
							locations.
						</p>
					</li>
				</ol>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="13">
			<name>Company Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability and Remedies</name>
			<description>
				<p>COMPANY IS NOT A BROKER, FINANCIAL INSTITUTION, CREDITOR, INSURER OR CHARITABLE
					ORGANIZATION.
				</p>

				<p>All information and content provided by Company through the Services is for
					informational and entertainment purposes only and Company does not guarantee the
					accuracy, completeness, or timeliness or reliability of any such information or
					content.
				</p>

				<p>No content or information is intended to provide financial, legal, tax, or other
					professional advice. Before making any decisions regarding purchasing the use of
					the Services or the purchase any other good or service, whether virtual or
					tangible, offered by the Services, you should consult your financial, legal,
					tax, or other professional advisers as appropriate. You acknowledge that you
					access content or information through the Services at your own risk and you are
					solely responsible for making the final determination as to the value and
					appropriateness of using the same.
				</p>

				<p>USERS ARE NOT EMPLOYEES, PARTNERS, AGENTS, JOINT VENTURES, OR FRANCHISEES OF
					COMPANY. COMPANY DOES NOT PROVIDE FINANCIAL SUPPORT OR ASSISTANCE TO USERS.
					USERS HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT COMPANY DOES NOT SUPERVISE, DIRECT, CONTROL OR
					USERS AND EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR OR CONNECTED
					TO THE PAYMENTS OR OTHER USER SERVICES PERFORMED IN ANY MANNER, INCLUDING BUT
					NOT LIMITED TO A WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF GOOD AND WORKMANLIKE SERVICES,
					WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR COMPLIANCE WITH ANY LAW,
					REGULATION, OR CODE.
				</p>

				<p>TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, COMPANY WILL NOT BE
					RESPONSIBLE TO ANY USER FOR ANY SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, OR
					CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING LOST PROFITS OR LOSS OF DATA, REGARDLESS OF
					FORESEEABILITY AND COMPANY’S MAXIMUM LIABILITY UNDER THIS AGREEMENT WILL AT ALL
					TIMES BE LIMITED TO A REFUND OF ANY MONIES SPENT BY AN APPLICABLE USER HEREUDNER
					WITHIN THE SIX (6) MONTHS PRECEDING ANY ALLEGED BREACH OF THIS AGREEMENT BY
					COMPANY.
				</p>

				<p>YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT IN THE EVENT OF ANY BREACH OF THIS
					AGREEMENT BY COMPANY, YOUR REMEDIES SHALL BE LIMITED TO AN ACTION FOR DAMAGES,
					IF ANY AND AS LIMITED ABOVE AND IN NO EVENT SHALL YOU BE ENTITLED TO SEEK TO
					ENJOIN OR RESTRAIN COMPANY’S PERFORMANCE IN ANY MANNER. ACCORDINGLY, YOU
					EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT ANY DAMAGE TO YOU WILL NOT BE IRREPARABLE OR OTHERWISE
					INCALCULABLE SO AS TO ENTITLE YOU TO SEEK AND/OR OBTAIN EQUITABLE OR INJUNCTIVE
					RELIEF.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="14">
			<name>Prohibited Conduct</name>
			<description>
				<p>You are granted a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable License to access
					and use the Services, strictly in accordance with these Terms. As a condition of
					your use of the Services, you represent and warrant to Company that you will not
					use the Services for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms.
					Further, you agree that you will comply with these Terms and will not:
				</p>

				<ol>
					<li>Use the Services in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or
						impair the Website or Website servers, or otherwise interfere with any other
						party’s use and enjoyment of the Services;
					</li>
					<li>Obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means
						not intentionally made available or provided for through the Services;
					</li>
					<li>Impersonate any person or entity, falsely claim an affiliation with any
						person or entity, forge another person’s digital signature, misrepresent the
						source, identity, or content of information transmitted via the Services, or
						perform any other similar fraudulent activity;
					</li>
					<li>Defame, harass, abuse, threaten or defraud Users, or collect, or attempt to
						collect, personal information about Users or third parties without their
						consent; and
					</li>
					<li>Attempt to indicate in any manner that you have a relationship with Company
						or that Company has endorsed you or any products or services for any
						purpose.
					</li>
				</ol>

				<p>Company also reserves all available legal rights and remedies to prevent the
					unauthorized use of the Services, including, but not limited to, technological
					barriers, IP mapping, and contacting your internet service provider.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="15">
			<name>Representations and Warranties</name>
			<description>
				<p>In addition to any other representations and warranties made herein, you hereby
					represent and warrant that i) you are not prohibited from receiving or using any
					aspect of the Services under applicable laws and ii) Company has not previously
					disabled your access to the Services for a violation of the law or these Terms
					or other applicable agreements, terms of use, or contracts.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="16">
			<name>Links to Third Party Sites</name>
			<description>
				<p>The Services may contain links to third-party websites. The third-party websites
					are not under the control of Company and Company is not responsible for the
					contents of the same, including without limitation any link contained therein.
					Company is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion
					of any link does not imply endorsement by Company of the website or any
					association with its operators.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="17">
			<name>Device and Internet Connection</name>
			<description>
				<p>Use and access of the Services may require the use of your personal computer,
					laptop, tablet, or mobile device, as well as communication with or use of space
					on such device. You are solely responsible for all internet and/or mobile data
					connection and all associated fees that you incur when accessing the Services.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="18">
			<name>International Users</name>
			<description>
				<p>The Services are controlled, operated and administered by Company from our
					offices within the United States. If you access the Services from a location
					outside the United States, you are responsible for compliance with all local
					laws. You agree that you will not use the Services in any country or in any
					manner prohibited by any applicable laws, restrictions or regulations.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="19">
			<name>Release</name>
			<description>

				<p>You hereby agree to release Company from all damages (whether direct, indirect,
					incidental, consequential or otherwise), losses, liabilities, costs and expenses
					of every kind and nature, known and unknown, arising out of a dispute between
					you and a third-party (including other Users) in connection with the Services
					and any content therein. In furtherance of the foregoing, you hereby waive any
					applicable law or statute, which says, in substance: “A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT
					EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE RELEASING PARTY DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST IN
					HIS FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH IF KNOWN BY HIM MUST HAVE
					MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE RELEASED PARTY.”
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="20">
			<name>Indemnification</name>
			<description>
				<p>To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to indemnify, defend
					and hold harmless Company, its officers, directors, employees, agents and
					assigns from and against any and all claims, losses, costs, debt, liabilities
					and expenses (including, but not limited to attorney’s fees) arising from (i)
					your misuse of and access to the Services; (ii) your violation of these Terms;
					(iii) your violation of any third-party right, including without limitation any
					copyright, intellectual property, or privacy right; (iv) your use of or
					inability to use the Services; and (v) any claim that you caused damage to a
					third-party.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="21">
			<name>Dispute Resolution</name>
			<description>
				<p>In the event the parties are not able to resolve any Dispute between them arising
					out of or concerning these Terms, or any provisions hereof, whether in contract,
					tort, or otherwise at law or in equity for damages or any other relief, then,
					except as provided below, the parties hereby agree to submit any dispute they
					cannot resolve informally to final and binding arbitration. The arbitration will
					be conducted in New Castle County, Delaware before a single neutral arbitrator
					in accordance with the rules of the American Arbitration Association. The
					arbitrator will follow Delaware law in adjudicating the dispute. The arbitrator
					will provide a detailed written statement of decision, which will be part of the
					arbitration award and admissible in any judicial proceeding to confirm, correct
					or vacate the award. Interpretations of these Terms, including determinations of
					unconscionability, will be determined by the arbitrator selected through this
					provision. The parties will initially share the cost of such arbitration,
					provided that the prevailing party will be entitled to all fees and costs
					associated with arbitration (or enforcement of an award therefrom), including,
					but not limited to, reasonable attorney’s fees, from the other party upon
					completion of the arbitration or subsequent enforcement action.
				</p>

				<p>The parties acknowledge and agree that any action with respect to your
					infringement or alleged infringement of any Intellectual Property Rights, any
					action in which Company seeks equitable relief, or any other action that may not
					be submitted to arbitration under applicable law, including the enforcement of
					any arbitration ruling, shall be tried by a court of competent jurisdiction
					located in New Castle County, Delaware. In that respect, you hereby consent to
					the jurisdiction of the State of Delaware agree that its laws will be used to
					resolve all disputes arising from or concerning these Terms.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="22">
			<name>Class Action Waiver</name>
			<description>
				<p>Any arbitration under these Terms will take place on an individual basis; class
					arbitrations and class/representative/collective actions are not permitted. THE
					PARTIES AGREE THAT A PARTY MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN EACH
					PARTY’S INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY
					PUTATIVE CLASS, COLLECTIVE AND/ OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING, SUCH AS IN THE
					FORM OF A PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL ACTION AGAINST THE OTHER. Further, unless
					both you and Company agree otherwise, the arbitrator may not consolidate more
					than one person’s claims and may not otherwise preside over any form of a
					representative or class proceeding.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="23">
			<name>Termination and Access Restriction</name>
			<description>
				<p>Company reserves the right to terminate your access to the Services, or any
					portion thereof at any time, without Notice, for any reason including, without
					limitation, a breach of these Terms. Use of the Services is unauthorized in any
					jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms,
					including, without limitation, this section.
				</p>


			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="24">
			<name>Severability</name>
			<description>
				<p>In the event that any provision of these Terms is determined to be unlawful, void
					or unenforceable, such provision shall nonetheless be enforceable to the fullest
					extent permitted by applicable law, and the unenforceable portion shall be
					deemed to be severed from these Terms, such determination shall not affect the
					validity and enforceability of any other remaining provisions.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="25">
			<name>Miscellaneous</name>
			<description>
				<p>Company’s performance of the obligations described herein is subject to existing
					laws and legal process, and nothing contained in these Terms are in derogation
					of Company’s right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement
					requests or requirements relating to your use of the Services or information
					provided to or gathered by Company with respect to such use.
				</p>

				<p>These Terms, the Privacy Policy, and any other document incorporated herein by
					reference constitute the entire agreement between you and Company with respect
					to the Services and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications
					and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between you and Company with
					respect to the Services. A printed version of these Terms and of any Notice
					given in electronic form will be admissible in judicial or administrative
					proceedings based upon or relating to these Terms to the same extent and subject
					to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally
					generated and maintained in printed form. It is the express wish to the parties
					that these Terms and all related documents be written in English.
				</p>

				<p>These Terms are non-transferable, and you may not assign your rights and
					obligations under these Terms without the express written consent of Company.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="26">
			<name>Copyright Infringement Policy</name>
			<description>
				<p>Company is committed to protecting the rights of copyright rights holders and
					seeks to comply with all applicable laws and regulations regarding the
					protection of intellectual property.
				</p>

				<p>If you are a copyright owner or an agent thereof and believe that any User
					Generated Content on the Services infringes on your copyright, you may submit a
					notification pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) by
					providing our designated agent for copyright claim notifications (“Designated
					Agent”) with the following information in writing (see 17 U.S.C. §512(c)(3) for
					further detail):
				</p>

				<ol>
					<li>A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf
						of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
					</li>
					<li>Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or,
						if multiple copyrighted works within the Services are covered by a single
						notification, a representative list of such works that appear within the
						Services;
					</li>
					<li>Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the
						subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which
						is to be disabled and information reasonably sufficient to permit the
						service provider to locate the material;
					</li>
					<li>Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact
						you, such as an address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic
						mail;
					</li>
					<li>A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in
						the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its
						agent, or the law; and
					</li>
					<li>A statement under penalty of perjury that the information in the
						notification is accurate, and you are the owner of, or authorized to act on
						behalf of the owner of, an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
					</li>
				</ol>

				<p>Company will process any notices of alleged copyright infringement and will take
					appropriate actions as permitted under the DMCA. Upon receipt of notices
					complying with the DMCA, Company will act expeditiously to remove or disable
					access to any material claimed to be infringing or claimed to be the subject of
					infringing activity and will act expeditiously to remove or disable access to
					any reference or link to material or activity that is claimed to be infringing.
				</p>

				<p>The designated agent can be reached at: copyright@moonsworth.com</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="27">
			<name>DMCA Counter Claims</name>
			<description>

				<p>Company may notify the owner or administrator of the affected Content so that he
					or she can make a counter-notification pursuant to his or her rights under the
					DMCA. If you receive such a notice, you may provide counter-notification in
					writing to the Designated Agent. To be effective, the counter-notification must
					be a written communication that includes the following:
				</p>

				<ol>
					<li>Your physical or electronic signature;</li>
					<li>Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has
						been disabled, and the location at which the material appeared before it was
						removed or access to it was disabled;
					</li>
					<li>A statement from you under the penalty of perjury, that you have a good
						faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of a
						mistake or misidentification of the material to be removed or disabled; and
					</li>
				</ol>

				<p>Your name, physical address and telephone number, and a statement that you
					consent to the jurisdiction of a Federal District Court for the judicial
					district in which your physical address is located, or if your physical address
					is outside of the United States, for any judicial district in which Company may
					be found, and that you will accept service of process from the person who
					provided notification of allegedly infringing material or an agent of such
					person.
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
		<agreement_section id="28">
			<name>Contact</name>
			<description>
				<p>If you have any questions regarding your use of the Services or compliance with
					these Terms, please contact us at legal@moonsworth.com
				</p>

			</description>
		</agreement_section>
	</agreement>
</component>
