<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>com.protonvpn.ProtonVPN</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
    <name>Proton VPN</name>
    <summary>High-speed Swiss VPN that safeguards your privacy.</summary>
    <description>
        <p>ProtonVPN is a secure and free VPN, now featuring better connection stability, faster
            speeds, and even more security features.</p>
        <p>ProtonVPN is the world's ONLY free VPN service that respects your privacy and is safe
            to use. Millions of people use ProtonVPN because:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>We do not record your browsing history</li>
            <li>We do not display privacy-invading ads</li>
            <li>We do not sell your data to third parties</li>
            <li>We do not limit how much you can download</li>
        </ul>
        <p>ProtonVPN is created by the CERN scientists behind ProtonMail, the world's largest
            encrypted email service with 20 million users, including many activists and journalists
            such as Reporters Without Borders.</p>
        <p>ProtonVPN’s Free VPN Service includes:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>STRONG ENCRYPTION - Your data is protected with AES-256 and 4096 RSA.</li>
            <li>SWISS-BASED - Your data is protected by some of the strongest privacy laws in the
                world.</li>
            <li>NO LOGS. EVER - We never log or share user data. Even if authorities request
                information, we have nothing to share.</li>
            <li>PERFECT FORWARD SECRECY - Your encrypted traffic cannot be captured and decrypted
                later.</li>
            <li>MULTI-PROTOCOL SUPPORT - ProtonVPN supports secure VPN protocols: WireGuard and
                OpenVPN.</li>
            <li>DNS LEAK PROTECTION - We encrypt your DNS to ensure your browsing activity cannot be
                exposed through DNS queries.</li>
            <li>ALWAYS-ON VPN/KILL SWITCH - Protect your IP address from being leaked through
                accidental disconnects.</li>
            <li>FULL DISK ENCRYPTION - Our VPN servers are fully encrypted to protect your data.</li>
            <li>ANONYMOUS - You do not need to share any personal data to use ProtonVPN.</li>
            <li>SPLIT TUNNELING SUPPORT - This advanced feature allows you to select what traffic
                goes through the VPN tunnel.</li>
            <li>BYPASS BLOCKING - Smart protocol selection automatically overcomes VPN bans and
                unblocks censored content.</li>
            <li>TRUSTED - Our code has undergone a security audit and is open source.</li>
            <li>MULTIPLE PLATFORM SUPPORT - Easy to use on Android, iOS, Windows, macOS, Linux, and
                more.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Note: Free users can only connect one device to Free servers in Japan, the Netherlands,
            and the US.</p>
    </description>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>
                https://images.prismic.io/gatsby-landing-pages/e6a71a70-741e-44ed-a947-439c0ea92801_secure-core.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <url type="homepage">https://protonvpn.com/</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/ProtonVPN/linux-app/issues</url>
    <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/ProtonVPN/linux-app</url>

    <releases>
        <release version="1.12.0" date="2022-10-02" />
    </releases>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
</component>