<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2023 Spaceslug -->
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.slugchess.SlugChess</id>

    <name>SlugChess</name>
    <summary>Chess with Fog-of-War and shuffled officers</summary>

    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>

    <supports>
        <control>pointing</control>
        <control>keyboard</control>
        <control>touch</control>
    </supports>
    <keywords>
      <keyword>game</keyword>
    </keywords>

    <description>
        <p>
            SlugChess online digital chess variant with fog-of-war and double shuffled officers. 
            It is both a rule set and an application for <em>Linux</em> and <em>Windows</em>. 
        </p>
        <p>
            In SlugChess you can only see a limited part of the game board based on the type and position of your pieces. 
            You can only move your pieces to squares you can see. Both white and blacks officers are shuffled separately and completely random. 
            Therefor you can't know where your opponents king is at the beginning of the game. 
            You win SlugChess by capturing the opponents king. There are two sub-variants of SlugChess with different vision rules. 
            They are <em>SlugChess Torch</em> and <em>SlugChess Sight</em>.
        </p>
        <p>
            In <em>SlugChess Torch</em> the vision is a range around your pieces, as if they are holding a touch. The range of pawns are 1 and officers 2. 
            This sub-variant results in methodical games where you have to fight for vision and build up and advantage.
        </p>
        <p>
            In <em>SlugChess Sight</em> the vision is the squares your pieces can move to. 
            Therefor your pieces can move as in normal chess but you can see a lot less. In addition knights and pawns have vision range of 1. 
            This sub-variant results in dynamic and aggressive games that can swing back and fourth and can end quickly.
        </p>
    </description>
    
    <url type="homepage">https://slugchess.com/</url>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.slugchess.SlugChess.desktop</launchable>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>SlugChess chessboard replay from white's perspective'</caption>
            <image type="source" width="1008" height="596">https://slugchess.com/assets/screenshot-chessboard-replay-1.png</image>
            <!--<image type="thumbnail" width="752" height="423">https://www.example.org/en_US/main-large.png</image>-->
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot >
            <caption>SlugChess start menu</caption>
            <image type="source" width="1009" height="597">https://slugchess.com/assets/screenshot-start-menu.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <!--<screenshot>
            <video container="matroska" codec="av1" width="800" height="600">https://www.example.org/en_US/screencast.mkv</video>
        </screenshot> -->
    </screenshots>

    <releases>
        <release version="1.0.0" date="2023-04-14">
            <description>
                Initial release
            </description>
        </release>   
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.0"></content_rating>
</component>
