<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.pixelomer.ShijimaQt</id>
    <name>Shijima-Qt</name>
    <developer id="com.pixelomer">
        <name>pixelomer</name>
    </developer>
    <summary>A cross-platform desktop application for running shimeji desktop pets</summary>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
    <url type="homepage">https://getshijima.app/</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/pixelomer/Shijima-Qt-releases/issues</url>
    <url type="donation">https://buymeacoffee.com/pixelomer</url>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
    <recommends>
        <control>keyboard</control>
        <control>pointing</control>
        <control>touch</control>
    </recommends>
    <categories>
        <category>Game</category>
    </categories>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.pixelomer.ShijimaQt.desktop</launchable>

    <description>
        <p>Shijima-Qt is a cross-platform desktop application for running shimeji desktop pets on Windows, macOS and Linux. It is still in its very early stages so bugs are to be expected, but feel free to give this alpha build a try!</p>
        <p>Features:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Easy Installation. Ready to use out of the box. No shortcut tricks or additional dependencies needed.</li>
            <li>Low Memory Footprint. Shijima will not use large amounts of RAM, even with dozens of mascots on-screen.</li>
            <li>Cross-platform. Works on iOS, iPadOS, Android, Windows, macOS, Linux and Nintendo Wii.</li>
            <li>Everything In One Place. Import and use all of your shimeji with one app. No separate copies needed.</li>
            <li>No Restarts. Install or uninstall shimeji and change settings without restarting Shijima.</li>
            <li>Hassle-Free Importing. Just select a zip/rar/7z archive. Shijima will find and copy shimeji files for you.</li>
        </ul>
    </description>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://github.com/pixelomer/Shijima-Qt/blob/main/.images/Shijima-Qt-Fedora.jpg?raw=true</image>
            <caption>Shimejis standing and sitting on a window</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://getshijima.app/shijima-qt.png</image>
            <caption>Shijima-Qt main window</caption>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <releases>
        <release version="v0.0.4" date="2025-03-12">
            <description>
                <p>This build mainly includes changes that could benefit streamers and anyone else interested in using Shijima-Qt as an overlay with programs like OBS.</p>
                <p>Changes:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Windowed mode for running mascots within a single window. The background color for this window is adjustable and this mode can be enabled/disabled at any time.</li>
                    <li>More ways to use the API and CLI.</li>
                    <li>libshijima changes</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="v0.0.3" date="2025-02-21">
            <description>
                <p>Changes:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Experimental multi-monitor support. It may not work as expected in all configurations so if you encounter any problems when using multiple monitors, please create an issue about it.</li>
                    <li>Shimeji should no longer fall when the active window is resized.</li>
                    <li>The Inspect dialog now shows more details about the selected shimeji and the environment.</li>
                    <li>Shijima-Qt now provides a basic CLI and HTTP API for interacting with shimeji. For the CLI usage, see ./shijima-qt --help (or platform equivalent). For the HTTP API details, see HTTP-API.md.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="v0.0.2" date="2025-02-15">
            <description>
                <p>Changes:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Shijima-Qt now ships with a default mascot, which is the same default mascot used in Shimeji by Group Finity and Shimeji-ee by Kilkakon. This mascot cannot be uninstalled or replaced.</li>
                    <li>Added a settings menu item where multiplication can be enabled/disabled and the size of shimeji can be adjusted.</li>
                    <li>Window tracking is now available on Windows.</li>
                    <li>Added window tracking support for GNOME 47.</li>
                    <li>Added metadata for Windows executable.</li>
                    <li>Shijima-Qt manager window and shimeji will now show up on all desktops by default on all platforms.</li>
                    <li>Fixed an issue where image files with uppercase letters would not be loaded properly.</li>
                    <li>When evaluating conditions, invalid JavaScript will now evaluate to false instead of crashing the program.</li>
                    <li>When all shimeji are dismissed, the manager window will now reappear automatically.</li>
                    <li>When a startup error occurs, a message box with the error details will be shown instead of crashing the program.</li>
                    <li>Removed margins in the license window.</li>
                    <li>Renamed the "Show settings" button to "Show manager" to make it less ambiguous.</li>
                    <li>Removed hardcoded /tmp paths on Linux and added Flatpak support. When started with the SHIJIMA_FLATPAK=1 environment variable, Shijima-Qt will use flatpak-spawn instead of running executables directly and appropriately translate temporary file paths while installing helper plugins.</li>
                    <li>Added an "Inspect" option for shimeji. When selected, a new window will pop up with information about the shimeji's name, position, current behavior and frame.</li>
                    <li>On Linux, Shijima-Qt will no longer crash if an appropriate window tracker backend is not available for the active window manager. Instead, the app will launch without window tracking. SHIJIMA_NO_WINDOW_TRACKING=1 environment variable may also be specified to manually disable window tracking.</li>
                    <li>Added unarr as a fallback library for extracting and importing shimeji. Shimeji in solid RAR archives can now be imported.</li>
                    <li>When deleting many shimeji at once, the confirmation dialog will now be truncated to show only the names for 5 of the shimeji being deleted.</li>
                    <li>Fixed an issue on GNOME where shimeji would not grab onto windows properly when using a desktop environment scale other than 100%.</li>
                    <li>Renamed DBus service name from com.pixelomer.ShijimaQT to com.pixelomer.ShijimaQt</li>
                    <li>Removed logging from GNOME plugin.</li>
                    <li>Fixed an issue where Shijima-Qt would fail to start again after crashing when running under KDE.</li>
                    <li>Fixed an issue where shimeji would not spawn immediately on macOS and attempting to close the manager window would result in weird behavior.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Known issues:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Using Shijima-Qt with multiple monitors is not supported.</li>
                    <li>On Windows, when the active window is closed, this may not be immediately detected by Shijima-Qt. As a result, shimeji may continue moving around on the now-gone window until a different window is activated.</li>
                    <li>Inspect and scale windows should not be resizable, but they are.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
        <release version="v0.0.1" date="2025-02-06">
            <description>
                <p>Known Issues:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>It is not immediately obvious how to spawn shimeji. You can spawn a shimeji by double clicking it or by selecting it and pressing enter.</li>
                    <li>Windows build does not support window tracking. Shimeji will not be able to stand on or grab onto windows on Windows.</li>
                    <li>Using Shijima-Qt with multiple monitors isn't supported.</li>
                    <li>Linux support is limited to KDE and GNOME. Both Wayland and X11 are supported. On Wayland, Shijima-Qt will run through XWayland.</li>
                    <li>While GNOME support is also available, the Linux build was mostly tested with KDE.</li>
                    <li>macOS build only contains Apple Silicon binaries. Intel Macs aren't supported.</li>
                    <li>Shimeji may move slower than expected on macOS.</li>
                    <li>Spawning a high number of shimeji with KDE may cause the desktop environment to completely freeze.</li>
                    <li>Shijima does not support actions related to moving windows. FallWithIE, WalkWithIE and ThrowIE are treated the same as Fall, Walk and Animate respectively.</li>
                    <li>On macOS, shimeji may not immediately appear. If this happens, open the licenses window by selecting Help > View Licenses and spawned shimeji should appear. You can later close this window.</li>
                    <li>macOS may prevent you from launching the app saying that it is "damaged". You can get around this by running xattr -rd com.apple.quarantine /path/to/Shijima-Qt.app in the Terminal.</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
</component>
