<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.github.imamhs.Shopne</id>

  <name>Shopne Arcade</name>
  <summary>A frontend for GnGeo emulator written purely in Python</summary>

  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>

  <supports>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
    <control>gamepad</control>
  </supports>

  <description>
    <p>
      Shopne Arcade is a front-end application designed to easily play Neo Geo system games on PC. It&apos;s interface is compatible for screens with low resolution such as 640x480 pixels. It lets users play Neo Geo system games from one interface where users will be able pick different game play experience settings such as Neo Geo games video resolutions, audio sampling rates, etc. Shopne Arcade is written in pure Python language without any external dependencies making it portable across various Linux Distributions.
    </p>
    <p>
      Neo Geo system emulation and front-end features:
    </p>
    <p>
      - Playing games in fullscreen mode - Automatically adjusting video frame rates - Interpolation between frames - Using GPU memory for performance - Synchronising video with monitor refresh rate - Video scaling - Video effects - Selecting of rendering engine (Choose YUV for native like graphics and arbitrary window scaling using window handles) - Emulating audio in different sampling rates - Full controller configuration for keyboard and gamepads - Support for different Neo Geo region BIOS - Save and Load games states (state files are saved in the directory .gngeo inside users home folder) - Showing games cover arts (double click into the game list) (cover art png files need to be placed inside the data/covers/ of Shopne Arcade program folder) - Adding multiple game roms files locations - Saving all settings
    </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.imamhs.Shopne.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://github.com/imamhs/Shopne-Arcade/blob/master/screenshot/shopne_19.png?raw=true</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/imamhs/Shopne-Arcade/raw/master/screenshot/gr.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/imamhs/Shopne-Arcade/raw/master/screenshot/con.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
