<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.bitwarden.desktop</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.bitwarden.desktop.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Bitwarden</name>
  <summary>A secure and free password manager for all of your devices.</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Bitwarden is the easiest and safest way to store all of your logins and
      passwords while conveniently keeping them synced between all of your
      devices.
    </p>
    <p>
      Password theft is a serious problem. The websites and apps that you use
      are under attack every day. Security breaches occur and your passwords
      are stolen. When you reuse the same passwords across apps and websites
      hackers can easily access your email, bank, and other important
      accounts.
    </p>
    <p>
      Security experts recommend that you use a different, randomly generated
      password for every account that you create. But how do you manage all
      those passwords? Bitwarden makes it easy for you to create, store, and
      access your passwords.
    </p>
    <p>
      Bitwarden stores all of your logins in an encrypted vault that syncs
      across all of your devices. Since it's fully encrypted before it ever
      leaves your device, only you have access to your data. Not even the
      team at Bitwarden can read your data, even if we wanted to. Your data
      is sealed with AES-256 bit encryption, salted hashing, and PBKDF2
      SHA-256.
    </p>
    <p>
      Bitwarden is 100% open source software. The source code for Bitwarden
      is hosted on GitHub and everyone is free to review, audit, and
      contribute to the Bitwarden codebase.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://camo.githubusercontent.com/efc3b807d82fd8eaf35375f5f2600414c17813c6/687474703a2f2f696d6775722e636f6d2f6f504d343479302e706e67</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.bitwarden.com/</url>
  <developer_name>8bit Solutions LLC</developer_name>
  <update_contact>hello@bitwarden.com</update_contact>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.7.0" date="2018-08-24"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
</component>