<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>com.pinegrow.Pinegrow</id>
	<metadata_license>CC-BY-SA</metadata_license>
	<name>Pinegrow</name>
	<summary>Visual web editor for professionals</summary>
	<url type="homepage">https://pinegrow.com/</url>
  <description>
  <p>
  Pinegrow lets you work faster with HTML, CSS / SASS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, GreenSock Interactions, WordPress and WooCommerce.
  </p>
  <p>
  Pinegrow works with standard web files and easily integrates into your existing workflow.
  </p>
  <p>
  Quickly build the layout of your webpage with powerful visual tools for adding, editing, moving, cloning and deleting HTML elements. Insert multiple elements with repeater and modify the layout of all selected elements with one move.
  </p>
  <p>
  Inspect active CSS rules, use rich visual controls, CSS Grid editor, Dev tools-like editor or code - all working together as one. Edit SASS and LESS, live, without any external tools.
  </p>
  <p>
  Turn hundreds of framework classes into powerful visual controls. Use the complete library of ready-to-use components and work with dynamic components like modals. Resize columns on the page and visualize the layout with display helpers.
  </p>
  <p>
  An add-on for Pinegrow Web Editor that lets you visually work with Tailwind CSS projects including those that use a custom theme.
  </p>
  <p>
  Use multi-page editing to edit your pages at multiple device sizes. Easily design responsive websites with Media query helper tool. Add custom breakpoints or let Pinegrow detect them by analyzing stylesheets.
  </p>
  <p>
  Pinegrow Pro lets you speed up your work even more with smart features such as master pages that let you define templates for your project. Turn page elements into reusable components with custom editable areas. Use Pinegrow as CMS for static HTML websites.
  </p>
  <p>
  Pinegrow lets you create powerful interactions and scroll scenes with custom animations designed with the timeline editor. Animations are powered by GreenSock GSAP, a proven high-performance animation library.
  </p>
  <p>
  Pinegrow is also the perfect tool for creating production-ready WordPress themes and plugins. Take any HTML page and turn it into a WordPress theme or Gutenberg blocks by assigning WordPress actions to individual elements on the page. Pinegrow exports the standard PHP WordPress files.
  </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://github.com/Malom-ctrl/com.pinegrow.Pinegrow/blob/5f36c90bcb53465735ff5d8458acedc61f41769e/screenshots/1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/Malom-ctrl/com.pinegrow.Pinegrow/blob/5f36c90bcb53465735ff5d8458acedc61f41769e/screenshots/2.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/Malom-ctrl/com.pinegrow.Pinegrow/blob/5f36c90bcb53465735ff5d8458acedc61f41769e/screenshots/3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.4" date="2023-04-26"></release>
  </releases>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">com.pinegrow.Pinegrow.desktop</launchable>
	<project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
	<developer_name>Pinegrow Pte. Ltd.</developer_name>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
