<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.tominlab.wonderpen</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.tominlab.wonderpen.desktop</launchable>
  <name>WonderPen</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-cn">妙笔</name>
  <developer_name>TominLab</developer_name>
  <summary>Writing novels, essays, etc.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-cn">强大易用的写作软件</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.tominlab.com/en/terms/service</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.tominlab.com/en/wonderpen</url>
  <url type="contact">https://www.tominlab.com/en/contact</url>
  <url type="faq">https://help.tominlab.com/en/wonderpen/guides</url>
  <description>
    <p>WonderPen is a powerful and easy-to-use writing app, whether you are a writer, a student or a writing enthusiast, you can use it to complete your writing.</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Tree-like multi-level directory, you can drag and drop to sort or change the nesting relationship at will, so that the directory structure of the long book is clear at a glance.</li>
      <li>An easy-to-use text editor that supports Markdown syntax.</li>
      <li>It can be switched to a full-screen composition mode to eliminate distractions and concentrate on writing.</li>
      <li>Easily export to image, PDF, Epub, Word, HTML and other formats.</li>
      <li>Supports whiteboard mode, where you can add notes, images, checklist, tables, kanban and other content arbitrarily.</li>
      <li>Individual memos can be added to each document.</li>
      <li>At the same time, it supports global note cards, which is convenient for reference when writing across documents.</li>
      <li>When there are too many documents, it can focus on a node in the document tree and hide others.</li>
      <li>Support full-text search and replace.</li>
      <li>Support chapter splitting and merging.</li>
      <li>Documents are automatically saved after modification.</li>
      <li>Support document snapshot and full library backup, support automatic backup, to ensure data security without losing manuscripts.</li>
      <li>Supports dark mode, and has built-in multiple themes such as green, yellow, and gray.</li>
      <li>Provides a large number of personalized settings, and can also add custom CSS to meet various usage habits.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Hope you enjoy this app as much as we do. If you have any questions or suggestions during use, you can contact us through the "Feedback" option in the "Help" menu, or send us an email: support@tominlab.com .</p>
  </description>
  
  <description xml:lang="zh-cn">
    <p>妙笔是一个强大且易用的写作工具，无论您是作家、学生还是写作爱好者，都可以使用它完成您的作品。</p>
    <p>功能特性：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>树状多级目录，可随意拖拽排序或改变嵌套关系，让长篇巨著的目录结构一目了然。</li>
      <li>简单易用的文本编辑器，支持 Markdown 语法。</li>
      <li>可切换为全屏专注模式，排除干扰，专心写作。</li>
      <li>便捷地导出为图片、PDF、Epub、Word、HTML 等多种格式。</li>
      <li>支持白板模式，可在其中任意添加便笺、表格、看板等内容。</li>
      <li>每个文档都可以添加单独的备注。</li>
      <li>同时支持全局备注卡片，方便跨文档写作时参考。</li>
      <li>当文档太多时，可聚焦于文档树中的一个节点，隐匿其余细节。</li>
      <li>支持全文搜索及替换。</li>
      <li>支持章节切分以及合并。</li>
      <li>文档修改后自动保存。</li>
      <li>支持文档快照以及全库备份，支持自动备份，确保数据安全不丢稿。</li>
      <li>支持夜间模式，还内置了浅绿、淡黄、深灰等多个主题。</li>
      <li>提供大量个性化设置，还可自定义 CSS，满足多种使用习惯。</li>
    </ul>
    <p>希望您像我们一样，喜爱这个应用。使用过程中有任何问题或建议，都可以通过「帮助」菜单中的「意见反馈」选项联系我们，或者也可以给我们发送邮件：support@tominlab.com。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Writing</caption>
      <image type="source">https://cdn.tominlab.com/upload/2023/11/19/wonderpen.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.4.3" date="2024-01-25"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <update_contact>support@tominlab.com</update_contact>
</component>
