<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<component type="desktop">
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>

    <id>com.faforever.Client</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.faforever.Client.desktop</launchable>

    <name>Forged Allience Forever</name>
    <developer_name>FAForever</developer_name>

    <url type="homepage">https://www.faforever.com/</url>
    <url type="help">https://forum.faforever.com/</url>
    <url type="donation">https://www.patreon.com/faf</url>

    <summary>The Community Driven Lobby for Supreme Commander: Forged Alliance</summary>

    <description>
        <p>
          Forged Alliance Forever is a community-driven project designed to facilitate online play for Supreme Commander: Forged Alliance. Complete with chat, matchmaking, replay vaults, tournaments and ever evolving balance.
        </p>
        <p>
          If you want to experience Forged Alliance in its true glory together with thousands of other players of all skill levels, FAF is the place to be.
        </p>
        <p>
          Host and join teamgames with up to 16 players simultaneously or measure your skill against others in one versus one combat against players from all over the world. Enjoy the original Supreme Commander and Supreme Commander: Forged Alliance campaigns with up to 3 friends in addition to completely new custom made co-op campaign maps! Experience countless variations on gameplay and thousands of player made maps to keep things fresh forever. Meet casual to competitive gamers. Forged Alliance Forever is one of the best online gaming communities out there complete with forums, clans, wiki, and a supremely moderated global chat to enjoy between games.
        </p>
        <p>
          In order to play Forged Alliance Forever, you must first install Supreme Commander: Forged Alliance through Steam.
        </p>
    </description>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://www.faforever.com/images/index-background.jpg</image>
            <caption>Main</caption>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <releases>
        <release version="v2021.10.0" date="2021-10-20"/>
    </releases>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
      <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">moderate</content_attribute>
      <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
      <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>

</component>
