<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.sigil_ebook.Sigil</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
    <name>Sigil</name>
    <summary>Multi-platform EPUB ebook editor</summary>

    <description>
        <p>Sigil was designed to make it easy to create great ebooks using the EPUB format. If you are formatting books for your own use, or you are a professional editor publishing books on multiple platforms, then Sigil is for you. You can use Sigil to format and package your books into an EPUB that looks exactly the way you want it to using an advanced set of features that have made Sigil one of most popular EPUB editors available.</p>

        <p>This open-source and completely free software is written and supported entirely by volunteers. The current Sigil development team includes Doug Massay and Kevin Hendricks as co-lead developers and maintainers. Previous developers/authors include John Schember, Grant Drake and Dave Heiland. Sigil was originally created by Strahinja Markovic in 2009 and remains completely free to download and use. Support is also provided by other volunteers who contribute code, translations and helpful answers to user’s questions. See the Help=&gt;About menu in Sigil for a complete list of contributors.</p>

        <p>Some Sigil features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Free and open source software under GPLv3</li>
          <li>Multi-platform: runs on Windows, Mac, and Linux</li>
          <li>Full UTF-16 support</li>
          <li>EPUB 2 and EPUB 3 spec support</li>
          <li>Multiple Views: Code View and Preview View</li>
          <li>Complete control over directly editing EPUB syntax in Code View</li>
          <li>Table of Contents generator with multi-level heading support</li>
          <li>Metadata editor</li>
          <li>User interface translated into many languages</li>
          <li>Themeable icons</li>
          <li>Spell checking with default and user configurable dictionaries</li>
          <li>Full Regular Expression (PCRE) support for Find &amp; Replace</li>
          <li>Supports import of EPUB and HTML files, images, and style sheets</li>
          <li>All imported files can have their formatting mended, and your code can be optionally “prettified”</li>
          <li>Plugin Support</li>
          <li>Checkpoint support (compare “snapshots” of changes)</li>
          <li>Pies and Puppies!</li>
        </ul>
    </description>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.sigil_ebook.Sigil.desktop</launchable>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>The main window</caption>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Sigil-Ebook/sigil-user-guide/master/src/OEBPS/Images/ui_buttons-moved.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Sigil-Ebook/sigil-user-guide/master/src/OEBPS/Images/toc-generate-toc.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <url type="homepage">https://sigil-ebook.com</url>
    <url type="help">https://github.com/Sigil-Ebook/Sigil/wiki</url>

    <releases>
        <release version="1.8.0" date="2022-02-02"/>
        <release version="0.9.18" date="2019-09-04"/>
    </releases>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
</component>
