<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.blockstream.Green</id>
  
  <name>Blockstream Green</name>
  <summary>Blockstream Green is a simple and secure Bitcoin wallet that makes it easy to get started sending and receiving Bitcoin and Liquid-based assets such as L-BTC and Tether’s USDt.</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-only</project_license>
  
  <supports>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </supports>
  
  <description>
    <p>
      Built by one of the most respected teams in the Bitcoin industry, Blockstream Green is supported across multiple platforms and is designed for Bitcoin beginners and power users alike.
    </p>
    <p>
      EASY SETUP
    </p>
    <p>
      No registration or personal details are required to get started, just write down your mnemonic and start making Bitcoin transactions right away.
    </p>
    <p>
      FASTER &amp; CHEAPER BITCOIN TRANSACTIONS
    </p>
    <p>
      Smart fee estimation ensures your Bitcoin payments arrive on time without being charged excessive fees.
    </p>
    <p>
      MULTILINGUAL
    </p>
    <p>
      We speak your language. Green includes support for Brazilian Portuguese, Chinese (Simplified), Dutch, English, French, German, Hebrew, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Russian, Spanish, Ukrainian, Vietnamese. And more to come!
    </p>
    <p>
      LIQUID SIDECHAIN SUPPORT
    </p>
    <p>
      Send and receive Liquid Bitcoin (L-BTC), Tether’s USDt, and any other Liquid-based assets with the Liquid wallet.
    </p>
    <p>
      TWO-FACTOR MULTISIG SECURITY
    </p>
    <p>
      Unique dual-key security with one key protected by two-factor authentication. Multiple authentication options are available including, Google Authenticator, SMS, and email.
    </p>
    <p>
      Bitcoin power users will feel right at home with a wide range of advanced features and industry-firsts:
    </p>
    <p>
      FEE CONTROL
    </p>
    <p>
      Fully customizable transaction fees with replace-by-fee support so that you can start low and adjust the fee if necessary. Great for pushing through urgent transactions without overpaying.
    </p>
    <p>
      HARDWARE WALLET SUPPORT
    </p>
    <p>
      Integration with Ledger Nano X via Bluetooth (see the official docs for latest compatibility across the various supported platform).
    </p>
    <p>
      TWO-FACTOR THRESHOLDS
    </p>
    <p>
      Require two-factor authentication for large payments only by setting a two-factor threshold. Total payments up to the threshold can be completed without 2FA.
    </p>
    <p>
      WATCH-ONLY WALLETS
    </p>
    <p>
      Keep an eye on your Bitcoin balances while on the go and receive payments from others without needing to grant payment permissions to your device.
    </p>
    <p>
      TESTNET SUPPORT
    </p>
    <p>
      Easily make test transactions on Bitcoin testnet.
    </p>
    <p>
      PRIVACY
    </p>
    <p>
      No documents, personal information, or KYC required. An email address is needed for wallet recovery purposes only. Connect via Tor at the tap of a button.
    </p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.blockstream.Green.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://blockstream.com/green</url>
  <releases>
	  <release version="1.2.0" date="2023-05-18">
		  <description>
			  <p>Avoid Jade firmware update when Jade is being setup. Fix Jade device state typo</p>
		  </description>
	  </release>
  </releases>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://blockstream.com/img/img/laptop_green_ui_lander.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
