<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.nordpass.NordPass</id>
    <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
    <name>NordPass Password Manager</name>
    <summary>An easy to use password manager brought to you by cybersecurity experts.</summary>
    <description>
        <p>NordPass - an easy to use password manager brought to you by cybersecurity experts. Keep passwords in a secure vault, access when and where you need them.</p>
        <p>NordPass is designed by the same team that created a leading VPN service, now trusted by more than 12 million users - NordVPN. Therefore, security and simplicity are the top NordPass priorities.</p>
        <p>With NordPass, store your passwords and secure notes all in one place, access them on any device, and share them with people you trust. Your passwords are protected by the latest encryption algorithm, XChaCha20, and zero-knowledge architecture. Your passwords are yours to have - we know nothing.</p>
        <p>What does NordPass do?</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Autosave. Forget saving your passwords manually. With NordPass, you can add them to your vault in a few simple clicks.</li>
            <li>Autofill. Scrolling through a database of logins and passwords isn’t for you? That’s what autofill is for. Let NordPass do the work.</li>
            <li>Password generator. Unique passwords are essential for truly secure accounts. With NordPass, you can generate them in a matter of seconds.</li>
            <li>Password strength checker. Using a password manager enhances your security, but it won’t help you if your passwords are easy to crack. Check how strong your passwords are before you use them on any accounts.</li>
            <li>Secure password sharing. We get it: sometimes, you need to share your passwords. If you do, you might as well share them safely with a secure password sharing feature.</li>
            <li>Secure all that matters. NordPass isn’t just for passwords. Store and access all your secure notes, including your credit card details.</li>
            <li>Accessibility. Passwords should be accessed when and where you need them. That’s why NordPass is available as a browser extension, as well as mobile and desktop apps.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>How much does NordPass cost?</p>
        <p>NordPass is free to use, whether it is a browser extension or an app. Want to access more features like secure password sharing or access your passwords on more than one device at once? Try NordPass Premium.</p>
        <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by NordPass</p>
    </description>
    <url type="help">https://support.nordpass.com/hc/en-us/</url>
    <url type="homepage">https://nordpass.com/</url>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.nordpass.NordPass.desktop</launchable>
    <developer_name>NordPass</developer_name>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image type="source">https://media.wired.com/photos/5e3335ca348ef000086b5d62/master/w_1600%2Cc_limit/Gear-NordPass-Mac-SOURCE-Nordpass.jpg</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <update_contact>sakcheen+flathub_AT_gmail.com</update_contact>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
    <releases>
        <release version="1.10.1" date="2020-03-16"/>
    </releases>
</component>