<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.microsoft.Teams</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
    <name>Microsoft Teams</name>
    <summary>Microsoft Teams for Linux is your chat-centered workspace in Office 365.</summary>

    <description>
        <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or
            supported by Microsoft Corporation.</p>

        <p>
            Microsoft Teams is your hub for teamwork in Office 365.
            All your team conversations, files, meetings, and apps live together
            in a single shared workspace, and you can take it with you on your
            favorite mobile device. Whether you’re sprinting towards a deadline
            or sharing your next big idea, Teams can help you achieve more.
        </p>
        
        <p>YOUR HUB FOR TEAMWORK</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Easily manage your team’s projects with file editing and sharing on the go</li>
            <li>Connect face-to-face with HD audio and video, and join meetings from almost anywhere</li>
            <li>Chat privately or in groups, and communicate with the entire team in dedicated channels</li>
            <li>Mention individual team members, or the whole team at once, to get your colleagues’ attention</li>
            <li>Focus on what matters most by saving important conversations and customizing your notifications</li>
            <li>Search your chats and team conversations to quickly find what you need</li>
            <li>Get the enterprise-level security and compliance you expect from Office 365</li>
        </ul>

        <p>
            This app requires a paid Office 365 commercial subscription,
            or a free or trial subscription of Microsoft Teams.
            If you’re not sure about your company’s subscription or the services
            you have access to, visit Office.com/Teams to learn more or contact your IT department.
        </p>

        <p>
            By downloading this app, you agree to the license and privacy terms (see aka.ms/privacy).
            To learn more, please visit aka.ms/microsoftteams.
        </p>
    </description>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.microsoft.Teams.desktop</launchable>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Microsoft Teams</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/Microsoft-Teams-1000x563.jpg</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Move conversations from email into Microsoft Teams with rich formatting, including attachments</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/58c77173c6d8a-58c77173c821dMove-conversations-from-email-into-Microsoft-Teams-with-rich-formatting-including-attachments..png-1000x666.png</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Ad hoc and scheduled voice and video meetings right from within Microsoft Teams</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/Ad-hoc-and-scheduled-voice-and-video-meetings-right-from-within-Microsoft-Teams-1000x563.jpg</image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>New bots help you complete tasks within your conversations</caption>
            <image>https://3er1viui9wo30pkxh1v2nh4w-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/225/2017/03/New-bots-help-you-complete-tasks-within-your-conversations.-1000x666.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <developer_name>Microsoft Corporation</developer_name>
    <url type="homepage">https://teams.microsoft.com/downloads</url>

    <releases>
        <release date="2019-12-04" version="1.2.0"/>
    </releases>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-info">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
</component>
