<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2025 Toledo1 -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.toledo1.Toledo1</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://toledo1.com/license/</project_license>
  <name>Toledo1</name>
  <summary>Advanced LLM browser with client-side search, pay-per-query model, and file processing</summary>
  <developer id="com.toledo1">
    <name>Toledo1</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Toledo1 is a revolutionary LLM browser that transforms how you interact with AI models and search the web.</p>
    <p>Unlike traditional browsers, Toledo1 treats URLs as direct connections to LLM inference engines, creating a direct chat line to any LLM available on the public internet, private cloud, or local desktop.</p>
    
    <p>Key features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li><em>Client-Side Search</em>: Powerful native desktop application that integrates seamlessly with your workflow. Search and process information directly from your PC.</li>
      <li><em>No Subscriptions</em>: Transparent pay-per-query pricing with enterprise-grade security. Only pay for what you use with our confidential API system.</li>
      <li><em>AI Agent</em>: Agentic search with MCP tools when Agent mode is selected (feature under development).</li>
      <li><em>Dynamic Code Copilot</em>: Leverage specialized code LLMs with customizable presets for diverse programming solutions.</li>
      <li><em>Real-Time Data Access</em>: Get live market data, weather information, and current events. Stay updated with accurate, real-time information.</li>
      <li><em>History Management</em>: Seamlessly transfer chat history between LLM systems while preserving context, including files and images.</li>
      <li><em>Multi-Purpose Assistant</em>: Customize Toledo1's behavior and expertise through flexible system settings for your specific needs.</li>
      <li><em>File &amp; Image Processing</em>: Process multiple file formats including text, PDF, and images. Extract and analyze information from your documents.</li>
      <li><em>Local Inference</em>: Maintain complete privacy with on-device processing when needed.</li>
    </ul>
    
    <p>Toledo1 represents a paradigm shift in web search, functioning as a manual compound AI system - a truth machine that chains multiple models on context using customizable presets.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.toledo1.Toledo1.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://toledo1.com/toledo1-linux-demo5.png</image>
      <caption>Transcribe images</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://toledo1.com/toledo1-linux-demo6.png</image>
      <caption>Search and resume previous conversations</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://toledo1.com/toledo1-linux-demo7.png</image>
      <caption>Chat with reasoning models across providers on the same chat thread</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://toledo1.com/toledo1-linux-demo8.png</image>
      <caption>Run local inference with the best models</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://toledo1.com/</url>
  <url type="contact">https://toledo1.com/contact/</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="1.9.8" date="2024-03-07">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release featuring:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Client-side search functionality</li>
          <li>Pay-per-query confidential API system</li>
          <li>Dynamic code assistance with specialized LLMs</li>
          <li>Real-time data access capabilities</li>
          <li>Cross-model history management</li>
          <li>Multi-format file and image processing</li>
          <li>Local inference support</li>
          <li>Customizable system settings</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
    <category>WebBrowser</category>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>Development</category>
    <category>Office</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>LLM</keyword>
    <keyword>AI</keyword>
    <keyword>Client-Side Search</keyword>
    <keyword>Pay-Per-Query</keyword>
    <keyword>Code Copilot</keyword>
    <keyword>File Processing</keyword>
    <keyword>Local Inference</keyword>
    <keyword>AI Agent</keyword>
    <keyword>Real-Time Data</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">768</display_length>
  </requires>
</component>
