<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.reqable.Reqable</id>
  <name>Reqable</name>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://reqable.com/en-US/policy/#license</project_license>
  <developer id="com.reqable">
  <name>Reqable</name>
  </developer>
  <summary>Advanced API Debugging Proxy and REST Client</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.reqable.Reqable.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://reqable.com/en-US/linux</url>
  <url type="help">https://reqable.com/en-US/docs</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/reqable/reqable-app/issues</url>
  <description>
    <p>Reqable = Fiddler + Charles + Postman, with Minimalist Design, Powerful Features, Efficient Performance and Desktop + Mobile Platforms.</p>
    <p>Reqable is a modern cross-platform project, designed for API development, testing, and debugging. Reqable fully supports HTTP1 and HTTP2 and partially supports HTTP3(QUIC).</p>
    <p>Features</p>
    <p>1. API debugging</p>
    <p>Reqable uses the classic MITM proxy method for debugging and supports such as rewriting, scripting (Python), breakpoints, and replay.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Support HTTP/1.x and HTTP2 protocol, HTTP3 (QUIC) is not supported yet.</li>
      <li>Support HTTP/HTTPS/Socks4/Socks4a/Socks5 proxy mode.</li>
      <li>Support HTTPS, TLSv1.1, TLSv1.2 and TLSv1.3 protocols.</li>
      <li>Support WebSocket upgraded based on HTTP1.</li>
      <li>Support HTTP/HTTPS secondary proxy.</li>
      <li>Composing API: Create REST API from captured traffic list.</li>
      <li>Search and filter: Multi-condition search, application, domain name, protocol, data type and other filters.</li>
      <li>Rewriting: Perform redirection, map local, map remote, modification for requests or responses.</li>
      <li>Breakpoint: Perform real-time breakpoint operations on requests or responses.</li>
      <li>Scripting: Support for writing Python scripts to process requests or responses.</li>
      <li>Gateway: Perform operations such as shielding and suspending for requests or responses.</li>
      <li>Mirroring: Configure mirror mapping for the specified domain name and port.</li>
      <li>Reverse proxy: Use local reverse proxy server to debug HTTPS traffics without trusting CA certificate.</li>
      <li>Highlighting: Set custom rules to highlight requests in multiple colors.</li>
      <li>Replay: Support single or multiple requests for playback testing.</li>
      <li>Diff tool: Compare request and response messages, quickly locate data deviations.</li>
      <li>History: Automatically save the recording list for easy retrospective viewing.</li>
      <li>Traffic source: Detect which application the traffic is coming from.</li>
      <li>HAR: Automatically associate HAR files, and support HAR export and open.</li>
      <li>SSL Certificates: Import custom SSL certificates, analyze pinned certificates and two-way authentication requests.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>2. API Testing</p>
    <p>Reqable can compose API for testing and also supports features such as API collection and history.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Supports HTTP/1.1, HTTP2 and HTTP3 (QUIC) protocols.</li>
      <li>API collection: Save API to collections and manage your APIs.</li>
      <li>Collection suppoert: Import collections from Postman and Hoppscotch.</li>
      <li>Environment: Global environment and user environments.</li>
      <li>Batch editing: Support batch editing of query parameters, request headers, forms, etc.</li>
      <li>Scripting: Write python script to process pre-request and post-request data.</li>
      <li>Code Snippet: Generate code for mainstream languages ​​or network libraries such as Python, Java, and NodeJS.</li>
      <li>Authorization settings: Support authorization methods such as API KEY, Basic Auth, and Bearer Token.</li>
      <li>Proxy settings: Support custom proxy, system proxy and debugging proxy, etc.</li>
      <li>Performance: You can view the time-consuming data of requests at different stages.</li>
      <li>Cookie management: Automatically save cookies or add cookies.</li>
      <li>History: Automatically save the request and response for easy retrospective viewing.</li>
      <li>cURL support: Create API from cURL or export API to cURL.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>3. Toolbox</p>
    <p>Reqable provides some commonly used tools.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Base64 Codec.</li>
      <li>URL Codec.</li>
      <li>Md5 Calculator.</li>
      <li>Timestamp Tool.</li>
      <li>JSON Viewer.</li>
      <li>XML Viewer.</li>
      <li>HEX Viewer.</li>
      <li>Image Viewer.</li>
      <li>Color Picker.</li>
      <li>Qrcode Generator.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/reqable/reqable-app/refs/heads/main/arts/products.webp</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Benchmark</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/reqable/reqable-app/refs/heads/main/arts/benchmark_en_01.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>API Debugging</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/reqable/reqable-app/refs/heads/main/arts/screenshot_en_01.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>API Testing</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/reqable/reqable-app/refs/heads/main/arts/screenshot_en_02.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Mobile App</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/reqable/reqable-app/refs/heads/main/arts/screenshot_en_03.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.33.12" date="2025-04-23">
      <url>https://github.com/reqable/reqable-app/releases/latest</url>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
