<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.blackmagicdesign.Resolve</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <name>DaVinci Resolve</name>
  <summary>Professional Editing, Color, Effects, and Audio Post-production!</summary>

  <description>
    <p>DaVinci Resolve is a professional tool for video editing, color correction, visual effects, and audio post-production all in one software suite. It is widely used in the film and television industry for its powerful tools and flexibility.</p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.blackmagicdesign.Resolve.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>DaVinci Resolve Cut Page</caption>
      <image>https://images.blackmagicdesign.com/images/products/davinciresolve/overview/onesolution/carousel/cut.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>DaVinci Resolve Edit Page</caption>
      <image>https://images.blackmagicdesign.com/images/products/davinciresolve/overview/onesolution/carousel/edit.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>DaVinci Resolve Color Page</caption>
      <image>https://images.blackmagicdesign.com/images/products/davinciresolve/overview/onesolution/carousel/color.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>DaVinci Resolve Fusion Page</caption>
      <image>https://images.blackmagicdesign.com/images/products/davinciresolve/overview/onesolution/carousel/fusion.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>DaVinci Resolve 18 Fairlight Page</caption>
      <image>https://images.blackmagicdesign.com/images/products/davinciresolve/overview/onesolution/carousel/fairlight.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/davinciresolve</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/support/contact/email</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.blackmagicdesign.com/support</url>

  <categories>
    <category>AudioVideo</category>
    <category>Video</category>
    <category>Audio</category>
  </categories>

  <developer id="com.blackmagicdesign">
    <name>Blackmagic Design</name>
    <url>https://www.blackmagicdesign.com</url>
  </developer>

  <releases>
    <release version="19.0.1" date="2024-09-04">
      <description>
        DaVinci Resolve 19.0.1 improves timeline responsiveness when moving large numbers of clips, provides smoother playback with a fixed playhead, and resolves various bugs including issues with media management, matte nodes, and Dolby audio workflows. General stability and performance enhancements are also included.
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="19.0" date="2024-08-22">
      <description>
        DaVinci Resolve 19 brings advanced AI-powered tools such as voice isolation and automatic scene cut detection. It also introduces enhanced volumetric rendering for VFX and improves color grading with the new Film Look Creator. Integration with Blackmagic Cloud enables real-time collaborative editing.
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="18.6.6" date="2023-12-15">
      <description>
        DaVinci Resolve 18.6.6 adds support for audio loudness standards, 3D spatial audio, and improved Fairlight FX. Neural Engine performance is faster, and the update enhances media management features like project media cleanup.
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="18.6.0" date="2023-10-05">
      <description>
        This release introduces cloud syncing for remote collaboration, support for new formats like Sony XAVC HS, and improved rendering performance. Users can now generate and upload proxies automatically to Blackmagic Cloud.
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="18.1.3" date="2023-08-15">
      <description>
        Minor update with bug fixes and support for new media formats like Sony Venice 2. Improved stability for Fusion and timeline performance.
      </description>
    </release>

    <release version="18.0.0" date="2023-04-12">
      <description>
        Initial release of DaVinci Resolve 18, introducing Blackmagic Cloud for collaborative workflows, AI-driven color correction tools, and major performance upgrades. Vertical video support and timeline locking are also featured.
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

<content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

  <provides>
    <binary>com.blackmagicdesign.resolve</binary>
  </provides>

</component>

