<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.sublimehq.SublimeText</id>
  <name>Sublime Text</name>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.sublimetext.com/eula</project_license>
  <developer_name>Sublime HQ Pty Ltd</developer_name>
  <summary>Sophisticated text editor for code, markup and prose</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.sublimetext.com/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/sublimehq/sublime_text/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://forum.sublimetext.com/</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.sublimehq.SublimeText.desktop</launchable>
  <description>
    <p>The sophisticated text editor for code, markup and prose.</p>
    <p>
     Sublime Text 4 is packed with new features and enhancements, including:
    </p>
    <p>
     GPU Rendering

     Sublime Text can now utilize your GPU on Linux, Mac and Windows when rendering the interface. This results in a fluid UI all the way up to 8K resolutions, all while using less power than before.
    </p>
    <p>
     Tab Multi-Select

     File tabs have been enhanced to make split views effortless, with support throughout the interface and built-in commands. The side bar, tab bar, Goto Anything, Goto Definition, auto complete and more have all been tweaked to make code navigation easier and more intuitive than ever.
    </p>
    <p>
     Context-Aware Auto Complete

     The auto complete engine has been rewritten to provide smart completions based on existing code in a project. Suggestions are also augmented with info about their kind, and provide links to definitions.
    </p>
    <p>
     Refreshed UI

     The Default and Adaptive themes have been refreshed with new tab styles and inactive pane dimming. Themes and Color Schemes support auto dark-mode switching. The Adaptive theme on Windows and Linux now features custom title bars.
    </p>
    <p>
     TypeScript, JSX and TSX Support

     Support for one of the most popular new programming languages is now shipped by default. Utilize all of the smart syntax-based features of Sublime Text within the modern JavaScript ecosystem.
    </p>
    <p>
     Superpowered Syntax Definitions

     The syntax highlighting engine has been significantly improved, with new features like handling non-deterministic grammars, multi-line constructs, lazy embeds and syntax inheritance. Memory usage has been reduced, and load times are faster than ever.
    </p>
    <p>
     Updated Python API

     The Sublime Text API has been updated to Python 3.8, while keeping backwards compatibility with packages built for Sublime Text 3. The API has been significantly expanded, adding features that allow plugins like LSP to work better than ever. Read the revamped documentation here.
    </p>
    <p>
      This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by Sublime HQ Pty Ltd.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://www.sublimetext.com/screenshots/sublime_text_4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Development</category>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>TextEditor</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="remote" height="256" width="256">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.sublimehq.SublimeText/master/com.sublimehq.SublimeText-256.png</icon>
  <icon type="remote" height="128" width="128">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.sublimehq.SublimeText/master/com.sublimehq.SublimeText-128.png</icon>
  <icon type="remote" height="48" width="48">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.sublimehq.SublimeText/master/com.sublimehq.SublimeText-48.png</icon>
  <releases>
    <release date="2021-12-21" version="4126" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
