<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.fourwindstechnology.SI</id>
  
  <name>Spatial Integration</name>
  <summary>Powerful 3D Geospatial Data Visualisation</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.spatialintegration.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/EULA.rtf</project_license>
  
  <description>
    <p>
      Spatial Integration (SI) is a powerful 3D geospatial data visualisation application designed for geoscientists and GIS professionals.
      SI enables users to visualise and present complex geospatial datasets in an intuitive 3D environment. 
      With support for an extensive range of data formats and advanced rendering capabilities, SI is ideal for applications such as geology, geophysics, environmental analysis, urban planning, and resource management.
    </p>
    <p>
      Designed for modern, large datasets, SI leverages the power of contemporary hardware to deliver smooth performance and high-quality visualisations of the largest geospatial datasets. 
      Need to transition from a global view of the Earth using world-wide SRTM data and Blue Marble to high resolution lidar and air photos? No problem - SI handles it all with ease.
    </p>
    <p>
      Spatial Integration offers both a free Community Edition and a feature-rich Professional Edition, catering to different user needs and budgets.
    </p>
    <p>Features include:
    <ul>
      <li>Wide range of supported geospatial data formats</li>
      <li>Handles big data sets efficiently. SRTM of the entire Earth with high detail lidar insets? No problem!</li>
      <li>Drill holes, downhole interval discs and graphs</li>
      <li>Open most 3D graphics file formats to include data from external sources, including animated models</li>
      <li>GIS vectors draped over a terrain surface</li>
      <li>Import point data from CSV or GIS formats</li>
      <li>Cutting-edge transparency effects</li>
      <li>Fast - made for modern hardware</li>
      <li>Projected (flat) and geocentric (globe) coordinate systems supported</li>
      <li>Apply multiple clip planes and sections adjustable in real-time</li>
      <li>Interrogate the scene with the Information tool and leave annotation banners</li>
      <li>Bookmarks</li>
      <li>Custom camera animations (Work in progress)</li>
      <li>In application help (F1) and YouTube tutorials</li>
      <li>Very capable Community Edition</li>
      <li>Upgrade to Professional for more surface overlays and internet source overlays, downhole drill graphs and more advanced features</li>
    </ul>
  </p>
  </description>
  
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.spatialintegration.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Alpha_Iso_Drill.png</image>
      <caption>Cutting-edge transparency effects</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.spatialintegration.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/NASADEM_BlueMarble_Globe.png</image>
      <caption>Huge CRS support. Projected and geocentric modes</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.spatialintegration.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Drill_disc_graph_transparency.png</image>
      <caption>Drill holes, downhole intervals and 3D assets</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  
  <releases>
    <release version="2.3.5" date="2026-01-23">
      <description>
      <p>
        Change Log:
        <ul>
          <li>Initial Flatpak packaging</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  
  <url type="homepage">https://www.spatialintegration.com/</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCjCyE_H9dAlwt0M9KHA4suw</url>
  
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
