<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>com.onepassword.OnePassword</id>
    <name>1Password</name>
    <url type="homepage">https://1password.com/</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/flathub/com.onepassword.OnePassword/issues</url>
    <url type="help">https://support.1password.com/</url>
    <developer_name>AgileBits Inc.</developer_name>
    <summary>Password manager and secure wallet</summary>
    <description>
        <p>If you install 1Password with Flatpak, you’ll have access to all the features 1Password for Linux has to offer except:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>You’ll need to lock and unlock 1Password in your browser separately from the app.</li>
          <li>You won’t be able to unlock 1Password or 1Password CLI with system authentication.</li>
          <li>You won’t be able to use the <a href="https://developer.1password.com/docs/ssh/agent/">SSH agent</a>.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by AgileBits Inc.</p>
    </description>
    <screenshots>
        <image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/watchtower-light.png</image>
        <image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/unlocked-light.png</image>
        <image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/locked-dark.png</image>
        <image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/system_auth-light.png</image>
        <image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/browser_extension.png</image>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
        <release version="8.10.8" date="2023-06-27"/>
        <url>https://releases.1password.com/linux/8.10/#1password-for-linux-8.10.8</url>
        <description>
            <ul>
                <li>- If you’re a family organizer, you can now invite and confirm family members directly in the apps.
                </li>
                <li>- You’ll now see a banner about <a href="https://developer.1password.com/docs/cli/shell-plugins">1Password Shell Plugins</a> on API Credential items.</li>
                <li>- We’ve updated the design and details included in the SSH authentication prompt so you can learn more
                    about the request.
                </li>
                <li>- We’ve removed the note about needing SSH keys to be in a Private vault from Settings > Developer
                    because they can now be stored elsewhere.
                </li>
                <li>- The LastPass importer now supports Yubikey for two-factor authentication on your LastPass account.
                </li>
                <li>- If your device is offline, you’ll now see an Offline Items list in the sidebar if you’ve made
                    changes that aren’t yet saved in your 1Password account.
                </li>
                <li>- You can now choose custom icons for your vaults directly in the app.</li>
                <li>- You can now <a href="https://developer.1password.com/docs/ssh/agent/config/">create the config file for the 1Password SSH agent</a>.</li>
                <li>- You can now see the progress when you import your LastPass data.</li>
                <li>- You can now reset the app in Settings > Advanced.</li>
                <li>- SSH-related options are now sorted together in the actions menu when viewing the details of an SSH
                    key.
                </li>
                <li>- We’ve improved the error message that’s shown if your shared folders fail to import from LastPass.
                </li>
                <li>- We’ve fixed an issue that caused TLS certificates with misformed serial numbers preventing
                    connections from working.
                </li>
                <li>- We’ve improved the import feature to prevent it from timing out while syncing your information.</li>
                <li>- We’ve updated the color of the banner for items that may be in the wrong account.</li>
                <li>- We’ve fixed an issue that caused items imported from LastPass to show the wrong Watchtower banner.
                </li>
                <li>- We’ve fixed an issue with multi-factor authentication in the LastPass importer.</li>
                <li>- We’ve fixed some incorrect punctuation of labels in Settings.</li>
                <li>- We’ve fixed an issue that could cause the importing from LastPass to fail if you sign into LastPass
                    using SSO.
                </li>
                <li>- We’ve fixed an issue with importing data from a LastPass account containing a lot users with access
                    to the same shared folder.
                </li>
                <li>- We’ve fixed an issue that could cause importing a 1PUX file to fail.</li>
                <li>- You can now connect to 1Password CLI even if the script or application running the CLI is not owned
                    by the root user.
                </li>
            </ul>
        </description>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    </content_rating>
    <update_contact>support@1password.com</update_contact>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>Proprietary</project_license>
</component>
