<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>com.rabbit_company.passky</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.rabbit_company.passky.desktop</launchable>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>

    <name>Passky</name>

    <categories>
        <category>Utility</category>
    </categories>

    <summary>Passky is a simple, modern, lightweight, open-source and secure password manager.</summary>

    <description>
      <p>Passky is open-source. This means that anyone can download it, dig into its code, and customize it to their liking. Using Passky doesn’t require an upfront cost or monthly subscription. It’s completely free to download and can be hosted by anyone who has the space to do so.</p>
      <p>Passky simplifies your digital life and solves your password problem. All you’ll ever need to do is remember a single, ultra-secure password that includes uppercase letters, lowercase letters, numbers, and special characters. Once you’ve got that written down in your wallet or purse (or buried in your memory), you’ll get the benefit of secure passwords across your online accounts without having to memorize dozens of codewords. This makes it one of the most secure ways to protect your online identity.</p>    
      <p>Passky has been designed with modern users in mind. That’s why we’ve strived to provide an interface that’s streamlined and easy to use. Unlike some of the competition, Passky can be easily used by anyone, including techies and computer novices. And since it’s built for performance, you won’t need to overtax your CPU or waste a lot of storage space to keep it running.</p>
    </description>

    <developer_name>Rabbit Company LLC</developer_name>

    <releases>
      <release date="2022-03-04" version="6.0.1" />
    </releases>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot><image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/passky1.png</image></screenshot>
        <screenshot><image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/passky2.png</image></screenshot>
        <screenshot><image type="source">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/image_2021-05-15_212635.png</image></screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

    <metadata>
        <value key="GnomeSoftware::popular-background">https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2021/05/passky_banner.png</value>
    </metadata>

    <url type="homepage">https://passky.org</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/Rabbit-Company/Passky-Desktop/issues</url>
    <url type="faq">https://passky.org/contact</url>
    <url type="donation">https://passky.org/donation</url>
    <url type="translate">https://crowdin.com/project/passky</url>
    <url type="contact">https://passky.org/contact</url>
</component>