<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.jetbrains.WebStorm</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA</metadata_license>
  <name>WebStorm</name>
  <summary>The smartest JavaScript IDE</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Use the full power of the modern JavaScript ecosystem – WebStorm’s got you covered!
    Enjoy the intelligent code completion, on-the-fly error detection, powerful navigation
    and refactoring for JavaScript, TypeScript, stylesheet languages, and all the most
    popular frameworks.</p>
    <p>Debug your client-side and Node.js apps with ease in the IDE – put breakpoints right
    in the source code, explore the call stack and variables, set watches, and use the
    interactive console.</p>
    <p>Take advantage of the linters, build tools, test runners, REST client, and other
    tools, all deeply integrated with the IDE. But any time you need Terminal, it's also
    available as an IDE tool window.</p>
    <p>Run and debug tests with Karma, Mocha, Protractor, and Jest in WebStorm. Immediately
    see test statuses right in the editor, or in a handy treeview from which you can quickly
    jump to the test.</p>
    <p>Use a simple unified UI to work with Git, GitHub, Mercurial, and other VCS. Commit
    files, review changes, and resolve conflicts with a visual diff/merge tool right in the
    IDE.</p>
    <p>WebStorm is available for a free 30-day evaluation. Monthly and yearly subscription
    options are available for companies and individual users.</p>
    <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by JetBrains s.r.o.</p>
    </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.jetbrains.com/webstorm/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://youtrack.jetbrains.com/</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.jetbrains.com/help/webstorm/</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.jetbrains.WebStorm.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="2018.3.3" date="2019-01-11">
      <description>
        <p>What’s new:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for Set Literals in Dart</li>
          <li>Completion for attribute bindings in Angular (e.g. [atrr.foo] )</li>
          <li>Better coding assistance for some Ionic and @angular/flex-layout attributes</li>
        </ul>
        <p>What’s fixed:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Wrong indent after self-closing JSX tags in JavaScript and TypeScript files</li>
          <li>Decorators are now supported in the class expressions like let newTest = @test class Test or export default @observer class Test</li>
          <li>When using the bundled TypeScript service in Angular apps, the Angular language service is now disabled. Otherwise, there’re false errors in the template files</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <developer_name>JetBrains</developer_name>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://www.jetbrains.com/webstorm/img/screenshots/webstorm-main.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <update_contact>sakcheen+flathub_AT_gmail.com</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
