<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2013 First Lastname <your@email.com> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.wonderunit.Storyboarder</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>Storyboarder</name>
  <summary>Create and edit storyboards</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      Storyboarder makes it easy to visualize a story as fast you can draw stick
      figures. Quickly draw to test if a story idea works. Create and show animatics
      to others. Express your story idea without making a movie.
    </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.wonderunit.Storyboarder.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Storyboarding session</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/megumumpkin/flathub/com.wonderunit.Storyboarder/storyboarder-screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://wonderunit.com/storyboarder/</url>
  <project_group>Wonder Unit</project_group>

  <provides>
    <binary>storyboarder</binary>
  </provides>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />

  <releases>
    <release version="3.0.0" date="2021-02-17">
      <description>
        <p>Localization</p>
        <p>Built-in support for American English, Russian, and Chinese (Simplified).
        Use the Language Editor to add your own! Share language files with friends!
        Invent a new language! Translate Storyboarder into your own secret twin language!</p>
        <p>Emotions</p>
        <p>Slap some personality on those faces with custom emotions you draw yourself!
        (And we really mean it, you have to draw them yourself. We ran out of time to
        add more examples).</p>
        <p>Hair</p>
        <p>Are your Characters due for a new 'do? Hoist luscious locks upon their
        heads using custom hair attachments, now in a fancy new tab! Please make
        and share further hair!</p>
        <p>Introducing stbr.link</p>
        <p>Storyboarder used to run a VR server on your local computer, but it didn't use secure HTTPS, and that stopped working in all the VR-capable browsers. So, now Shot Generator VR routes connections through stbr.link, a server operated by Wonder Unit. You can share the link with friends, and they can browse your scenes in VR, hosted by your computer, in multi-user mode. stbr.link does not store or have access to any of your data other than the basics it needs to setup connections between computers -- once you've connected to peers, your Shot Generator scenes, models, and images are transferred peer-to-peer. But keep in mind that anyone with the correct link can download Shot Generator files from your computer while VR is running.</p>
        <p>Added</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Shot Generator: Insert Image via Drag/Drop or Paste</li>
          <li>Storyboarder: Localization</li>
          <li>Storyboarder: zh-CN Localization</li>
          <li>Shot Generator: Remember Window Size</li>
          <li>Shot Generator: Scale UI Automatically on Window Resize</li>
          <li>IK support for custom characters that have the same set of bones as built-in characters.</li>
          <li>Shot Generator: Character Rotation Gizmo, Add Rotation Podium</li>
          <li>VR now uses stbr.link where multiple users can connect</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixed</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Scale UI Save/Restore</li>
          <li>Scale UI Min/Max Based on Screen Resolution</li>
          <li>Shot Generator never-ending camera movement bug</li>
          <li>Better lock to prevent overwrite in multi-user VR</li>
          <li>VR Pose Capture bug fix</li>
          <li>Storyboarder: Video Export</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
