<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.opera.opera-gx</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.opera.opera-gx.desktop</launchable>
  <name>Opera GX</name>
  <developer_name>Opera</developer_name>
  <summary>Opera GX: THE gaming browser</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.opera.com/legal/eula-computers</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.opera.com/gx/</url>
  <url type="faq">https://help.opera.com/en/faq/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://opera.atlassian.net/servicedesk/customer/portal/118</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.opera.com/help</url>
  <description>
   <p>Opera GX: THE gaming browser for powerful players</p>
   <p>Opera GX doesn't play by regular browser rules. It isn't here to blend in. It's here to take over.
Designed from the ground up for gamers, streamers, modders, and anyone who wants more say in how their browser looks, sounds, and performs.
GX puts you in the driver's seat with unique performance features:
  <ul>
    <li>GX Control → limit RAM, and network usage, so your games stay smooth while your browser stays light.</li>
    <li>GX Cleaner → clear out old files and junk with one click and keep your browser running like new.</li>
    <li>Hot Tabs Killer → spot resource-draining tabs and shut them down instantly.</li>
  </ul>
</p>
<p>
Personalize every pixel of GX with GX Mods. Customize your themes, sounds, wallpapers, shaders, splash screens, icons and more. Build your own mod or browse thousands of community creations in the GX Store.

Stay connected with your crew directly in the sidebar. Built-in Discord, Twitch, TikTok, WhatsApp, Instagram, Bluesky, Facebook Messenger, Telegram, or Slack — all fully integrated so you chat, stream and scroll without losing focus. Forget any tab overload.

GX Corner keeps you ahead of the game with free games, release calendars, gaming news and the hottest deals — all in one spot, updated daily.

Tune your audio with the built-in Music Player supporting Spotify, Apple Music, YouTube Music and more — no extra apps, no switching tabs. Protect your privacy with built-in Free VPN, Ad Blocker, Tracker Blocker, and Cryptomining Protection. And when things get awkward, hit Panic Button (F12) to instantly hide your session.

Your data stays yours — Opera GX follows strict security standards, with no-log VPN independently audited by Deloitte.
Opera GX also includes:
<ul>
  <li>Split Screen browsing</li>
  <li>Video Pop-Out for floating video windows</li>
  <li>Tab Islands &amp; Tab Emojis to keep your tabs organized and easy to spot</li>
  <li>Aria browser AI — free, built-in AI assistant for instant answers</li>
  <li>My Flow for seamless file and link sharing across devices</li>
  <li>Workspaces &amp; Pinboards to keep your projects tidy</li>
</ul>
</p>
<p>With 30+ million users worldwide and a global Discord community shaping GX every day, Opera GX is way more than a browser. It becomes your personalized control room for gaming, creating, streaming… and getting things done.
Download Opera GX and enjoy the Internet from your own POV.</p>
  </description>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>web browser</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
    <category>WebBrowser</category>
    <category>InstantMessaging</category>
    <category>Chat</category>
    <category>Feed</category>
  </categories>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://proxy.gxcorner.games/resizer/assets/Speed_dial_page_640c2ce482.png</image>
      <caption>Speed dial page - dark theme</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://proxy.gxcorner.games/resizer/assets/Speed_dial_page_Light_theme_9a26989a76.png</image>
      <caption>Speed dial page - light theme</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://proxy.gxcorner.games/resizer/assets/Limiters_page_2c3986a694.png</image>
      <caption>GX Control</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://proxy.gxcorner.games/resizer/assets/Customisation_86cec41e67.png</image>
      <caption>Mods page</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="128.0.5807.51" date="2026-03-05">
      <description>Initial Opera GX release for flathub</description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
