<?xml version="1.0"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.super_productivity.SuperProductivity</id>
  <name>Super Productivity</name>
  <summary>Advanced to-do list app with timeboxing, time tracking, and third-party integration</summary>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://super-productivity.com/</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/johannesjo/super-productivity/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://github.com/sponsors/johannesjo</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.super_productivity.SuperProductivity.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="stock">com.super_productivity.SuperProductivity</icon>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>ProjectManagement</category>
  </categories>
  <developer id="com.super_productivity">
    <name>Johannes Millan</name>
  </developer>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <description>
    <ul>
      <li>Keep organized and focused! Plan and categorize your tasks using sub-tasks, projects and tags and color code them as needed.</li>
      <li>Use timeboxing and track your time. Create time sheets and work summaries in a breeze to easily export them to your company's time tracking system.</li>
      <li>A break reminder reminds you when it's time to step away.</li>
      <li>The anti-procrastination feature helps you gain perspective when you really need to.</li>
      <li>Need some extra focus? A Pomodoro timer is also always at hand.</li>
      <li>Collect personal metrics to see which of your work routines need adjustments.</li>
      <li>Integrate with Jira, GitHub, GitLab, Gitea and OpenProject. Auto import tasks assigned to you, plan the details locally, automatically create work logs, and get notified immediately, when something changes.</li>
      <li>Back up and synchronize your data across multiple devices with Dropbox and WebDAV support</li>
      <li>Attach context information to tasks and projects. Create notes, attach files or create project-level bookmarks for links, files, and even commands.</li>
      <li>Super Productivity respects your privacy and does NOT collect any data and there are no user accounts or registration. You decide where you store your data!</li>
      <li>It's free and open source and always will be.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://super-productivity.com/static/7d2933a034590b3f40301a65e1d52538/34ae2/standard.png</image>
      <caption>An overview of today's tasks, including time estimates and progress tracking</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://super-productivity.com/static/80c1ca336f5d3ad06390fdfecc7c6ad7/34ae2/jira.png</image>
      <caption>Task details imported from GitHub</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://super-productivity.com/static/f259c271688b81febdf8082b22645823/34ae2/break-reminder.png</image>
      <caption>Break reminder</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://super-productivity.com/static/d56fca55ab08d2464fb7b0bbd15d43a0/34ae2/timeline-calendar.png</image>
      <caption>A timeline view of tasks, including integration with calendar events</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://super-productivity.com/static/92c8d60be9f55a4bf6a8ebc97e3bb6a5/34ae2/worklog.png</image>
      <caption>Worklog view, showing a summary of tasks broken down by year, month, week, and day</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="10.2.3" date="2024-11-29"/>
  </releases>
</component>
