<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>de.billardgl.Billardgl</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">de.billardgl.Billardgl.desktop</launchable>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>

    <name>Billiards</name>
    <name xml:lang="ar">بلياردو</name>
    <name xml:lang="bn">বিলিয়ার্ডস</name>
    <name xml:lang="de">Billard</name>
    <name xml:lang="es">Billar</name>
    <name xml:lang="fr">Billard</name>
    <name xml:lang="hi">बिलियर्ड्स</name>
    <name xml:lang="id">Biliar</name>
    <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Sinuca</name>
    <name xml:lang="ro">Biliard</name>
    <name xml:lang="th">บิลเลียด</name>
    <name xml:lang="vi">Bida</name>
    <name xml:lang="zh_CN">桌球</name>
    <name xml:lang="zh_TW">撞球</name>

    <categories>
        <category>Game</category>
    </categories>

    <summary>Fun 3D billiards game</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ar">لعبة بلياردو ممتعة ثلاثية الأبعاد</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="bn">মজার 3D বিলিয়ার্ডস খেলা</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="de">Spaßiges 3D-Billard-Spiel</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="es">Practica tus habilidades con este juego de billar en 3D</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu de billard amusant en 3D</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="hi">3D बिलियर्ड्स गेम</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="id">Game biliar 3D seru</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Divertido jogo de sinuca em 3D</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ro">Jocuri de biliard 3D</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="th">เกมบิลเลียด 3 มิติ</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="vi">Trò chơi bida 3D vui nhộn</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">趣味3D桌球游戏</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">有趣的 3D 撞球遊戲</summary>

    <description><p>Do you love playing billiards, or have you ever wanted to learn how to play? This game lets you have the experience of playing pool and other similar games right from your home. It’s simple to learn and use, yet highly realistic. This app is a great tool for both playing for fun and improving your game.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ar"><p>هل تحب لعب البلياردو، هل كنت تريد في أي وقت مضى أن تتعلم كيف تلعبها؟ هذه اللعبة تتيح لديك تجربة لعب البلياردو وغيرها من الألعاب المماثلة مباشرة من منزلك. إنها سهلة التعلم والإستخدام، لكنها واقعيةٌ للغاية. هذا التطبيق أداة عظيمة لكل من اللعب من أجل المتعة ولتحسين لعبك.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="bn"><p>আপনি কি বিলিয়ার্ড খেলতে ভালবাসেন, অথবা কখনো খেলা শিখতে চেয়েছেন? এই খেলার মাধ্যমে আপনি ঘরে বসেই পুল এবং আরো অন্যান্য একইরকম খেলার অভিজ্ঞতা অর্জন করতে পারবেন। অত্যন্ত বাস্তবধর্মী হলেও এই খেলাটি সহজে শেখা ও ব্যবহার করা যায়। শুধু মজার জন্য খেলা বা আপনার দক্ষতা বাড়ানোর জন্যও এই এ্যাপটি খুবই কার্যকরী।</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="es"><p>¿Te gusta jugar al billar, o tal vez has querido aprender como jugarlo? Con este programa puedes jugar al billar y a otros juegos parecidos desde tu casa por completamente gratis. Este programa es muy realista y sencilla para aprender a jugar, para practicar estrategias o simplemente para divertirte por un rato.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="fr"><p>Aimez-vous jouer au billard, ou avez-vous jamais voulu apprendre comment y jouer ? Ce jeu vous donne une expérience de jeu de billard et autres jeux similaires depuis le confort de votre maison. Il est simple à prendre en main et à utiliser, tout en étant hautement réaliste. Cette application est un excellent outil à la fois pour vous divertir et pour améliorer votre technique de jeu.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="hi"><p>क्या आपको बिलियर्ड्स खेलना भाता है या क्या कभी आपने इसे सीखना चाहा है? यह गेम आपको अपने घर से ही पूल और ऐसे ही अन्य गेमों को खेलने का मजेदार एहसास देता है। इसे सीखना और इस्तेमाल करना आसान है। यह ऐप्स आनंद के लिए खेलने के लिए या अपने खेल में सुधार लाने, दोनों के लिए कमाल है।</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="id"><p>Apakah Anda suka bermain biliar, atau pernah ingin belajar cara memainkannya? Permainan ini membuat Anda mendapatkan pengalaman bermain biliar dan sejenisnya langsung di rumah Anda. Mudah untuk dipelajari dan digunakan, juga sangat realistis. Aplikasi ini cocok untuk bermain sambil bersenang-senang sekaligus meningkatkan kemampuan biliar Anda.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR"><p>Você gosta de jogar sinuca ou sempre quis aprender a jogar? Este jogo proporciona a experiência de jogar sinuca e outros jogos similares direto da sua casa. É fácil de aprender e de usar, mas altamente realista. Este programa é uma ótima ferramenta para jogar, se divertir e melhorar o seu jogo.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ro"><p>Iti place sa joci biliard,sau ai vrut sa inveti vreodata sa inveti cum se joaca?Acest joc te lasa sa ai parte de experienta jocului chiar de acasa.Este simplu de invatat,dar si foarte realist.Aceasta aplicatie este o unealta grozava pentru invatare dar si pentru a-ti imbunatati jocul.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="th"><p>คุณรักการเล่นบิลเลียดหรือคุณเคยอยากที่จะเรียนรู้วิธีการเล่นมั้ย เกมนี้ช่วยให้คุณมีประสบการณ์ในการเล่นบิลเลียดและเกมอื่น ๆ ที่คล้ายกันได้จากที่บ้านของคุณ มันง่ายที่จะเรียนรู้และใช้ แต่สมจริงอย่างมาก แอพนี้เป็นเครื่องมือที่ดีสำหรับทั้งการเล่นเพื่อความสนุกสนานและปรับปรุงเกมการเล่นของคุณ</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="vi"><p>Bạn thích chơi bida, hoặc đã từng muốn tìm hiểu cách chơi như thế nào? Trò chơi này sẽ mang đến cho bạn trải nghiệm như được chơi bida và các trò chơi tượng tự khác ngay tại nhà. Đây là trò chơi rất dễ tìm hiểu và chơi với độ thực tế cao. Ứng dụng này chính là công cụ tuyệt vời để vừa chơi để giải trí vừa cải thiện trình độ của bạn.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_CN"><p>您爱打桌球吗？您想学吗？这款游戏让您足不出户即可体验桌球这类游戏的快乐。简单易操作，带给您最真实的体验。畅玩的同时提升游戏技能，这款APP带给您惊喜。</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_TW"><p>你喜歡玩撞球或你曾想過要學如何玩撞球嗎？這個遊戲讓你在家裡就可以擁有撞球和其他類似遊戲的體驗。它很簡單易學並且容易使用，而且感覺非常真實。這款應用程式是一個很棒的工具，可以獲得樂趣，也可以改善你的撞球技巧。</p></description>

    <developer_name>Tobias Nopper, Stefan Disch, Martina Welte</developer_name>

    <releases>
      <release date="2003-07-14" version="1.75" />
    </releases>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot><image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/de.billardgl.Billardgl/C/de.billardgl.billardgl-screenshot1.jpg</image></screenshot>
        <screenshot><image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/de.billardgl.Billardgl/C/de.billardgl.billardgl-screenshot2.jpg</image></screenshot>
        <screenshot><image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/de.billardgl.Billardgl/C/de.billardgl.billardgl-screenshot3.jpg</image></screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

    <metadata>
        <value key="GnomeSoftware::popular-background">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/thumbnails/de.billardgl.Billardgl/de.billardgl.billardgl-thumb.jpg</value>
    </metadata>

    <url type="homepage">http://www.billardgl.de/index-en.html</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://sourceforge.net/p/billardgl/bugs/</url>
</component>
