<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>dudetronics.nostar.DroidStar</id>
    <name>DroidStar</name>
    <provides>
        <id>DroidStar.desktop</id>
    </provides>
    <summary>DroidStar (Connects to M17, Fusion (YSF/FCS), DMR, P25, NXDN, D-STAR (REF/XRF/DCS) reflectors and AllStar nodes)</summary>
    <developer_name>dudetronics.com/</developer_name>
    <description>
        <p>
            This software connects to M17, Fusion (YSF/FCS, DN and VW modes are supported), DMR, P25, NXDN, D-STAR (REF/XRF/DCS)
            reflectors and AllStar nodes (as an IAX2 client) over UDP. It is compatible with all of the AMBE USB devices
            out there (ThumbDV, DVstick 30, DVSI, etc). It also supports MMDVM modems and can be used as a hotspot, or as a
            stand-alone transceiver via direct mode to the MMDVM device.

            A vocoder plugin can be downloaded from a URL, which will place the vocoder into the correct location
            for the platform. Add a full http url, including the filename, to the Vocoder URL option on the settings tab,
            and click the Download vocoder button.

            For Android and iOS devices, the vocoder URL download method is the only way to load a vocoder plugin.
            For Linux/MacOS/Windows, a vocoder can also be manually placed. Copy the plugin to the system settings
            file location. On Linux, this is ~/.config/dudetronics. It is the same place where the host and id files
            are located (DMRHosts.txt, DMRIDs.data, etc).

            The vocoder plugin filename must be named vocoder_plugin.platform.arch where platform and arch can be any
            of the following: platform: linux, darwin, winnt, android, ios arch: x86_64, arm, arm64

            The platform and arch for your device are identified on the About tab.
            Download from : https://ke0zvd.com/installing-the-software-vocoder/
        </p>
    </description>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
    <url type="homepage">http://www.dudetronics.com/</url>
    <project_group>none</project_group>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Main JTDX window</caption>
            <image>
                https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FsjXl18X0AAm5O9?format=png
            </image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
        <release version="git 2f695e6" date="2023-03-15"/>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
    <update_contact>castilloeduardo@outlook.com.ar</update_contact>
</component>