<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
	<id>eu.ngdevelopment.tsukitag</id>
	<name>Tsuki-tag</name>
	<summary>Anime imageboard browser, aggregator, downloader, tagger, converter, collection manager. Download images from imageboards while keeping or modifying the original tag list, browse and create your own collections, configure workspaces for customizable image downloads with file and tag templating support.</summary>
	<metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-3.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
	<description>
		<p>Tsuki-tag is an aggregated anime imageboard browser and collection manager, which lets you browse multiple image sources in a combined view, search images using tags, download images into configured workspaces (folders) with customization and filename templating support, and manage or curate multiple collections of your chosen images.</p>
		<p>Tsuki-tag can inject EXIF metadata information (tag, image attributes, copyright notice, etc.) into the images during downloading or saving, with an additional option to convert non-JPG images to JPG images which support EXIF metadata. This could provide artists with a great way of creating and organizing a collection of images for reference, or to manage and appropriately annotate their own images with author and copyright information.</p>
		<p>Features include:</p>
		<ul>
			<li> Browse an aggregated collection of images retrieved from a number of pre-configured image providers in a paginated view. </li>
			<li> Fine-tune which providers are queried, along with what type of images should be shown ('safe', 'questionable', 'explicit'). </li>
			<li> Search for images using tags and tag combinations with wildcard support, exclude images from being displayed using another set of tags with wildcard and regular expression support. </li>
			<li> Hover over images for a quick look at their attributes and information, or select them to keep them available for batch operations. </li>
			<li> Open images in separate tabs and continue browsing. </li>
			<li> Multi-selection system with support for batch operations (batch add to / remove from workspaces and online lists, batch update or annotate). </li>
			<li> Create online lists, which are a local collection of image metadata which can be browsed just as the online providers. </li>
			<li> Create workspaces, which on top of the features of online lists, lets you download images to configured folders with customizable behavior. </li>
			<li> Import local files or folders to workspaces, or convert one of your image folders to a workspace. </li>
			<li> Create metadata groups, which are a collection of information such as author, copyright notice, description and notes, which can be directly injected into the EXIF metadata of the JPG images files during workspace operations. </li>
			<li> Convert non-JPG images to JPG for EXIF support. </li>
			<li> Add, edit, or remove image tags before workspace or online list operations. </li>
			<li> Create tag rules for your online lists or workspaces with wildcard and regular expression support, to automatically process an image across multiple lists. </li>
			<li> Automatically add or remove tags when an image is added to, or removed from a workspace or online list, with templating support. </li>
			<li> Specify the file names of files to be downloaded to a workspace, with templating support. </li>
			<li> Global tag blacklisting with wildcard and regular expression support. </li>
			<li> Several other features such as opening images in your default image editor, opening or copying the image website URL, re-downloading the image from the original provider, and more. </li>
		</ul>
	</description>
	<developer_name>ngelsi</developer_name>
	<url type="homepage">https://ngelsi.ngdevelopment.eu</url>
	<url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/ngelsi/tsuki-tag-native/issues</url>
	<url type="donation">https://ko-fi.com/ngelsi</url>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image>https://ngelsi.ngdevelopment.eu/images/main01.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>https://ngelsi.ngdevelopment.eu/images/main02.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>https://ngelsi.ngdevelopment.eu/images/main03.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>https://ngelsi.ngdevelopment.eu/images/main04.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>https://ngelsi.ngdevelopment.eu/images/main05.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>		
	</screenshots>
	<releases>
		<release version="0.9.2" date="2022-01-28">
			<description>
				<p>v0.9.2 is an initial BETA release which provides the featureset described in the description above.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>
</component>