<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>fm.cancel.Ripcord</id>
  <name>Ripcord</name>
  <summary>Alternative desktop chat client for Slack (and Discord)</summary>

  <url type="homepage">https://cancel.fm/ripcord//</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://dev.cancel.fm/issues</url>

  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>

  <description>
    <p>Ripcord is a desktop chat client for group-centric services like Slack and Discord. It provides a traditional compact desktop interface designed for power users. It's not built on top of web browser technology: it has a small resource footprint, responds quickly to input, and gets out of your way. Shareware is coming back, baby.</p>
    <p>Ripcord is developed independently, and is <b>not affiliated with Slack or Discord.</b></p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">fm.cancel.Ripcord.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cancel.fm/ripcord/static/ripcord_screenshot_win_6.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cancel.fm/ripcord/static/ripcord_screenshot_win_5.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cancel.fm/ripcord/static/ripcord_screenshot_win_7.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="0.4.29" date="2021-06-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>General:</li>
          <li>Added option to add extra highlighting to the active tab with an extra line of color (off by default.)</li>
          <li>Minor tweaks to the GUI style engine to make disabled widgets more distinct from enabled widgets.</li>
        </ul>
        <ul>
          <li>Slack:</li>
          <li>Fixed sign-in with username &amp; password no longer working.
          <ul>
            <li>Some stuff changed on Slack's servers. Now Ripcord has been updated to deal with it.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Fixed file upload no longer working.
          <ul>
            <li>Same as above.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Added per-message explicit timestamp in the right-click menu for messages.</li>
          <li>Increased per-workspace custom emoji limit from 100,000 to 1,000,000.</li>
          <li>Added a workaround for Apple <code>rdar://12345</code> links being mangled due to URL parsing treating the <code>12345</code> part as an integer IP address.
          <ul>
            <li>This integer parsing is apparently the "correct" behavior for parsing URLs, but results in <code>rdar://12345</code> links being useless in Ripcord.</li>
            <li>Ripcord now has a workaround that will rewrite those URLs to <code>rdar://problem/12345</code> when they're clicked on or copied to the clipboard. This prevents the the number part from being (correctly?) parsed as integer, and should still work with the <code>rdar://</code> URL handlers.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Added <code>gemini://</code> as a whitelisted URL scheme.</li>
          <li>Added <code>snrx://</code> as a whitelisted URL scheme.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Note for Slack users: there is a known and unresolved issue where your channel sidebar may become cluttered with junk channels named like <code>#mpdm-foo--bar</code>. I know about this and I'm fixing it. The fix for it didn't make it into this version, 0.4.29, because a complete and flexible solution for it involves changing some code that will require heavy testing, and I didn't want to delay releasing an update any longer. Sorry about that.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Discord</li>
          <li>Added a dedicated mute button for other users in voice chats.
          <ul>
            <li>Finally.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Added ability to bookmark group DM channels.
          <ul>
            <li>Finally.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Added support for replying to messages in DM and group DM channels.</li>
          <li>Added support for newer permissions flags, like "request to speak" for stage channels.</li>
          <li>Added a menu item and a toolbar button to join or start DM and group DM voice calls.
          <ul>
            <li>The only way to do this previously was to right-click on the DM channel in the sidebar. That was stupid. Now there's a regular menu item and toolbar button.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Added guild creation date in the right-click menu for guilds.</li>
          <li>Added channel creation date in the right-click menu for channels.</li>
          <li>Added anti-spam warning in the "accept invite" menu/dialog.</li>
          <li>Changed the URL used when clicking on the thumbnail of an uploaded video so that web browsers will prefer to play the video in a tab instead of download the video as a file to disk.
          <ul>
            <li>Finally.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Fixed a bug where angle brackets could be treated as Qt's pseudo-HTML text styling markers in the rich embed text sub-view.
          <ul>
            <li>This was not an exploitable bug. It was caused by Qt's document layout system automatically trying to apply bold, italic, etc. styling if it thought the plain text had HTML-like tags in it.</li>
          </ul></li>
          <li>Fixed unsent input text being cleared when navigating from one Discord channel to another while quick reply input mode is engaged.</li>
        </ul>
        <ul>
          <li>Windows</li>
          <li>Reordered some initialization procedures to slightly reduce startup time.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>