<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>rm.reaper.Reaper</id>
  <name>Reaper</name>
  <summary>Digital Audio Workstation.</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.reaper.fm/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://forum.cockos.com/forumdisplay.php?f=22</url>
  <url type="help">https://forum.cockos.com/</url>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.reaper.fm/dist-agreement.php</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>REAPER is a complete digital audio production application for computers, offering a full multitrack audio and MIDI recording, editing, processing, mixing and mastering toolset.  </p>
    <p> Using REAPER you can import any audio and MIDI, synthesize, sample, compose, arrange, edit, mix, and master songs or any other audio projects. If you add a hardware audio interface and a microphone, you have a complete professional quality recording studio, suitable for recording anything from a soloist to a band to an orchestra.</p>
    <p>"REAPER" is a trial shareware version.</p>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">fm.reaper.Reaper.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Overview</caption>
      <image>https://www.reaper.fm/v6img/ss_persp_v63.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="v6.58" date="2022-05-18">
      <description>
        <p>Video</p>
        <ul>
          <li>decode mono audio to stereo when using WMF </li>
          <li>fix various video decoding issues when using WMF •</li>
          <li>fix rendering embedded AAC 4-channel audio when using WMF </li>
          <li>fix rendering video with certain colorspace/size combinations when using WMF • </li>
          <li>support embedding multichannel audio in MP4 video when using WMF </li>
          <li>support rendering video-only or audio-only mp4 when using WMF</li>
          <li>improve error message when AVFoundation encoder fails to initialize </li>
          <li>support rendering multichannel AAC when using AVFoundation </li>
        </ul>

        <p>Render</p>
        <ul>
          <li>support rendering region matrix via master • </li>
          <li>fix normalizing render when rendering video with WMF </li>
          <li>if render bounds set to "selected regions" and no regions are selected, render all regions </li>
          <li>improve render speed when rendering stems or regions via master • </li>
          <li>always display one momentary loudness measurement and one short-term loudness measurement in HTML charts </li>
          <li>optionally display project regions/markers in HTML charts </li>
          <li>remove option to render to .wmv or .wma files; there's no reason to use these file formats as containers for modern codecs • </li>
        </ul>

        <p>Razor edits</p>
        <ul>
          <li>fix potential display flickering after certain actions/zoom/scroll • </li>
          <li>fix potential incorrect drawing when zoomed in very far </li>
          <li>add undo points when clearing selections </li>
          <li>prevent selections from being lost when loading a project with missing media </li>
        </ul>

        <p>VST</p>
        <ul>
          <li>avoid duplicate entries when multiple instances of a VST3 UID16 are found with different filename parts • </li>
          <li>support scanning Windows .vst3 bundles that have the system filesystem attribute set • </li>
        </ul>

        <p>Auto-save</p>
        <ul>
          <li>improve error messages • </li>
          li
        </ul>

        <p>Drag and drop</p>
        <ul>
          <li>fix color of insert-new-track indicator text • </li>
          li
        </ul>

        <p>IDEs</p>
        <ul>
          <li>use 6.53-style sorting for watch lists • </li>
          li
        </ul>

        <p>JSFX</p>
        <ul>
          <li>update classic volume adjustment JSFX to use a step size of 0.1dB </li>
          lli
        </ul>

        <p>LV2</p>
        <ul>
          <li>support compatibility setting to ignore state-change notifications • </li>
          lli
        </ul>

        <p>Media explorer</p>
        <ul>
          <li>fix My Computer view when localized • </li>
          lli
        </ul>

        <p>Media items</p>
        <ul>
          <li>allow clicking item notes and item properties buttons on locked items </li>
          lli
        </ul>

        <p>MIDI editor</p>
        <ul>
          <li>fix mouse modifier to delete touched notes when moving mouse very slowly • </li>
          lli
        </ul>

        <p>Performance</p>
        <ul>
          <li>fix mouse modifier to delete touched notes when moving mouse very slowly • </li>
          lli
        </ul>

        <p>ReaFIR</p>
        <ul>
          <li>fix inconsistent processing of first block of audio </li>
          lli
        </ul>

        <p>ReaScript</p>
        <ul>
          <li>make Lua handling of unspecified Optional const char* parameters consistent with EEL2, other data types • </li>
          lli
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <developer_name>
        Cockos Incorporated
    </developer_name>
  <update_contact>
        support@cockos.com
    </update_contact>
</component>