<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>games.zetsubou.SablesGrimoireDemo</id>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<name>Sable's Grimoire (Demo)</name>
	<summary>Monster girl visual novel which takes place in a magic academy</summary>
	<description>
		<p>Sable's Grimoire tells the story of an aspiring magic researcher who begins to attend an academy filled with demi-humans.</p>
		<p>When Sable is accepted into Amadronia Magic Academy, a prestigious academy famous for its resources and curriculum, he believes that he has crossed an important milestone in his life.</p>
		<p>As an aspiring magic researcher, not to mention one of the few pure-blooded human beings capable of using magic, Sable has high hopes for his time at Amadronia. His dream of becoming a world-renowned magic researcher is finally within his grasp, and with the assistance of the much-lauded teaching staff at Amadronia, he is sure that the next few years of his life will be as productive as they are enlightening.</p>
		<p>Unfortunately for Sable, his first day at Amadronia quickly proves to him that this will not be the case.</p>
		<p>Arrogant elves, a ravenous rokurokubi, a poison-tongued mandragora, a pyromaniac dragon, unenthusiastic teachers - Amadronia is nothing like Sable envisioned. The students in his class are unruly, his "teacher" has no interest in teaching, the principal willfully breaks academy rules, and it seems like everywhere he turns, Sable finds one more reason to doubt Amadronia's proud legacy.</p>
		<p>Will Sable manage to survive at this clearly dysfunctional academy? Or will he, like so many others, leave Amadronia feeling utterly disillusioned?</p>
	</description>
	<categories>
		<category>Game</category>
	</categories>
	<url type="homepage">https://zetsubou.games</url>
	<url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/koroshiya/mm-flatpak/issues</url>
	<url type="contact">https://twitter.com/ZetsubouGames</url>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">games.zetsubou.SablesGrimoireDemo.desktop</launchable>
	<releases>
		<release version="1.2.0" date="2023-04-07">
			<description>
				<p>Version 1.2.0 is the initial flatpak build</p>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>
	<project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
	<developer_name>Zetsubou Games</developer_name>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image type="source">https://cdn.zetsubou.games/Flatpak/SablesGrimoireDemo/screenshots/1.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image type="source">https://cdn.zetsubou.games/Flatpak/SablesGrimoireDemo/screenshots/2.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image type="source">https://cdn.zetsubou.games/Flatpak/SablesGrimoireDemo/screenshots/3.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image type="source">https://cdn.zetsubou.games/Flatpak/SablesGrimoireDemo/screenshots/4.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image type="source">https://cdn.zetsubou.games/Flatpak/SablesGrimoireDemo/screenshots/5.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1">
		<content_attribute id="sex-nudity">mild</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="sex-themes">mild</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="sex-appearance">mild</content_attribute>
	</content_rating>
</component>
