<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.grisbi.Grisbi</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Grisbi</name>
  <summary>Personal finances manager</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire de comptabilité personnelle</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Grisbi is a very functional personal financial management program
      with a lot of features: checking, cash and liabilities accounts,
      several accounts with automatic contra entries, several currencies,
      including euro, arbitrary currency for every operation, money
      interchange fees, switch to euro account per account, description
      of the transactions with third parties, categories, sub-categories,
      financial year, notes, breakdown, transfers between accounts, even
      for accounts of different currencies, bank reconciliation, scheduled
      transactions, automatic recall of last transaction for every third
      party, nice and easy user interface, user manual, QIF import/export.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
      Grisbi est un logiciel libre de comptabilité personnelle conçu pour
      vous permettre de classer de façon simple et intuitive vos opérations
      financières, quelles qu’elles soient, afin de pouvoir les exploiter au
      mieux en fonction de vos besoins.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
      Grisbi a pris le parti de la simplicité et de l’efficacité pour un usage
      de base, sans toutefois exclure la sophistication nécessaire à un usage
      plus avancé. Les fonctionnalités futures tenteront toujours de respecter
      ces critères.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source" width="1039" height="725">http://grisbi.org/public/Screenshots/screnshot-grisbi1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source" width="1039" height="725">http://grisbi.org/public/Screenshots/screnshot-ib.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source" width="1039" height="725">http://grisbi.org/public/Screenshots/screnshot-report.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://grisbi.org/</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.grisbi.Grisbi.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.0.5" date="2021-08-31">
      <artifacts>
        <artifact type="source">
          <location>http://downloads.sourceforge.net/project/grisbi/grisbi%20stable/2.0.x/2.0.5/grisbi-2.0.5.tar.bz2</location>
          <checksum type="sha256">bd3adbabfc4b4dfc05eff62d2b36458a24b0f00d07cf35a29f6af2f203c77a3f</checksum>
        </artifact>
      </artifacts>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
