<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>io.github.chris2511.xca</id>
    <name>XCA</name>
    <summary>X Certificate and Key management</summary>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://github.com/chris2511/xca/raw/master/COPYRIGHT</project_license>
    <provides>
        <binary>xca</binary>
    </provides>
    <description>
        <p>
            XCA is intended for creating and managing X.509 certificates, certificate requests, RSA, DSA and EC private keys, Smartcards and CRLs.
            Everything that is needed for a CA is implemented.
            All CAs can sign sub-CAs recursively. These certificate chains are shown clearly.
            For an easy company-wide use there are customiseable templates that can be used for certificate or request generation.
        </p>
        Features
        <ul>
            <li>Start your own PKI and create all kinds of private keys, certificates, requests or CRLs</li>
            <li>Import and export them in any format like PEM, DER, PKCS#7, PKCS#12</li>
            <li>Use them for your IPsec, OpenVPN, TLS or any other certificate based setup</li>
            <li>Manage your Smart-Cards via PKCS#11 interface</li>
            <li>Export certificates and requests as OpenSSL config file</li>
            <li>Create Subject- and/or Extension- templates to ease issuing similar certs</li>
            <li>Convert existing certificates or requests to templates</li>
            <li>Get the broad support of x509v3 extensions as flexible as OpenSSL but user friendlier</li>
            <li>Adapt the columns to have your important information at a glance</li>
        </ul>
    </description>
    <developer_name>Christian Hohnstädt, Kerstin Steinhauff et al.</developer_name>
    <releases>
        <release date="2020-04-29" version="2.3.0">
            <ul>
                <li>
                    Close #191 OID LN differs warning popups at startup
                </li>
                <li>
                    Close #189 Database compaction #189
                </li>
                <li>
                    Improve PKCS11 library loading for portable app
                </li>
                <li>
                    Refactor native separators / and \ on windows.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Support TLS encrypted MariaDB and PostgreSQL connection
                </li>
                <li>
                    Close #182: UI not using Windows native theme in 2.2.1 portable
                </li>
                <li>
                    Close #70: cant open ics file in ical on macos mojave
                </li>
                <li>
                    Close #72: Add checkbox for OCSP staple feature
                </li>
                <li>
                    Use DESTDIR instead of destdir when installing. Follows autotools convention.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Close #172 #46: Multiple OCSP Responders
                </li>
                <li>
                    Close #170 xca-portable-2.2.1 cannot change language
                </li>
                <li>
                    Fix certificate assignment when importing a CA certificate
                </li>
                <li>
                    Close #163: Show key type/size on column of Certificates tab
                </li>
            </ul>
        </release>
    </releases>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://www.hohnstaedt.de/xca/images/screenshots/XCA-Screenshot-certs.png</image>
            <image>https://www.hohnstaedt.de/xca/images/screenshots/XCA-Screenshot-keygen.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
    <url type="homepage">https://www.hohnstaedt.de/xca/index.php</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/chris2511/xca/issues</url>
    <url type="help">https://www.hohnstaedt.de/xca/index.php/documentation/manual</url>
</component>
