<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.eclab.edisyn</id>
  <name>Edisyn</name>
  <summary>Synthesizer Patch Editor and Librarian</summary>
  <developer id="io.github.eclab">
    <name>Sean Luke</name>
  </developer>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#c1c1c1ff</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#5a5a5aff</color>
  </branding>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>Edisyn is a synthesizer patch editor library written in pure Java.   It runs on MacOS, Linux, and Windows.</p>
    <p>Edisyn is particularly good at exploring the space of patches.  It has to my knowledge the most sophisticated set of general-purpose patch-exploration tools of any patch editor available.</p>
    <p>Edisyn presently supports:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Alesis D4 and DM5</li>
      <li>ASM Hydrasynth Family (Single mode only)</li>
      <li>Audiothingies Micromonsta</li>
      <li>Casio CZ Series (CZ101, CZ1000, CZ3000, CZ5000, CZ-1, CZ-230S)</li>
      <li>DSI Prophet '08, Tetra, Mopho, Mopho Keyboard, Mopho SE, and Mopho x4 (Single and (for Tetra) Combo modes)</li>
      <li>DSI Prophet 12</li>
      <li>E-Mu Morpheus and Ultraproteus (Single, Hyperpreset, and MidiMap modes)</li>
      <li>E-Mu Planet Phatt, Orbit and Orbit v2, Carnaval, Vintage Keys, and Vintage Keys Plus</li>
      <li>E-Mu Proteus 1, 1XR, 2, 2XR, 3, 3XR, and 1+Orchestral</li>
      <li>E-Mu Proteus 2000 series (Proteus 1000/2000/2500, Virtuoso 2000, Xtreme Lead-1, Mo'Phatt, B-3, Planet Earth, Orbit-3, Proteus Custom, XL-1 Turbo, Turbo Phatt, Vintage Pro, XL-7, MP-7, PX-7, PK-6, XK-6, MK-6, Halo, Vintage Keys Keyboard, and (v2.0) Auditiy 2000.</li>
      <li>JL Cooper MSB+ Rev2</li>
      <li>Kawai K1, Kawai K1m, and Kawai K1r (Single and Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>Kawai K4 and Kawai K4r (Single, Multi, Drum, and Effect Modes)</li>
      <li>Kawai K5 and K5m (Single and Multi Modes, plus single-cycle wave uploading)</li>
      <li>Korg SG Rack and SG Pro X (Single (for SG Rack) and Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>Korg MicroKorg (Single and Vocoder Modes)</li>
      <li>Korg Microsampler</li>
      <li>Korg Wavestation SR (Performance, Patch, and Wave Sequence Modes)</li>
      <li>Korg Volca Series (Joint editor for Bass, Beats, Drum Single, Drum Split, FM, Keys, Kick, NuBass, Sample/Sample2 Multi, Sample2 Single, /u/pajen firmware)</li>
      <li>M-Audio Venom (Single, Multi, Arpeggiator, and Global Modes)</li>
      <li>Novation Drumstation and D Station</li>
      <li>Novation ReMOTE SL, SL MKII, and SL Compact Series</li>
      <li>Oberheim Matrix 6, 6R, and 1000 (Single and (for 1000) Global Modes)</li>
      <li>PreenFM2</li>
      <li>Red Sound DarkStar and DarkStar XP2</li>
      <li>Roland D-110 (Tone and Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>Roland JV-80 and JV-880 (Single, Multi, and Drum Modes)</li>
      <li>Roland U-110</li>
      <li>Roland U-20/U-220 (Single, Multi, and Drum Modes)</li>
      <li>Sequential Prophet Rev2</li>
      <li>Waldorf Blofeld and Waldorf Blofeld Keyboard (Single and Multi Modes, plus Wavetable uploading)</li>
      <li>Waldorf Kyra (Single and Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>Waldorf M</li>
      <li>Waldorf Microwave II, XT, and XTk (Single and Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>Waldorf Pulse 2</li>
      <li>Waldorf Rocket</li>
      <li>Yamaha DX7 Family (DX7, TX7, TX802, TX216/TX816, Korg Volca FM, Dexed, DX200, DX9)</li>
      <li>Yamaha 4-Op FM Family (DX21, DX27, DX100, TX81Z, DX11, TQ5, YS100, YS200, B200, V50, etc.) (Single and (for TX81Z and DX11) Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>Yamaha FB01 (Single and Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>Yamaha FS1R (Voice, Performance, and Fseq Modes)</li>
      <li>Yamaha TG33, SY22, and SY35 (Single and (for TG33) Multi Modes)</li>
      <li>General CC, NRPN, and RPN editing</li>
      <li>Microtuning editing</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Edisyn has infinite levels of undo, CC and NRPN mapping and learning, offline modes, per-parameter customization, real-time parameter updates, test notes and chords, Pseudo-MPE support, and lots more.  Edisyn also has many specialized tools designed to help you explore new patch possibilities without directly programming them.  These include:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>
        <em>Randomization:</em> Weighted patch mutation</li>
      <li>
        <em>Merging:</em> Weighted recombination of two patches of your choice</li>
      <li>
        <em>Mixing:</em> Bulk recombination of many patches into a single one</li>
      <li>
        <em>Blending:</em> Random recombination of two randomly-chosen patches on your synth</li>
      <li>
        <em>Nudging:</em> Pushing the patch to sound a bit more (or a bit less) like one of four other patches of your choice</li>
      <li>
        <em>Morphing:</em> Real-time interpolation of four patches to form a new patch</li>
      <li>
        <em>Hill-Climbing and Constriction:</em> Evolutionary techniques for guided randomized search through the space of parameters, where Edisyn iteratively offers patch possibilities for you to grade, then looks for new ones based on your assessments.</li>
      <li>
        <em>Deep-Learned Models:</em> Improvements to Randomization and Hill-Climbing using a deep-learned Variational Autoencoder neural network (DX7 Family only)</li>
    </ul>

  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Screenshot</caption>
      <image type="source">https://github.com/eclab/edisyn/blob/0f491d143d7d1b30812c87e138efd1b2d1a93b0e/resources/pics/Banner.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="34" date="2024-10-30" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>Version 34 has patch editors for the Waldorf M and Dave Smith Instruments Prophet 12, improvements for the Yamaha DX7 and 4-Op FM families, and improvements for accessibility for the blind.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/eclab/edisyn</url>
  <url type="help">https://cs.gmu.edu/~eclab/projects/edisyn/Edisyn.pdf</url>
  <categories>
    <category>AudioVideo</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>Synthesizer</keyword>
    <keyword>Midi</keyword>
    <keyword>Editor</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <requires>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
  </requires>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.eclab.edisyn.desktop</launchable>
</component>
