<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.pol_rivero.github-desktop-plus</id>
  <name>Desktop Plus</name>
  <summary>GitHub Desktop fork with advanced functionality and Bitbucket integration</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <developer id="io.github.pol_rivero">
    <name>Pol Rivero</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>
      This is a fork of shiftkey's GitHub Desktop port. In addition to being frequently updated
      with the official upstream (desktop/desktop), it has many quality of life improvements and
      advanced features for power users.
    </p>
    <p>
      <p>General:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Red color for destructive action buttons.</li>
        <li>Add icons to some similar-looking buttons for faster visual recognition.</li>
        <li>Allow generating branch name presets by calling an external script (e.g. fetching ticket numbers from an issue tracker).</li>
        <li>Bitbucket integration:
          <ul>
            <li>Preview and create pull requests.</li>
            <li>View pull requests status, including checks.</li>
            <li>Display a commit or PR in Bitbucket (web browser).</li>
            <li>Correctly set repository owner (instead of displaying "Other").</li>
          </ul>
        </li>
      </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
      <p>Repositories list:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Pull all button to fetch and pull from all remotes at once.</li>
        <li>Allow hiding the 'Recent' repositories section.</li>
      </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
      <p>Branches list:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Add warning indicator to local-only branches (branches that are not on the remote).</li>
        <li>Allow manually setting which is the default branch for a repository (even if it doesn't match the one configured in the remote).</li>
      </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
      <p>History tab:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Search commits by title, message, tag, or hash.</li>
        <li>Use a different font style for merge commits in order to make them visually distinct, since most of the time they are not as relevant.</li>
        <li>If a commit modifies only 1 file, allow double-clicking the commit to open the file. For other commits, you can still double-click the file as usual.</li>
      </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
      <p>Changes tab:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Context menu option to permanently discard changes without sending to trash (useful when the there are many changed files and the regular "Discard" is extremely slow).</li>
      </ul>
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/pol-rivero/github-desktop-plus</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.pol_rivero.github-desktop-plus.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pol-rivero/github-desktop-plus/refs/heads/main/docs/assets/flathub/image1.png</image>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pol-rivero/github-desktop-plus/refs/heads/main/docs/assets/flathub/image2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="3.5.2" date="2025-02-24">
      <url>https://github.com/desktop/desktop/releases/tag/release-3.5.2</url>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
