<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.gitlab.Openlyst.doudou</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Doudou</name>
  <summary>Privacy-focused music player for personal media server</summary>
  
  <description>
    <p>
      Your personal music player that puts privacy first. Stream your music collection 
      from your own media server with a beautiful, modern interface that works on all 
      your devices. No tracking, no ads, no cloud services - just your music.
    </p>
    <p>
      Doudou works with popular self-hosted media servers:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Jellyfin - Full support (recommended)</li>
      <li>Plex - Working with limitations</li>
      <li>Subsonic - Full SubSonic API compatibility</li>
      <li>Local Files - Play music directly from your device without any server</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      Key Features:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Zero tracking - No data collection, analytics, or ads</li>
      <li>Beautiful modern interface that adapts to your device</li>
      <li>Gapless playback with smooth crossfades</li>
      <li>Drag-and-drop queue management and radio mode</li>
      <li>High quality audio - Supports MP3, FLAC, AAC, OGG, M4A, WAV, OPUS, and more</li>
      <li>Background playback - Music continues while you use other apps</li>
      <li>Offline listening - Download your favorites for offline playback</li>
      <li>Album artwork from embedded metadata, local images, or online sources</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      Note: This is a preview build (v10.0.0-preview) that has been tested but may 
      contain bugs. Please report any issues on GitLab.
    </p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.gitlab.Openlyst.doudou.desktop</launchable>
  
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.com/Openlyst/doudou</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.com/Openlyst/doudou/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://gitlab.com/Openlyst/doudou/-/discussions</url>
  <url type="donation">https://openlyst.onrender.com/apps/doudou</url>
  
  <developer id="io.gitlab.Openlyst">
    <name>Openlyst</name>
  </developer>
  
  <provides>
    <binary>doudou</binary>
  </provides>
  
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  
  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  
  <categories>
    <category>Audio</category>
    <category>Music</category>
    <category>Player</category>
    <category>AudioVideo</category>
  </categories>
  
  <keywords>
    <keyword>music</keyword>
    <keyword>audio</keyword>
    <keyword>player</keyword>
    <keyword>jellyfin</keyword>
    <keyword>plex</keyword>
    <keyword>subsonic</keyword>
    <keyword>streaming</keyword>
    <keyword>self-hosted</keyword>
    <keyword>privacy</keyword>
    <keyword>media</keyword>
    <keyword>flac</keyword>
    <keyword>mp3</keyword>
  </keywords>
  
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Doudou music player main interface</caption>
      <image>https://gitlab.com/Openlyst/repos/flathub/-/raw/main/image.png?ref_type=heads</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  
  <releases>
    <release version="10.0.0-preview" date="2025-12-18" type="development">
      <description>
        <p>Preview release v10.0.0 - This is a debug build that has been tested but may contain bugs.</p>
        <p>Major new features in this release:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Local Music Support - Play music directly from local filesystem without a media server (MP3, FLAC, WAV, OGG, M4A, AAC, WMA, OPUS, AIFF, ALAC, APE, WEBM)</li>
          <li>Swing Music Server Support - Full support for Swing Music self-hosted servers with JWT authentication</li>
          <li>API Key Authentication for Jellyfin (X-Emby-Token) as alternative to username/password</li>
          <li>Quick Connect support for Jellyfin - login by entering a code from your server dashboard</li>
          <li>Local Playlists - Full playlist support for local music with create, rename, delete, and reorder</li>
          <li>Album Art Service - Fetches artwork from embedded metadata, local images, MusicBrainz, and Cover Art Archive</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Desktop UI improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Complete desktop UI redesign with modern liquid glass aesthetic</li>
          <li>New DesktopTheme system with frosted glass sidebar and gradient effects</li>
          <li>Now Playing album art glow uses dominant color from artwork</li>
          <li>Reusable glass components: DesktopGlassContainer, DesktopPlayButton, DesktopProgressSlider</li>
          <li>New music card components with hover effects and glow</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Bug fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed download button not responding when tapped</li>
          <li>Fixed "Callback invoked after it has been deleted" crash when changing tracks</li>
          <li>Fixed track duration timestamps showing incorrect values</li>
          <li>Fixed Subsonic track durations and favoriting issues</li>
          <li>Fixed local music album art not displaying</li>
          <li>Fixed account login failing after API key authentication attempts</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#4CAF50</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#2E7D32</color>
  </branding>
</component>