<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component>
 <id>io.github.hvdwofl.jExifToolGUI</id>
 <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>MIT</project_license>
 <name>jExifToolGUI</name>
 <summary>Simple frontend for the ExifTool</summary>
 <description>
  <p> jExifToolGUI is a java/Swing Windows/Linux/MacOS graphical frontend for the excellent command-line application called ExifTool by Phil Harvey. 
  </p>
  <p>ExifTool is a platform-independent Perl command-line application and library for reading, writing and editing meta information in a wide variety of files. Exiftool is by far the best and most extensive metadata tool available! It reads and writes metadata information from/to many files, but primarily focuses on photos/images. It reads/writes exif, gps, xmp, maker notes for many cameras, JFIF, GeoTIFF, ICC Profile, Photoshop IRB, FlashPix and many, many more tags. It can use a "reference" image to write the tags to a multiple set of photos or a complete directory containing photos. Author/creator/maintainer of ExifTool: Phil Harvey.
  </p>
  <p>jExifToolGui is a java/Swing program that functions as a graphical frontend (GUI) for exiftool. Many thanks go to Phil Harvey for his excellent tool. Without ExifTool, this jExifToolGui Graphical frontend for ExifTool would never have existed.
  </p>
  <p>jExifToolGui is (just) a graphical frontend for ExifTool. It can use a "reference" image to write the tags to a multiple set of photos, like gps tags for photos that were taken at the same location but somehow miss or contain the incorrect gps info. jExifToolGUI also contains extensive renaming functionality based on the exif info in your photos. This jExifToolGUI program is free, Open Source software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version. 
  </p>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image>https://hvdwolf.github.io/jExifToolGUI/screenshots/Linux-LXDE-mainscreen.jpg</image>
   <caption>jExifToolGUI on GNU/Linux</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image>https://hvdwolf.github.io/jExifToolGUI/screenshots/ExtraMenu.png</image>
   <caption>Extra menus</caption>
  </screenshot>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image>https://hvdwolf.github.io/jExifToolGUI/screenshots/LinuxGeotagging-x600.jpg</image>
   <caption>Geotagging</caption>
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">https://hvdwolf.github.io/jExifToolGUI/</url>
 <update_contact>tobiasmue@gnome.org</update_contact>
</component>

