<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.essentialist_app.essentialist</id>
  
  <name>Essentialist</name>
  <summary>Essentialist is a simple, private, and cross-platform flashcard app designed to make studying and note-taking a seamless process. 🧠</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  
  <description>
    <p>Essentialist is a simple, private, and cross-platform flashcard app designed to make studying and note-taking a seamless process. 🧠</p>
    <p><b>Create Flashcards from Notes</b></p>
    <p>Tired of creating flashcards in a separate app after taking notes? Essentialist makes it easy. Your flashcard decks are just simple Markdown files, which means you can create cards directly while taking notes. This is a perfect workflow for students and anyone who takes notes and wants to quickly turn them into study material. Each card is defined by a simple H2 header (## Your Card Title).</p>
    <p>Because your decks are plain text files, they are:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Easy to manage: You can organize them with any file manager.</li>
      <li>Future-proof: Plain text is a universal format.</li>
      <li>Editable with any editor: Use your favorite text editor to make changes.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Essentialist supports a variety of Markdown features, including lists, tables, emojis, and basic text styling (italic and bold). Please note that image support is not yet available.</p>
    <p><b>Privacy and Simplicity at the Core</b></p>
    <p>We believe your data should stay yours. Essentialist doesn't perform any network operations. It respects your privacy by keeping your data right where it belongs: on your device. There's no cloud, no sync service, and no data collection.</p>
    <p>The app features a minimalist user interface that's distraction-free and helps you focus on your learning. It includes a dark theme for comfortable late-night study sessions and robust keyboard bindings for quick navigation and interaction. For those who prefer the command line, there's also a companion terminal application.</p>
    <p><b>Learn Anywhere, On Any Device</b></p>
    <p>Whether you're on your laptop, desktop, or phone, Essentialist has you covered. It's not just for Linux; it's also available on Windows, macOS, and Android, allowing you to study and review your flashcards in different environments without being locked into a single platform.</p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.essentialist_app.essentialist.desktop</launchable>
  
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>A screenshot of the application</caption>
      <image>https://essentialist.app/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  
  <url type="homepage">https://essentialist.app</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/essentialist-app/essentialist/issues</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/essentialist-app/essentialist</url>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

  <releases>
    <release version="0.3.1" date="2025-08-30">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

</component>
