<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>io.github.junalmeida.webapps_manager</id>
  <icon type="stock">io.github.junalmeida.webapps_manager</icon>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.junalmeida.webapps_manager</launchable>

  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"></content_rating>

  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/junalmeida/webapps_manager</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.0.1" date="2024-12-16">
      <url type="details">https://github.com/junalmeida/webapps_manager/releases/tag/v0.0.1</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Webapps manager QT Ui and Flatpak distribution</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <provides>
    <binary>webapps_manager</binary>
  </provides>
  <developer id="io.github.junalmeida">
    <name>Marcos Junior</name>
  </developer>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/junalmeida/webapps_manager/refs/heads/master/docs/screenshot.png</image>
      <caption>Web Apps Manager screenshot</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <name>Web Apps Manager</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Gestor d'Aplicacions Web</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Správce webových aplikací</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Reteja Aplikaĵa Administrilo</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Gestor de Aplicaciones Web</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Gestionnaire d'Applications Web</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Gestore di Applicazioni Web</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">ウェブアプリケーションマネージャー</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Webapps-beheerder</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Správca webových aplikácií</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Upravitelj spletnih aplikacij</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Webbapplikationshanterare</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Web Uygulama Yöneticisi</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Менеджер веб-додатків</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxWeb Apps Managerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">網頁應用程式管理員</name>
  <summary>Web Apps is a simple tool to manage web applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Web Apps és una eina senzilla per gestionar aplicacions web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Web Apps estas simpla ilo por administri retajn aplikojn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Web Apps es una herramienta sencilla para gestionar aplicaciones web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Web Apps est un outil simple pour gérer les applications web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Web Apps è uno strumento semplice per gestire le applicazioni web</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">Web Appsはウェブアプリケーションを管理するためのシンプルなツールです。</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Web Apps is een eenvoudige tool om webapplicaties te beheren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Web Apps je preprosto orodje za upravljanje spletnih aplikacij</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Web Apps är ett enkelt verktyg för att hantera webbapplikationer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Web Apps, web uygulamalarını yönetmek için basit bir araçtır</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Web Apps - це простий інструмент для управління веб-додатками</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxWeb Apps is a simple tool to manage web applicationsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">Web Apps 是一個管理網頁應用程式的簡單工具。</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Install web apps as desktop applications, so they appear in their own windows and task bar
      icon. I can use an isolated environment of the chosen browser.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Instal·leu aplicacions web com a aplicacions d'escriptori, de manera que
      apareguin a les seves pròpies finestres i icona de la barra de tasques. Puc utilitzar un
      entorn aïllat del navegador escollit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Instalu retajn aplikaĵojn kiel labortablajn aplikojn, tiel ke ili aperu en siaj
      propraj fenestroj kaj taskobreto-ikono. Mi povas uzi izolitan medion de la elektita retumilo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Instale aplicaciones web como aplicaciones de escritorio, para que aparezcan en
      sus propias ventanas e icono de la barra de tareas. Puedo usar un entorno aislado del
      navegador elegido.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Installez des applications web comme des applications de bureau, afin qu'elles
      apparaissent dans leurs propres fenêtres et icône de la barre des tâches. Je peux utiliser un
      environnement isolé du navigateur choisi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Installa applicazioni web come applicazioni desktop, in modo che appaiano nelle
      loro finestre e icona della barra delle applicazioni. Posso utilizzare un ambiente isolato del
      browser scelto.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">
      ウェブアプリケーションをデスクトップアプリケーションとしてインストールし、それらが独自のウィンドウとタスクバーアイコンに表示されるようにします。選択したブラウザの分離された環境を使用できます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Installeer webapps als desktopapplicaties, zodat ze in hun eigen vensters en
      taakbalkpictogram verschijnen. Ik kan een geïsoleerde omgeving van de gekozen browser
      gebruiken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Namestite spletne aplikacije kot namizne aplikacije, tako da se prikažejo v
      svojih oknih in ikoni opravilne vrstice. Uporabim lahko izolirano okolje izbranega brskalnika.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Installera webbapplikationer som skrivbordsapplikationer, så att de visas i
      sina egna fönster och aktivitetsfältets ikon. Jag kan använda en isolerad miljö för den valda
      webbläsaren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Web uygulamalarını masaüstü uygulamaları olarak yükleyin, böylece kendi
      pencerelerinde ve görev çubuğu simgesinde görünürler. Seçilen tarayıcının izole edilmiş bir
      ortamını kullanabilirim.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Встановіть веб-додатки як настільні програми, щоб вони з'являлися у власних
      вікнах та значку панелі завдань. Я можу використовувати ізольоване середовище вибраного
      браузера.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxInstall web apps as desktop applications, so they appear in their own
      windows and task bar icon. I can use an isolated environment of the chosen browser.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">將網頁應用程式安裝為桌面應用程式，使其顯示在自己的窗口和任務欄圖標中。我可以使用所選瀏覽器的隔離環境。</p>
  </description>
</component>