<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>io.itch.Itch</id>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">io.itch.Itch.desktop</launchable>
	<name>itch</name>
	<summary>Install, update and play indie games</summary>
	<url type="homepage">https://itch.io/</url>
	<url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/itchio/itch/issues</url>
	<url type="help">https://itch.io/docs/itch/</url>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>MIT</project_license>
	<description>
		<p>
		The itch.io app, itch, lets you effortlessly download and run games and software from itch.io. All of your downloads are kept in a single place and are automatically updated. Access your collections and purchases, or browse for new games via the in-app browser.
		</p>
		<p>Browse games like the creator intended</p>
		<p>
		On itch.io creators control how their project pages look. The built in browser lets you download and install games while exploring the unique page designs of our creators.
		</p>
		<p>Always updated</p>
		<p>
		Not only will the games you've installed automatically update, the app itself will automatically transform as we launch new functionality and features. Games using our new command line tools will generate delta patches, ensuring that you only download what's changed when new games come out.
		</p>
		<p>Browser games offline</p>
		<p>
		You can sync any browser based games right into the app, letting you play them offline whenever you want. Once you're back online you'll be able to grab any updates if necessary.
    </p>
    <p>Join the community</p>
    <p>
    Learn more about the development of the app in our community. Share feature requests and general feedback with other members of itch.io. If you're a programmer then you'll be glad to hear that the entire project is open source on GitHub, we look forward to your pull requests.
    </p>
    <p>Available in your language</p>
    <p>
    The itch app is available in over 20 languages, thanks to the itch.io community!
    </p>
	</description>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1">
		<content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">moderate</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">moderate</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="violence-realistic">moderate</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">moderate</content_attribute>
		<content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
	</content_rating>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Collections</caption>
			<image>https://static.itch.io/images/app/collections@1x.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>Content browsing</caption>
			<image>https://static.itch.io/images/app/gamepage@1x.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>Offline browser games</caption>
			<image>https://static.itch.io/images/app/html5@1x.png</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<releases>
		<release version="v25.5.1" date="2021-05-12">
			<description>
				<ul>
				  <li>Update to Electron 10.4.5</li>
          <li>Update various dependencies</li>
          <li>App is now signed with itch corp. certificate. (Also updated butler and itch-setup)</li>
          <li>Add physical games as a common filter option</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>
</component>
