<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2012-2019 mpv.io -->
<component type="desktop">
 <id>io.mpv.Mpv</id>
 <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>GPL-2.0+ AND LGPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
 <name>mpv</name>
 <summary>a free, open source, and cross-platform media player</summary>
 <launchable type="desktop-id">io.mpv.Mpv.desktop</launchable>
 <translation type="gettext">mpv</translation>
 <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
 <description>
  <p>
   Mpv is a movie player based on MPlayer and mplayer2. It supports a wide variety
of video file formats, audio and video codecs, and subtitle types. Special
input URL types are available to read input from a variety of sources other
than disk files. Depending on platform, a variety of different video and audio
output methods are supported.
  </p>
  <p>Features:</p>
  <ul>
   <li>Drag and drop playlist</li>
   <li>Loading external configuration files</li>
  </ul>
 </description>
 <releases>
  <release date="2018-10-02" version="0.29.1">
   <description>
    <p>
     This release contains the following changes:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>af_rubberband: Fix for A-V drift on seeking.</li>
      <li>ao_alsa: Fixes to remove spam during pausing and end-of-file.</li>
      <li>ao_jack: Fix for mpv attempting to connect to non-standard devices such as MIDI.</li>
      <li>ao_openal: Drop support for Apple's bundled OpenAL due to lack of features to successfully build.</li>
      <li>ao_pulse: Fix for audio buffer length calculation.</li>
      <li>demux_lavf: Fix EDL playback of certain DASH streams.</li>
      <li>demux_lavf: Mark v4l streams as not seekable.</li>
      <li>demux_raw: Fix for gapless playback from raw audio input.</li>
      <li>drm_atomic: Fix to enable video output with devices without a video overlay plane.</li>
      <li>encode: Fix for crashes in case of failure to write to output.</li>
      <li>encode: Fix for encoding when utilizing lavfi-complex.</li>
      <li>Fix to strip HDR peak metadata if attached to SDR video.</li>
      <li>macOS: Capability to fall back on SW rendering for testing purposes.</li>
      <li>macOS: Fix for issues with the main menu.</li>
      <li>macOS: Fix for side by side split view.</li>
      <li>macOS: Fixes for crashes, most notably those happening on 10.14.</li>
      <li>macOS: No longer let older, unsupported versions of the Swift build tools through configure.</li>
      <li>manpage: Misc fixups.</li>
      <li>stream_{smb,file}: Fix for partial writes to buffers.</li>
      <li>stream_libarchive: Fix hang when an out-of-bound seek happens.</li>
      <li>stream_smb: Fix for crashes due to libsmbclient and threading.</li>
      <li>vo_gpu: Fix for corruption when multiple compute shaders override each others' block sizes.</li>
      <li>ytdl_hook: Always load "ytdl://" URLs with ytdl_hook first.</li>
      <li>ytdl_hook: Fix audio streams not being picked up for some sites.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
     This listing is incomplete. See git log for complete changelog.
    </p>
   </description>
  </release>
 </releases>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image>https://mpv.io/images/mpv-screenshot-34cd36ae.jpg</image>
   <caption>The main window showing the application in action</caption>
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">https://mpv.io/</url>
 <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/mpv-player/mpv/issues</url>
</component>
