<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <id>io.raphamorim.Rio</id>
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>rio</name>
  <summary>A hardware-accelerated GPU terminal emulator powered by WebGPU, focusing to run in desktops and browsers. </summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Rio is a terminal application that's built with Rust, WebGPU, Tokio runtime. It targets to
      have the best frame per second experience as long you want, but is also configurable to use as
      minimal from GPU.
    </p>

    <p>
      The terminal renderer is based on redux state machine, lines that has not updated will not
      suffer a redraw. Looking for the minimal rendering process in most of the time. Rio is also
      designed to support WebAssembly runtime so in the future you will be able to define how a tab
      system will work with a WASM plugin written in your favorite language.
    </p>

    <p>
      Rio uses WGPU, which is an implementation of WebGPU for use outside of a browser and as
      backend for firefox's WebGPU implementation. WebGPU allows for more efficient usage of modern
      GPUs than WebGL.
    </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.raphamorim.Rio.desktop</launchable>

  <url type="homepage">https://raphamorim.io/rio/</url>
  <url type="help">https://raphamorim.io/rio/docs/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/raphamorim/rio/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://github.com/sponsors/raphamorim</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.patreon.com/raphamorim</url>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Navigation under X11 (bottom tabs)</caption>
      <image>https://raphamorim.io/rio/assets/posts/0.0.15/demo-navigation-x11.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Navigation under Wayland (minimal tabs)</caption>
      <image>https://raphamorim.io/rio/assets/posts/0.0.15/demo-navigation-wayland.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Breadcrumbs</caption>
      <video>https://raphamorim.io/rio/assets/features/demo-breadcrumb.png</video>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>High performance renderer</caption>
      <image>https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/1*1enyoIVZivAcHY_kfYXUvQ.gif</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <developer_name>Raphael Amorim</developer_name>

  <releases>
    <release version="v0.0.22" date="2023-10-02">
      <description>
        <p>
          <ul>
            <li>Now you can add extra fonts to load:<br/>
                <pre>
                [fonts]
                extras = [{ family = "Microsoft JhengHei" }]
                </pre></li>
            <li>Added ScrollLineUp, ScrollLineDown, ScrollHalfPageUp, ScrollHalfPageDown, ScrollToTopand ScrollToBottom to bindings.</li>
            <li>Fix japanese characters on Microsoft Windows (Ref: #266).</li>
            <li>Navigation fonts now use the CascadiaCode built-in font and cannot be changed.</li>
            <li>Proper select adapter with is_srgb filter check.</li>
            <li>Switched to queue rendering instead of use staging_belt.</li>
            <li>Fixed leaks whenever buffer dropped map callbacks.</li>
            <li>Forked and embedded glyph-brush project to sugarloaf. Glyph-brush was originally created Alex Butler and is licensed under Apache-2.0 license.</li>
            <li>Upgrate wgpu to 0.17.1.</li>
          </ul>
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
