<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.ulduzsoft.KchmViewer</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>KchmViewer</name>
  <summary>A viewer of CHM (MS-Help) files</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KchmViewer is a reader for CHM (WinHelp) and EPUB files using Qt toolkit with optional KDE support. The main point of kchmviewer is compatibility with non-English CHM files, including most international charsets.</p>
    <p>Some highlights of KchmViewer:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>CHM and EPUB format support</li>
      <li>Standalone viewer, depends on Qt/Webkit only. Optional KDE support</li>
      <li>Tab browsing, built-in search, persistent bookmarks...</li>
      <li>Best multilanguage support; correctly shows non-English chm files, including Cyrillic, Chinese, Japanese and others</li>
      <li>Could be integrated into other apps via DBUS interface</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <developer_name>George Yunaev</developer_name>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://sourceforge.net/p/kchmviewer/bugs</url>
  <url type="donation">https://sourceforge.net/p/kchmviewer/donate</url>
  <url type="faq">http://www.ulduzsoft.com/linux/kchmviewer/frequently-asked-questions</url>
  <url type="help">http://www.ulduzsoft.com/linux/kchmviewer/kchmviewer-integration-reference</url>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.ulduzsoft.com/linux/kchmviewer</url>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Default interface</caption>
      <image>https://screenshots.debian.net/screenshots/000/007/618/large.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>kchmviewer</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.ulduzsoft.KchmViewer.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
    <release version="7.7" date="2016-10-05">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added a hotkey to copy the currently opened URL to clipboard (Ctrl+I).</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.5" date="2015-11-15">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added more useful information into About window.</li>
          <li>Fixed EPUB default encoding to be UTF-8.</li>
          <li>Changed the TOC/Index/Search default click to be single-click, not system-specific.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.4" date="2015-11-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Zoom level is now inherited in newly opened windows.</li>
          <li>Fixed the empty or stale tab names while using the back/forward navigation buttons and new tab options.</li>
          <li>Added -v and --version command-line options.</li>
          <li>Added an option (Settings/Browser/Always use single click) to use a single-click to open tree items in the contents/index tabs despite the selected OS activator such as KDE double-click. Off by default.</li>
          <li>Fixed TOC parsing on some CHM files which had TOC names without associated URLs.</li>
          <li>Disabled encoding selection menu for epubs.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.3" date="2015-02-22">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added X11-specific way to bring the window to front when requested.</li>
          <li>Added search highlighting suggested by Jomart.</li>
          <li>Various KDE build fixes.</li>
          <li>Added an option to disable automatic auto-expansion of Table of Contents entries.</li>
          <li>Fixed the new version check which was triggered on older versions.</li>
          <li>Fixed Qt5 build, it works fine now.</li>
          <li>Fixed settings storage on Qt4/Qt5.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.2" date="2014-12-23">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Ported to Qt5 (but still builds and works with Qt4).</li>
          <li>Added support for 3rd party integration.</li>
          <li>Fixed some minor issues.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.1" date="2014-10-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added support for creating kchmviewer as a portable app.</li>
          <li>Fixed a crash when indexing (in search) certain malformed HTML files.</li>
          <li>Fixed parsing CHM files whose filenames contained URL-encoded characters.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="7.0" date="2014-04-13">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>The 7.0 branch contains significant code changes comparing to previous branches.</li>
          <li>The code has been cleaned up, and certain features were rewritten. No loss in functionality is expected, please report bugs if you experience any.</li>
          <li>Known issues: the search dictionaries will be regenerated again, and some information from the old book configuration from older versions will not be loaded.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
