<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>me.ahmetcetinkaya.whph</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>WHPH • Work Hard Play Hard</name>
  <summary>Productivity app for task management, habit tracking and time optimization</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Görev yönetimi, alışkanlık takibi ve zaman optimizasyonu için uygulama</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Aplikace pro správu úkolů, sledování návyků a optimalizaci času.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Produktivitetsapp til opgavestyring, vanesporring og tidsoptimering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Produktivitäts-App für Aufgaben, Gewohnheiten und Zeitoptimierung.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Διαχείριση εργασιών, συνηθειών και χρόνου.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Productivity app for task management, habit tracking and time optimization</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">App de productividad para gestionar tareas, hábitos y optimizar el tiempo.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Sovellus tehtävien hallintaan, tapojen seurantaan ja ajan optimointiin.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">App de productivité pour gérer les tâches, les habitudes et le temps.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">App per gestire attività, monitorare abitudini e ottimizzare il tempo.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">タスク管理、習慣追跡、時間最適化のための生産性アプリ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">작업 관리, 습관 추적, 시간 최적화를 위한 생산성 앱</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Productiviteitsapp voor taakbeheer, gewoonte tracking en tijdoptimalisatie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="no">Produktivitetsapp for oppgavestyring, vanesporing og tidsoptimalisering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Aplikacja do zarządzania zadaniami, śledzenia nawyków i optymalizacji czasu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Gestão de tarefas, hábitos e otimização de tempo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Aplicație pentru gestionarea sarcinilor, obiceiurilor și optimizarea timpului.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Управление задачами, привычками и временем.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Aplikacija za upravljanje nalog, sledenje navad in optimizacijo časa.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Produktivitetsapp för uppgiftshantering, vanespårning och tidsoptimering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Управління завданнями, звичками та часом.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">用于任务管理、习惯跟踪和时间优化的生产力应用</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      WHPH is a comprehensive productivity app designed to help you manage tasks, develop new habits, and optimize your time. It tracks application usage to enhance focus, allowing you to analyze your progress, celebrate achievements, and stay motivated.
    </p>
    <p>Key Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Task Management: Organize and track your daily tasks efficiently</li>
      <li>Habit Tracking: Build and maintain positive habits with progress monitoring</li>
      <li>Time Optimization: Analyze your time usage patterns and improve productivity</li>
      <li>Application Usage Tracking: Monitor how you spend time on different applications</li>
      <li>Progress Analysis: View detailed insights into your productivity patterns</li>
      <li>Achievement System: Celebrate milestones and stay motivated</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Why Choose WHPH?</p>
    <p>
      WHPH combines multiple productivity tools into one unified experience. Whether you're looking to manage your daily tasks, build better habits, or understand how you spend your time, WHPH provides the insights and tools you need to enhance your productivity and achieve your goals.
    </p>
    <p>
      The app is designed with privacy in mind • all your data stays on your device, giving you complete control over your personal productivity information.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">
      WHPH, görevlerinizi yönetmenize, yeni alışkanlıklar geliştirmenize ve zamanınızı optimize etmenize yardımcı olmak için tasarlanmış kapsamlı bir üretkenlik uygulamasıdır. Odaklanmayı artırmak için uygulama kullanımını takip eder, ilerlemenizi analiz etmenize, başarıları kutlamanıza ve motive kalmanıza olanak tanır.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Temel Özellikler:</p>
    <ul>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Görev Yönetimi: Günlük görevlerinizi verimli bir şekilde organize edin ve takip edin</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Alışkanlık Takibi: İlerleme izleme ile olumlu alışkanlıklar geliştirin ve sürdürün</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Zaman Optimizasyonu: Zaman kullanım kalıplarınızı analiz edin ve üretkenliği artırın</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Uygulama Kullanım Takibi: Farklı uygulamalarda zamanınızı nasıl geçirdiğinizi izleyin</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">İlerleme Analizi: Üretkenlik kalıplarınız hakkında detaylı içgörüler görüntüleyin</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Başarı Sistemi: Kilometre taşlarını kutlayın ve motive kalın</li>
    </ul>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Neden WHPH'yi Seçmelisiniz?</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">
      WHPH, birden fazla üretkenlik aracını tek bir birleşik deneyimde birleştirir. Günlük görevlerinizi yönetmek, daha iyi alışkanlıklar geliştirmek veya zamanınızı nasıl geçirdiğinizi anlamak istiyorsanız, WHPH üretkenliğinizi artırmak ve hedeflerinize ulaşmak için ihtiyacınız olan içgörüleri ve araçları sağlar.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">
      Uygulama gizlilik gözetilerek tasarlanmıştır • tüm verileriniz cihazınızda kalır ve kişisel üretkenlik bilgileriniz üzerinde tam kontrol sahibi olursunuz.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">WHPH je komplexní aplikace pro produktivitu navržená tak, aby vám pomohla spravovat úkoly, rozvíjet nové návyky a optimalizovat váš čas. Sleduje používání aplikací pro zlepšení soustředění, umožňuje analyzovat váš pokrok, slavit úspěchy a zůstat motivovaní. Klíčové funkce: Správa úkolů: Efektivně organizujte a sledujte své denní úkoly Sledování návyků: Budujte a udržujte pozitivní návyky s monitorováním pokroku Optimalizace času: Analyzujte vzorce využití času a zlepšete produktivitu Sledování používání aplikací: Monitorujte, jak trávíte čas v různých aplikacích Analýza pokroku: Prohlížejte si podrobné poznatky o vašich vzorcích produktivity Systém úspěchů: Oslavujte milníky a zůstaňte motivovaní Proč si vybrat WHPH? WHPH kombinuje více nástrojů produktivity do jednoho sjednoceného zážitku. Ať už chcete spravovat své denní úkoly, budovat lepší návyky nebo pochopit, jak trávíte svůj čas, WHPH poskytuje poznatky a nástroje, které potřebujete ke zvýšení produktivity a dosažení svých cílů. Aplikace je navržena s ohledem na soukromí • všechna vaše data zůstávají na vašem zařízení, což vám dává úplnou kontrolu nad vašimi osobními informacemi o produktivitě. Podporované platformy: Android Windows Linux Začněte svou cestu k lepší produktivitě ještě dnes s WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">WHPH er en omfattende produktivitetsapp designet til at hjælpe dig med at administrere opgaver, udvikle nye vaner og optimere din tid. Den sporer applikationsbrug for at forbedre fokus, hvilket giver dig mulighed for at analysere dine fremskridt, fejre præstationer og forblive motiveret. Nøglefunktioner: Opgavestyring: Organiser og spor dine daglige opgaver effektivt Vanesporring: Byg og vedligehold positive vaner med fremskridtsovervågning Tidsoptimering: Analyser dine tidsmønstre og forbedr produktiviteten Applikationsbrugssporing: Overvåg hvordan du bruger tid på forskellige applikationer Fremskridtsanalyse: Se detaljerede indsigter i dine produktivitetsmønstre Præstationssystem: Fejr milepæle og forbliv motiveret Hvorfor vælge WHPH? WHPH kombinerer flere produktivitetsværktøjer i én samlet oplevelse. Uanset om du ønsker at administrere dine daglige opgaver, bygge bedre vaner eller forstå hvordan du bruger din tid, giver WHPH de indsigter og værktøjer du har brug for til at forbedre din produktivitet og nå dine mål. Appen er designet med privatliv i tankerne • alle dine data forbliver på din enhed, hvilket giver dig fuld kontrol over dine personlige produktivitetsoplysninger. Understøttede platforme: Android Windows Linux Start din rejse mod bedre produktivitet i dag med WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">WHPH ist eine umfassende Produktivitäts-App, die Ihnen hilft, Aufgaben zu verwalten, neue Gewohnheiten zu entwickeln und Ihre Zeit zu optimieren. Sie verfolgt die Anwendungsnutzung, um den Fokus zu verbessern, und ermöglicht es Ihnen, Ihren Fortschritt zu analysieren, Erfolge zu feiern und motiviert zu bleiben. Hauptfunktionen: Aufgabenverwaltung: Organisieren und verfolgen Sie Ihre täglichen Aufgaben effizient Gewohnheitsverfolgung: Bauen Sie positive Gewohnheiten auf und erhalten Sie sie mit Fortschrittsüberwachung Zeitoptimierung: Analysieren Sie Ihre Zeitnutzungsmuster und verbessern Sie die Produktivität Anwendungsnutzungsverfolgung: Überwachen Sie, wie Sie Zeit in verschiedenen Anwendungen verbringen Fortschrittsanalyse: Betrachten Sie detaillierte Einblicke in Ihre Produktivitätsmuster Erfolgssystem: Feiern Sie Meilensteine und bleiben Sie motiviert Warum WHPH wählen? WHPH kombiniert mehrere Produktivitätstools in einer einheitlichen Erfahrung. Ob Sie Ihre täglichen Aufgaben verwalten, bessere Gewohnheiten aufbauen oder verstehen möchten, wie Sie Ihre Zeit verbringen • WHPH bietet die Einblicke und Tools, die Sie benötigen, um Ihre Produktivität zu steigern und Ihre Ziele zu erreichen. Die App wurde mit Datenschutz im Hinterkopf entwickelt • alle Ihre Daten bleiben auf Ihrem Gerät und geben Ihnen vollständige Kontrolle über Ihre persönlichen Produktivitätsinformationen. Unterstützte Plattformen: Android Windows Linux Beginnen Sie noch heute Ihre Reise zu besserer Produktivität mit WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το WHPH είναι μια ολοκληρωμένη εφαρμογή παραγωγικότητας σχεδιασμένη να σας βοηθήσει να διαχειρίζεστε εργασίες, να αναπτύσσετε νέες συνήθειες και να βελτιστοποιείτε τον χρόνο σας. Παρακολουθεί τη χρήση εφαρμογών για να ενισχύσει την εστίαση, επιτρέποντάς σας να αναλύετε την πρόοδό σας, να γιορτάζετε επιτεύγματα και να παραμένετε παρακινημένοι. Βασικά Χαρακτηριστικά: Διαχείριση Εργασιών: Οργανώστε και παρακολουθήστε τις καθημερινές σας εργασίες αποτελεσματικά Παρακολούθηση Συνηθειών: Δημιουργήστε και διατηρήστε θετικές συνήθειες με παρακολούθηση προόδου Βελτιστοποίηση Χρόνου: Αναλύστε τα μοτίβα χρήσης του χρόνου σας και βελτιώστε την παραγωγικότητα Παρακολούθηση Χρήσης Εφαρμογών: Παρακολουθήστε πώς περνάτε χρόνο σε διαφορετικές εφαρμογές Ανάλυση Προόδου: Δείτε λεπτομερείς πληροφορίες για τα μοτίβα παραγωγικότητάς σας Σύστημα Επιτευγμάτων: Γιορτάστε ορόσημα και παραμείνετε παρακινημένοι Γιατί να Επιλέξετε το WHPH; Το WHPH συνδυάζει πολλαπλά εργαλεία παραγωγικότητας σε μια ενοποιημένη εμπειρία. Είτε θέλετε να διαχειρίζεστε τις καθημερινές σας εργασίες, να δημιουργήσετε καλύτερες συνήθειες ή να κατανοήσετε πώς περνάτε τον χρόνο σας, το WHPH παρέχει τις πληροφορίες και τα εργαλεία που χρειάζεστε για να ενισχύσετε την παραγωγικότητά σας και να επιτύχετε τους στόχous σας. Η εφαρμογή είναι σχεδιασμένη με γνώμονα την ιδιωτικότητα • όλα τα δεδομένα σας παραμένουν στη συσκευή σας, δίνοντάς σας πλήρη έλεγχο των προσωπικών σας πληροφοριών παραγωγικότητας. Υποστηριζόμενες Πλατφόρμες: Android Windows Linux Ξεκινήστε το ταξίδι σας προς καλύτερη παραγωγικότητα σήμερα με το WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">WHPH is a comprehensive productivity app designed to help you manage tasks, develop new habits, and optimize your time. It tracks application usage to enhance focus, allowing you to analyze your progress, celebrate achievements, and stay motivated. Key Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Task Management: Organize and track your daily tasks efficiently</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Habit Tracking: Build and maintain positive habits with progress monitoring</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Time Optimization: Analyze your time usage patterns and improve productivity</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Application Usage Tracking: Monitor how you spend time on different applications</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Progress Analysis: View detailed insights into your productivity patterns</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Achievement System: Celebrate milestones and stay motivated Why Choose WHPH? WHPH combines multiple productivity tools into one unified experience. Whether you're looking to manage your daily tasks, build better habits, or understand how you spend your time, WHPH provides the insights and tools you need to enhance your productivity and achieve your goals. The app is designed with privacy in mind • all your data stays on your device, giving you complete control over your personal productivity information. Supported Platforms:</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Android</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Windows</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Linux Start your journey to better productivity today with WHPH!</li>
    </ul>
    <p xml:lang="es">WHPH es una aplicación de productividad integral diseñada para ayudarte a gestionar tareas, desarrollar nuevos hábitos y optimizar tu tiempo. Rastrea el uso de aplicaciones para mejorar el enfoque, permitiéndote analizar tu progreso, celebrar logros y mantenerte motivado. Características principales: Gestión de tareas: Organiza y rastrea tus tareas diarias eficientemente Seguimiento de hábitos: Construye y mantén hábitos positivos con monitoreo de progreso Optimización del tiempo: Analiza tus patrones de uso del tiempo y mejora la productividad Seguimiento de uso de aplicaciones: Monitorea cómo pasas tiempo en diferentes aplicaciones Análisis de progreso: Ve insights detallados sobre tus patrones de productividad Sistema de logros: Celebra hitos y mantente motivado ¿Por qué elegir WHPH? WHPH combina múltiples herramientas de productividad en una experiencia unificada. Ya sea que busques gestionar tus tareas diarias, construir mejores hábitos o entender cómo pasas tu tiempo, WHPH proporciona los insights y herramientas que necesitas para mejorar tu productividad y lograr tus objetivos. La aplicación está diseñada con la privacidad en mente • todos tus datos permanecen en tu dispositivo, dándote control completo sobre tu información de productividad personal. Plataformas soportadas: Android Windows Linux ¡Comienza tu viaje hacia una mejor productividad hoy con WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">WHPH on kattava tuottavuussovellus, joka on suunniteltu auttamaan sinua hallitsemaan tehtäviä, kehittämään uusia tapoja ja optimoimaan aikaasi. Se seuraa sovellusten käyttöä parantaakseen keskittymistä, antaen sinun analysoida edistymistäsi, juhlia saavutuksia ja pysyä motivoituneena. Tärkeimmät Ominaisuudet: Tehtävien Hallinta: Järjestä ja seuraa päivittäisiä tehtäviäsi tehokkaasti Tapojen Seuranta: Rakenna ja ylläpidä positiivisia tapoja edistymisen seurannalla Ajan Optimointi: Analysoi aikankäyttömalleja ja paranna tuottavuutta Sovellusten Käytön Seuranta: Seuraa, miten käytät aikaa eri sovelluksissa Edistymisen Analyysi: Katso yksityiskohtaisia näkemyksiä tuottavuusmalleistasi Saavutusjärjestelmä: Juhli virstanpylväitä ja pysy motivoituneena Miksi Valita WHPH? WHPH yhdistää useita tuottavuustyökaluja yhteen yhdistettyyn kokemukseen. Halusitpa hallita päivittäisiä tehtäviäsi, rakentaa parempia tapoja tai ymmärtää, miten käytät aikaasi, WHPH tarjoaa tiedot ja työkalut, joita tarvitset tuottavuutesi parantamiseen ja tavoitteidesi saavuttamiseen. Sovellus on suunniteltu yksityisyys mielessä • kaikki tietosi pysyvät laitteessasi, antaen sinulle täyden kontrollin henkilökohtaisista tuottavuustiedoistasi. Tuetut Alustat: Android Windows Linux Aloita matkasi kohti parempaa tuottavuutta tänään WHPH:n kanssa!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">WHPH est une application de productivité complète conçue pour vous aider à gérer les tâches, développer de nouvelles habitudes et optimiser votre temps. Elle suit l'utilisation des applications pour améliorer la concentration, vous permettant d'analyser vos progrès, célébrer les réussites et rester motivé. Fonctionnalités clés : Gestion des tâches : Organisez et suivez vos tâches quotidiennes efficacement Suivi des habitudes : Construisez et maintenez des habitudes positives avec surveillance des progrès Optimisation du temps : Analysez vos modèles d'utilisation du temps et améliorez la productivité Suivi d'utilisation d'applications : Surveillez comment vous passez du temps sur différentes applications Analyse des progrès : Visualisez des insights détaillés sur vos modèles de productivité Système de réussite : Célébrez les étapes importantes et restez motivé Pourquoi choisir WHPH ? WHPH combine plusieurs outils de productivité en une expérience unifiée. Que vous cherchiez à gérer vos tâches quotidiennes, construire de meilleures habitudes ou comprendre comment vous passez votre temps, WHPH fournit les insights et outils dont vous avez besoin pour améliorer votre productivité et atteindre vos objectifs. L'application est conçue avec la confidentialité à l'esprit • toutes vos données restent sur votre appareil, vous donnant un contrôle complet sur vos informations de productivité personnelles. Plateformes supportées : Android Windows Linux Commencez votre voyage vers une meilleure productivité dès aujourd'hui avec WHPH !</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">WHPH è un'app di produttività completa progettata per aiutarti a gestire attività, sviluppare nuove abitudini e ottimizzare il tuo tempo. Traccia l'utilizzo delle applicazioni per migliorare la concentrazione, permettendoti di analizzare i tuoi progressi, celebrare i risultati e rimanere motivato. Caratteristiche Principali: Gestione Attività: Organizza e traccia le tue attività quotidiane in modo efficiente Tracciamento Abitudini: Costruisci e mantieni abitudini positive con monitoraggio dei progressi Ottimizzazione del Tempo: Analizza i tuoi modelli di utilizzo del tempo e migliora la produttività Tracciamento Utilizzo Applicazioni: Monitora come trascorri il tempo su diverse applicazioni Analisi dei Progressi: Visualizza insights dettagliati sui tuoi modelli di produttività Sistema di Risultati: Celebra i traguardi e rimani motivato Perché Scegliere WHPH? WHPH combina molteplici strumenti di produttività in un'esperienza unificata. Che tu stia cercando di gestire le tue attività quotidiane, costruire abitudini migliori o capire come trascorri il tuo tempo, WHPH fornisce gli insights e gli strumenti di cui hai bisogno per migliorare la tua produttività e raggiungere i tuoi obiettivi. L'app è progettata pensando alla privacy • tutti i tuoi dati rimangono sul tuo dispositivo, dandoti il controllo completo sulle tue informazioni personali di produttività. Piattaforme Supportate: Android Windows Linux Inizia il tuo viaggio verso una migliore produttività oggi con WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">WHPHは、タスクの管理、新しい習慣の開発、時間の最適化を支援するために設計された包括的な生産性アプリです。集中力を向上させるためにアプリケーションの使用状況を追跡し、進歩を分析し、成果を祝い、モチベーションを維持することができます。 主な機能： タスク管理： 日々のタスクを効率的に整理・追跡 習慣追跡： 進歩監視でポジティブな習慣を構築・維持 時間最適化： 時間使用パターンを分析し、生産性を向上 アプリケーション使用状況追跡： 異なるアプリケーションでの時間の使い方を監視 進歩分析： 生産性パターンの詳細な洞察を表示 達成システム： マイルストーンを祝い、モチベーションを維持 なぜWHPHを選ぶのか？ WHPHは複数の生産性ツールを一つの統一された体験に組み合わせます。日々のタスクを管理したい、より良い習慣を構築したい、または時間の使い方を理解したい場合でも、WHPHは生産性を向上させ、目標を達成するために必要な洞察とツールを提供します。 このアプリはプライバシーを念頭に置いて設計されています • すべてのデータはデバイスに保存され、個人の生産性情報を完全にコントロールできます。 サポートされているプラットフォーム： Android Windows Linux 今日からWHPHでより良い生産性への旅を始めましょう！</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">WHPH는 작업 관리, 새로운 습관 개발, 시간 최적화를 도와주도록 설계된 포괄적인 생산성 앱입니다. 집중력을 향상시키기 위해 애플리케이션 사용량을 추적하여 진행 상황을 분석하고, 성취를 축하하며, 동기를 유지할 수 있습니다. 주요 기능: 작업 관리: 일일 작업을 효율적으로 정리하고 추적 습관 추적: 진행 상황 모니터링으로 긍정적인 습관을 구축하고 유지 시간 최적화: 시간 사용 패턴을 분석하고 생산성 향상 애플리케이션 사용량 추적: 다양한 애플리케이션에서 시간을 어떻게 보내는지 모니터링 진행 상황 분석: 생산성 패턴에 대한 상세한 통찰력 제공 성취 시스템: 이정표를 축하하고 동기 유지 왜 WHPH를 선택해야 할까요? WHPH는 여러 생산성 도구를 하나의 통합된 경험으로 결합합니다. 일일 작업을 관리하거나, 더 나은 습관을 구축하거나, 시간을 어떻게 보내는지 이해하고 싶든, WHPH는 생산성을 향상시키고 목표를 달성하는 데 필요한 통찰력과 도구를 제공합니다. 이 앱은 개인정보 보호를 염두에 두고 설계되었습니다 • 모든 데이터가 기기에 저장되어 개인 생산성 정보를 완전히 통제할 수 있습니다. 지원되는 플랫폼: Android Windows Linux 오늘부터 WHPH로 더 나은 생산성을 향한 여정을 시작하세요!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">WHPH is een uitgebreide productiviteitsapp ontworpen om je te helpen taken te beheren, nieuwe gewoontes te ontwikkelen en je tijd te optimaliseren. Het volgt app-gebruik om focus te verbeteren, waardoor je je voortgang kunt analyseren, prestaties kunt vieren en gemotiveerd kunt blijven. Belangrijkste Functies: Taakbeheer: Organiseer en volg je dagelijkse taken efficiënt Gewoontetracking: Bouw en onderhoud positieve gewoontes met voortgangsmonitoring Tijdoptimalisatie: Analyseer je tijdgebruikpatronen en verbeter productiviteit App-gebruiktracking: Monitor hoe je tijd besteedt aan verschillende applicaties Voortgangsanalyse: Bekijk gedetailleerde inzichten in je productiviteitspatronen Prestatie systeem: Vier mijlpalen en blijf gemotiveerd Waarom WHPH Kiezen? WHPH combineert meerdere productiviteitstools in één uniforme ervaring. Of je nu je dagelijkse taken wilt beheren, betere gewoontes wilt ontwikkelen, of wilt begrijpen hoe je je tijd besteedt, WHPH biedt de inzichten en tools die je nodig hebt om je productiviteit te verbeteren en je doelen te bereiken. De app is ontworpen met privacy in gedachten • al je gegevens blijven op je apparaat, waardoor je volledige controle hebt over je persoonlijke productiviteitsinformatie. Ondersteunde Platforms: Android Windows Linux Begin vandaag je reis naar betere productiviteit met WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="no">WHPH er en omfattende produktivitetsapp designet for å hjelpe deg med å administrere oppgaver, utvikle nye vaner og optimalisere tiden din. Den sporer applikasjonsbruk for å forbedre fokus, slik at du kan analysere fremgangen din, feire prestasjoner og holde deg motivert.</p>
    <p xml:lang="no">Hovedfunksjoner:</p>
    <ul>
      <li xml:lang="no">Oppgavestyring: Organiser og spor dine daglige oppgaver effektivt</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Vanesporing: Bygg og oppretthold positive vaner med fremdriftsovervåking</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Tidsoptimalisering: Analyser tidsmønstre og forbedre produktiviteten</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Applikasjonsbrukssporing: Overvåk hvordan du bruker tid på forskjellige applikasjoner</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Fremdriftsanalyse: Se detaljert innsikt i produktivitetsmønstrene dine</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Prestasjonssystem: Feir milepæler og hold deg motivert</li>
    </ul>
    <p xml:lang="no">Hvorfor velge WHPH? WHPH kombinerer flere produktivitetsverktøy i én samlet opplevelse. Enten du ønsker å administrere daglige oppgaver, bygge bedre vaner eller forstå hvordan du bruker tiden din, gir WHPH innsikten og verktøyene du trenger for å forbedre produktiviteten og nå målene dine.</p>
    <p xml:lang="no">Appen er designet med personvern i tankene • alle dataene dine forblir på enheten din, noe som gir deg full kontroll over din personlige produktivitetsinformasjon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="no">Støttede plattformer:</p>
    <ul>
      <li xml:lang="no">Android</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Windows</li>
      <li xml:lang="no">Linux</li>
    </ul>
    <p xml:lang="no">Start din reise mot bedre produktivitet i dag med WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">WHPH to kompleksowa aplikacja produktywności zaprojektowana, aby pomóc Ci zarządzać zadaniami, rozwijać nowe nawyki i optymalizować czas. Śledzi użycie aplikacji w celu poprawy koncentracji, umożliwiając analizę postępów, świętowanie osiągnięć i utrzymanie motywacji. Kluczowe Funkcje: Zarządzanie Zadaniami: Organizuj i śledź swoje codzienne zadania efektywnie Śledzenie Nawyków: Buduj i utrzymuj pozytywne nawyki z monitorowaniem postępów Optymalizacja Czasu: Analizuj swoje wzorce użycia czasu i poprawiaj produktywność Śledzenie Użycia Aplikacji: Monitoruj, jak spędzasz czas w różnych aplikacjach Analiza Postępów: Przeglądaj szczegółowe wglądy w swoje wzorce produktywności System Osiągnięć: Świętuj kamienie milowe i utrzymuj motywację Dlaczego Wybrać WHPH? WHPH łączy wiele narzędzi produktywności w jedno ujednolicone doświadczenie. Niezależnie od tego, czy chcesz zarządzać codziennymi zadaniami, budować lepsze nawyki, czy rozumieć, jak spędzasz czas, WHPH zapewnia wglądy i narzędzia potrzebne do poprawy produktywności i osiągnięcia celów. Aplikacja została zaprojektowana z myślą o prywatności • wszystkie Twoje dane pozostają na Twoim urządzeniu, dając Ci pełną kontrolę nad osobistymi informacjami o produktywności. Obsługiwane Platformy: Android Windows Linux Rozpocznij swoją podróż do lepszej produktywności już dziś z WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">WHPH é uma aplicação de produtividade abrangente, concebida para o ajudar a gerir tarefas, desenvolver novos hábitos e otimizar o seu tempo. Monitoriza a utilização de aplicações para melhorar o foco, permitindo-lhe analisar o seu progresso, celebrar conquistas e manter-se motivado.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Principais funcionalidades:</p>
    <ul>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gestão de tarefas: Organize e acompanhe as suas tarefas diárias de forma eficiente</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Rastreamento de hábitos: Construa e mantenha hábitos positivos com monitorização de progresso</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Otimização de tempo: Analise os seus padrões de utilização de tempo e melhore a produtividade</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Monitorização de utilização de aplicações: Acompanhe como passa o tempo em diferentes aplicações</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Análise de progresso: Veja insights detalhados sobre os seus padrões de produtividade</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Sistema de conquistas: Celebre marcos e mantenha-se motivado</li>
    </ul>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Porquê escolher o WHPH? O WHPH combina múltiplas ferramentas de produtividade numa experiência unificada. Quer pretenda gerir as suas tarefas diárias, construir melhores hábitos ou compreender como utiliza o seu tempo, o WHPH fornece os insights e ferramentas necessários para melhorar a sua produtividade e alcançar os seus objetivos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A aplicação foi concebida com a privacidade em mente • todos os seus dados permanecem no seu dispositivo, dando-lhe controlo total sobre as suas informações pessoais de produtividade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Plataformas suportadas:</p>
    <ul>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Android</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Windows</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Linux</li>
    </ul>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Comece hoje a sua jornada para uma melhor produtividade com o WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">WHPH este o aplicație cuprinzătoare de productivitate concepută să vă ajute să gestionați sarcinile, să dezvoltați obiceiuri noi și să vă optimizați timpul. Urmărește utilizarea aplicațiilor pentru a îmbunătăți concentrarea, permițându-vă să vă analizați progresul, să sărbătoriți realizările și să rămâneți motivați. Caracteristici Cheie: Gestionarea Sarcinilor: Organizați și urmăriți eficient sarcinile zilnice Urmărirea Obiceiurilor: Construiți și mențineți obiceiuri pozitive cu monitorizarea progresului Optimizarea Timpului: Analizați modelele de utilizare a timpului și îmbunătățiți productivitatea Urmărirea Utilizării Aplicațiilor: Monitorizați cum petreceți timpul în diferite aplicații Analiza Progresului: Vizualizați informații detaliate despre modelele de productivitate Sistemul de Realizări: Sărbătoriți momentele importante și rămâneți motivați De Ce Să Alegeți WHPH? WHPH combină multiple instrumente de productivitate într-o experiență unificată. Indiferent dacă doriți să vă gestionați sarcinile zilnice, să construiți obiceiuri mai bune sau să înțelegeți cum vă petreceți timpul, WHPH oferă perspectivele și instrumentele de care aveți nevoie pentru a vă îmbunătăți productivitatea și a vă atinge obiectivele. Aplicația este concepută cu confidențialitatea în minte • toate datele dvs. rămân pe dispozitivul dvs., oferindu-vă control complet asupra informațiilor personale de productivitate. Platforme Suportate: Android Windows Linux Începeți călătoria către o productivitate mai bună astăzi cu WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">WHPH (Work Hard Play Hard, круто работай — круто отдыхай) — это комплексное приложение для повышения продуктивности, разработанное для помощи в управлении задачами, развитии новых привычек и оптимизации времени. Оно отслеживает использование приложений для улучшения сосредоточенности, позволяя анализировать прогресс, отмечать достижения и поддерживать мотивацию. Основные возможности: Управление задачами: Эффективно организуйте и отслеживайте свои ежедневные задачи. Отслеживание привычек: Формируйте и поддерживайте полезные привычки с помощью остлеживания продвижения. Оптимизация времени: Анализируйте свои шаблоны использования времени и улучшайте плодотворности. Отслеживание использования приложений: Отслеживайте, как вы проводите время в различных приложениях. Анализ прогресса: Просматривайте подробную информацию для понимания своих шаблонов продуктивности. Система достижений: Отмечайте достижения и сохраняйте мотивацию. Почему стоит выбрать WHPH? WHPH объединяет несколько инструментов для улучшения плодотворности в единый интерфейс. WHPH предоставляет необходимые инструменты и аналитику для повышения плодотворности и достижения целей, независимо от того, хотите ли вы управлять своими повседневными задачами, вырабатывать полезные привычки или понимать, как вы проводите время. Приложение разработано с учётом конфиденциальности — все ваши данные остаются на вашем устройстве, предоставляя вам полный контроль над вашей личной информацией о плодотворности. Поддерживаемые платформы: Android Windows Linux Начните свой путь к повышению плодотворности уже сегодня с WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">WHPH je celovita aplikacija za produktivnost, zasnovana za pomoč pri upravljanju nalog, razvijanju novih navad in optimizaciji vašega časa. Sledi uporabi aplikacij za izboljšanje osredotočenosti, kar vam omogoča analizirati napredek, praznovanje dosežkov in ohranjanje motivacije. Ključne Funkcije: Upravljanje Nalog: Učinkovito organizirajte in sledite svojim dnevnim nalogam Sledenje Navad: Gradite in vzdržujte pozitivne navade z nadzorom napredka Optimizacija Časa: Analizirajte vzorce uporabe časa in izboljšajte produktivnost Sledenje Uporabe Aplikacij: Spremljajte, kako preživljate čas v različnih aplikacijah Analiza Napredka: Oglejte si podrobne vpoglede v vaše vzorce produktivnosti Sistem Dosežkov: Praznujte mejnike in ostanite motivirani Zakaj Izbrati WHPH? WHPH združuje več orodij za produktivnost v eno enotno izkušnjo. Ne glede na to, ali želite upravljati svoje dnevne naloge, graditi boljše navade ali razumeti, kako preživljate svoj čas, WHPH zagotavlja vpoglede in orodja, ki jih potrebujete za izboljšanje produktivnosti in doseganje ciljev. Aplikacija je zasnovana z mislijo na zasebnost • vsi vaši podatki ostanejo na vaši napravi, kar vam daje popoln nadzor nad vašimi osebnimi informacijami o produktivnosti. Podprte Platforme: Android Windows Linux Začnite svojo pot k boljši produktivnosti danes z WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">WHPH är en omfattande produktivitetsapp designad för att hjälpa dig hantera uppgifter, utveckla nya vanor och optimera din tid. Den spårar appanvändning för att förbättra fokus, vilket gör det möjligt för dig att analysera dina framsteg, fira prestationer och hålla dig motiverad. Nyckelfunktioner: Uppgiftshantering: Organisera och spåra dina dagliga uppgifter effektivt Vanespårning: Bygg och underhåll positiva vanor med framstegsspårning Tidsoptimering: Analysera dina tidsanvändningsmönster och förbättra produktivitet Appanvändningsspårning: Övervaka hur du spenderar tid i olika applikationer Framstegsanalys: Se detaljerade insikter om dina produktivitetsmönster Prestationssystem: Fira milstolpar och håll dig motiverad Varför Välja WHPH? WHPH kombinerar flera produktivitetsverktyg i en enhetlig upplevelse. Oavsett om du vill hantera dina dagliga uppgifter, bygga bättre vanor eller förstå hur du spenderar din tid, ger WHPH de insikter och verktyg du behöver för att förbättra din produktivitet och uppnå dina mål. Appen är designad med integritet i åtanke • all din data stannar på din enhet, vilket ger dig fullständig kontroll över din personliga produktivitetsinformation. Stödda Plattformar: Android Windows Linux Börja din resa mot bättre produktivitet idag med WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">WHPH • це комплексний додаток продуктивності, розроблений для допомоги в управлінні завданнями, розвитку нових звичок та оптимізації вашого часу. Він відстежує використання додатків для покращення концентрації, дозволяючи аналізувати ваш прогрес, святкувати досягнення та залишатися мотивованими. Ключові Функції: Управління Завданнями: Ефективно організовуйте та відстежуйте ваші щоденні завдання Відстеження Звичок: Будуйте та підтримуйте позитивні звички з моніторингом прогресу Оптимізація Часу: Аналізуйте шаблони використання часу та покращуйте продуктивність Відстеження Використання Додатків: Моніторте, як ви проводите час у різних додатках Аналіз Прогресу: Переглядайте детальні відомості про ваші шаблони продуктивності Система Досягнень: Святкуйте віхи та залишайтеся мотивованими Чому Обрати WHPH? WHPH поєднує кілька інструментів продуктивності в один уніфікований досвід. Незалежно від того, чи хочете ви управляти своїми щоденними завданнями, будувати кращі звички або розуміти, як ви проводите свій час, WHPH надає розуміння та інструменти, необхідні для покращення вашої продуктивності та досягнення ваших цілей. Додаток розроблений з урахуванням приватності • всі ваші дані залишаються на вашому пристрої, надаючи вам повний контроль над вашою особистою інформацією про продуктивність. Підтримувані Платформи: Android Windows Linux Почніть свою подорож до кращої продуктивності сьогодні з WHPH!</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">WHPH 是一个旨在帮助您管理任务、培养新习惯和优化时间的综合生产力应用。它跟踪应用程序使用情况以增强专注力，让您能够分析进展、庆祝成就并保持动力。 主要功能： 任务管理： 高效地组织和跟踪您的日常任务 习惯跟踪： 通过进度监控建立和维持积极习惯 时间优化： 分析您的时间使用模式并提高生产力 应用程序使用跟踪： 监控您在不同应用程序上花费的时间 进度分析： 查看生产力模式的详细洞察 成就系统： 庆祝里程碑并保持动力 为什么选择 WHPH？ WHPH 将多个生产力工具结合到一个统一的体验中。无论您是想管理日常任务、建立更好的习惯，还是了解如何花费时间，WHPH 都能提供提升生产力和实现目标所需的洞察和工具。 该应用在设计时考虑了隐私保护 • 所有数据都存储在您的设备上，让您完全控制个人生产力信息。 支持的平台： Android Windows Linux 今天就开始使用 WHPH 踏上更好生产力的旅程！</p>

  </description>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>Office</category>
  </categories>
  <developer id="me.ahmetcetinkaya">
    <name>Ahmet Cetinkaya</name>
  </developer>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">me.ahmetcetinkaya.whph.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://whph.ahmetcetinkaya.me</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/issues</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph</url>
  <url type="donation">https://ahmetcetinkaya.me/donate</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/5.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/6.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/7.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ahmet-cetinkaya/whph/master/fastlane/metadata/android/en-US/images/phoneScreenshots/8.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.21.1" date="2026-02-13" />
    <release version="0.21.0" date="2026-02-11" />
    <release version="0.20.4" date="2026-01-25" />
    <release version="0.20.3" date="2026-01-22" />
    <release version="0.20.2" date="2026-01-22" />
  </releases>
</component>
