<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>moe.bdim.iCloudMail</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>iCloud Mail</name>
  <summary>Unofficial desktop app for iCloud Mail</summary>

  <description>
    <p>Experience seamless access to your iCloud Mail with this unofficial desktop application. Elevate your email management with a dedicated desktop app that integrates with iCloud, bringing your emails to the forefront of your digital experience.</p>
    <p>Key Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Effortless Email Access: Access your iCloud Mail seamlessly from your desktop. Enjoy a dedicated space for managing your emails, streamlining your communication workflow.</li>
      <li>Desktop Convenience: Embrace the simplicity of a dedicated desktop app. Easily compose, read, and organize your iCloud emails for a focused and efficient email experience.</li>
      <li>Notifications: Stay on top of your inbox with optional notifications for important emails and updates. Receive timely reminders to respond and manage your email communication effectively.</li>
      <li>Context Menu: Full support for copy, paste, cut, undo, redo, zoom, reload and fullscreen operations.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Please Note: This application is an independent project and is not affiliated with or endorsed by Apple Inc. It is designed to enhance the desktop experience for iCloud Mail users.</p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">moe.bdim.iCloudMail.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/bdim404/icloud-mail-flatpak/main/screenshot.jpg</image>
      <caption>iCloud Mail sign in page</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/bdim404/icloud-mail-flatpak</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/bdim404/icloud-mail-flatpak/issues</url>

  <developer_name>Bdim404</developer_name>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">moderate</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2025-10-29">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
    <category>Email</category>
    <category>Office</category>
  </categories>

  <keywords>
    <keyword>mail</keyword>
    <keyword>email</keyword>
    <keyword>icloud</keyword>
    <keyword>apple</keyword>
  </keywords>

  <provides>
    <binary>icloud-mail</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
