<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<releases>
    <release version="1.7.61" date="2026-03-16" urgency="low" type="stable">
        <description>
            <ul>
                <li>Lucky the Leprechaun, just in time for ol' St. Patty's day (Thanks SoK!)</li>
                <li>OS-Font-Rendering now works on Windows, so all languages and emoji should
  render properly (Thanks Claude!).</li>
                <li>OS-Font-Rendering now works on Linux (or other Posix-y platforms like Mac
  homebrew) when Cairo/Pango is detected, so all languages and emoji should
  render properly there too (Thanks Claude!).</li>
                <li>Windows builds now use ANGLE (Almost Native Graphics Layer Engine) instead of
  relying directly on OpenGL. ANGLE is an implementation of OpenGL ES that runs
  on top of Direct3D, which gives us much better support across hardware on
  Windows than we had before.</li>
                <li>Added scenev1 protocol 36, which enables V2 auth for servers. This allows
  servers to receive authenticated V2 account info for all players before they
  are allowed to join and fixes the spoofing vulnerabilities that V1 auth had.
  V2 account ids look like 'a-XXX' whereas old V1 looked like 'pb-XXXX'. The
  default protocol is still 33, but if you are running a server it is highly
  recommended to set your protocol to 36 in your server config to enable this.</li>
                <li>Added `bascenev1.SessionPlayer.get_account_id()`, which supersedes the old
  `get_v1_account_id()`. The new method returns a V1 account id for players
  connected via protocol &lt; 36 and a V2 account id for protocol &gt;= 36.
  `get_v1_account_id()` is now deprecated and will be removed when api 9
  support ends.</li>
                <li>Wired up an http request on the V1 master server you can use to get V2 account
  ids given a V1 account id. You can use this to migrate old account databases
  for V2 auth. https://legacy.ballistica.net/v2id/YOURV1IDHERE</li>
                <li>Clients will now wait for responses for up to 10 seconds when connecting to a
  server and 30 seconds if contact is lost once connected. Hopefully this
  reduces disconnects due to momentary network issues. Holler if this feels like
  too long. Old values were 5 and 10 seconds respectively.</li>
                <li>Improved efficiency of various low level logging calls in the C++ layer
  (Thanks std::string_view!).</li>
                <li>Fixed an issue where clicks could sometimes be lost in the nearby-parties
  browser.</li>
                <li>Fixed party window sub-menus staying after closing the root window.
  (Thanks temp!)</li>
                <li>Add `bascenev1.get_client_ping` which returns the current ping (RTT in ms)
  for a connected client.</li>
                <li>Simplified the Python build process for Android (see
  `efrotools.python_build_android`). For now we're still compiling to a static
  library which has some technical advantages for our use-case over the
  officially-supported many-shared-libraries route. The old build path is still
  in place (labeled '_old') but I'll remove it soon.</li>
                <li>Android Python has been bumped to the latest bug fix release (3.13.12).</li>
                <li>Fixed an issue where the sqlite3 module was not available in Android Python.</li>
                <li>Windows builds will create a .dmp file in the executable directory on crashes,
  which can be useful to send to me to diagnose crash bugs.</li>
                <li>Starting to add some tests of low level C++ stuff (the Object class in this
  case) to make sure it stays in good working order. Do `make test-ex` to see
  that stuff.</li>
                <li>Server with v2-auth enabled now provide verified account-ids of all clients
  in the client-info-lists they send out.</li>
                <li>Added GL debug logging. This can hopefully give us clues if we're doing
  something that doesn't play nicely with certain graphics hardware. To enable
  this, flip logging levels for `ba.gfx` to 'info' or 'debug' in the dev
  console.</li>
                <li>The client now connects to basn (regional) nodes using proper dns names with
  standard public TLS. No more passing around self-signed-certificates and other
  weirdness that is more likely to be blocked at the network level.</li>
                <li>Volume slider values now properly match user expectations. This means 50%
  volume is half as loud as 100%, and lower volumes can now be fine tuned better
  (Thanks TheMikirog!).</li>
                <li>Added support for `datetime.date` values to dataclassio (serialized as
  YYYY-MM-DD strings).</li>
                <li>(build 22759) ANGLE GL rendering on Windows is now properly loading compressed
  textures; previously was using fallback half-res cpu-based decompression which
  is slow and ugly (Thanks SoK for the heads-up).</li>
                <li>You can now use `ba*.app.accounts.primary.request_transient_api_key()` to get
  a temporary api-key for the signed-in account that you can use to call REST
  functions/etc.</li>
                <li>Added experimental support for Python's native REPL which gives us cool
  features like autocompletion, command history, multiline statements and line
  editing(going left/right). This is currently disabled by default but can be
  enabled via the `Use Native Python REPL` config key. (Thanks Loup-Garou911XD!)</li>
                <li>Network connectivity improvements: devices with no UDP connectivity should be
  able to establish connectivity to the master-server (though udp is still
  required for gameplay). Also, establishing connectivity on first launch should
  be substantially faster.</li>
                </ul>
        </description>
        <url>https://github.com/efroemling/ballistica/releases/tag/v1.7.61</url>
        <artifacts>
            <artifact type="source">
                <location>https://github.com/efroemling/ballistica/archive/refs/tags/v1.7.61.tar.gz</location>
                </artifact>
            <artifact type="source" platform="x86_64-linux-gnu">
                <location>https://github.com/efroemling/ballistica/releases/download/v1.7.61/bombsquad_build_env.tar</location>
                <checksum type="sha256">0cb9b58f73e48fd7d64df2b5dbbab2b6e509f3447c37bd00536a5e02532ce28b</checksum>
                </artifact>
        </artifacts>
    </release>
    <release version="1.7.59" date="2026-01-13" urgency="low" type="stable">
        <description>
            <p>This stable release fixes bugs.</p>
            </description>
    </release>
</releases>
