<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>net.sonobus.SonoBus</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">net.sonobus.SonoBus.desktop</launchable>
    <name>SonoBus</name>
    <summary>Free and open source network audio streaming</summary>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
    <description>
        <p>
            SonoBus is an application for streaming high-quality, low-latency peer-to-peer
            audio between devices over the internet or a local network.
        </p>

        <p>
            Features:
            Connects multiple users together to send and receive audio among all in a group,
            with fine-grained control over latency, quality and overall mix. Includes optional
            input compression, noise gate, and EQ effects, along with a master reverb. 
       </p>
            
       <p>     
            All settings are dynamic, network statistics are clearly visible. 
            Works as a standalone application on macOS, Windows, iOS, and GNU/Linux, and as
            an audio plugin (AU, VST, and AAX) on macOS and Windows. Use it on your desktop
            or in your DAW, or on your mobile device.
       </p>
            
       <p>
            Easy to setup and use, yet still provides all the details that audio nerds want to see.
            Audio quality can be instantly adjusted from full uncompressed PCM (16, 24, or 32 bit)
            or with various compressed bitrates (16-256 kbps per channel) using 
            the low-latency Opus codec.
      </p>
    </description>
    <url type="homepage">https://sonobus.net/</url>
    <url type="help">https://groups.google.com/u/1/g/sonobus-users</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/sonosaurus/sonobus/issues</url>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://sonobus.net/assets/images/sonobus_screenshot.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
    <releases>
        <release version="1.4.3" date="2021-04-02">
            <description>
                <p>New features:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Multi-channel (>2) support added.</li>
                    <li>Input Mixer added to control how the inputs are mixed and grouped for sending and for monitoring.</li>
                    <li>Input effects are now per channel as configured by grouping.</li>
                    <li>Full gate/compressor/eq effects now available per user track (and even per channel there if desired)</li>
                    <li>You can route remote users to specific outputs (if you have activated them, or are using the plugin in multi-bus capable host)</li>
                    <li>Can now insert Audio Unit plugin in "instrument" slots so you can get access to multi-bus outputs on hosts like Logic...</li>
                    <li>Added minimal/full view mode choice.</li>
                    <li>Recording filenames now include group name.</li>
                    <li>Added support for MP3 playing on platforms that didn't have it.</li>
                    <li>Initially mute incoming audio of new connections while they are auto-adjusting jitter buffers until stability is achieved.</li>
                    <li>Added Default User Volume level in options (fixed in 1.4.1), </li>
                    <li>Text Chat added, for another way to communicate within a group during a session.</li>
                    <li>Self-monitoring delay (and backing track delay) options to help overcome latency related rhythmic issues.</li>
                    <li>Added Group Latency Match feature</li>
                    <li>Added command line options to start sonobus and immediately connect, or to load a saved setup, along with basic "headless" operation mode for power users.</li>
                    <li>Initial translation support for several languages.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>Enhancements:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Fixed bug when using file playback and recording simultaneously</li>
                    <li>Added return-to-start button for file playback (keybinding is 0)</li>
                    <li>Added Auto Jitter buffer adjust drop rate threshold option</li>
                    <li>Prevent user leave/join messages in chat in public groups</li>
                    <li>Simplified update check download</li>
                    <li>Fixed layout of public group page</li>
                    <li>Updated some visual elements (time sliders, etc)</li>
                    <li>Updated translations</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
  </releases>
</component> 

