<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.waterfoxco.waterfox-g5</id>

  <name>Waterfox</name>
  <summary>A lightweight, free and open source web browser built for the modern web.</summary>

  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MPL-2.0</project_license>

  <developer_name>WaterfoxCo Ltd.</developer_name>

  <categories>
    <category>Internet</category>
    <category>Web Browser</category>
  </categories>

  <description>
    <p>Important: This flatpak is not affiliated with, in any way, WaterfoxCo Ltd., System1, or the
      Mozilla Foundation</p>

    <p> Waterfox gives you a sane way to browse the web. Built with you, the user, in mind.</p>

    <p>Waterfox's Enhanced Tracking Protection safeguards your privacy while you surf. It prevents
      trackers from following you around the internet and collecting data about your browsing habits
      and interests without interfering with site operation. It also protects you from malicious
      programmes like malware that drain your battery.</p>

    <p>Private Browsing does not save your browsing data, such as history or cookies, and does not
      leave a trail once you log out. Waterfox also includes Enhanced Tracking Protection, which
      stops hidden trackers from collecting your data and slowing down your browsing.</p>

    <p>What you do within your browser stays with you. We don't need to know. Telemetry is disabled
      within the browser - and only limited data collection is used to keep your browser up to date
      and secure. Read more in the Privacy Policy.</p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.waterfoxco.waterfox-g5.desktop</launchable>

  <url type="homepage">https://www.waterfox.net/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/waterfoxco/waterfox/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://waterfox.net/support/category/linux</url>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />


  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://github.com/FloridaMan7588/waterfox-flatpak/blob/master/images/screenshot_1.png?raw=true</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/FloridaMan7588/waterfox-flatpak/blob/master/images/screenshot_2.png?raw=true</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/FloridaMan7588/waterfox-flatpak/blob/master/images/screenshot_3.png?raw=true</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="G5.1.2" date="2023-01-17"/>
  </releases>

  <keywords>
    <keyword>internet</keyword>
    <keyword>waterfox</keyword>
    <keyword>browser</keyword>
    <keyword>web</keyword>
  </keywords>
</component>