<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>net.stabyourself.nottetris2</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>CC-BY-NC-SA-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Not Tetris 2</name>
  <summary>Pyisics-based Tetris</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Not Tetris 2 is the spiritual successor of the classic Tetris mixed with physics. The result is a fun spinoff in which blocks are no longer bound to the usual grid. Blocks can be rotated and placed at any angle, resulting in a complete mess if not careful. And with the newest cutting edge technology, Not tetris 2 allows line clears when the lines are sufficiently filled. The old mode is still available for play and is now called Stack.
    </p>
    <p>
      Also in this version is a multiplayer mode that allows up to 2 players on a single computer, with each having their own seperate Stack to fill. In the Invade mode, players can bounce their blocks to their opponent's side and save up on their own space.
    </p>
    <p>
      Features:
      <ul>
        <li>
          <b>It's like Tetris, but it's not:</b> It's got all the upsides of Tetris and all the downsides of physics
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>Clean look:</b> With selectable screen size and color, you can make it as big and as green as you want
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>Nostalgia pure:</b> Remember the Tetris music? Well it is in here too! As well as the other two tracks
        </li>
        <li>
          <b>Fun for Two:</b> Simultaneous head-to-head multiplayer guarantees exciting battles
        </li>
      </ul>
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://stabyourself.net/images/screenshots/nottetris2-1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://stabyourself.net/images/screenshots/nottetris2-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://stabyourself.net/images/screenshots/nottetris2-3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://stabyourself.net/images/screenshots/nottetris2-4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>http://stabyourself.net/images/screenshots/nottetris2-5.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">http://stabyourself.net/nottetris2/</url>
  <update_contact>flathub.org</update_contact>
</component>
