<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <!--Created with jdAppStreamEdit 9.1-->
  <id>net.tangysoft.usenext</id>
  <name>UseNeXt</name>
  <summary>Usenext Usenet reader</summary>
  <developer id="net.tangysoft">
    <name>Tangysoft</name>
  </developer>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <update_contact>tobiasmue@gnome.org</update_contact>
  <description>
    <p>Tangysoft Usenet Client is a streamlined, user-friendly software designed to access and interact with Usenet newsgroups. Usenet, one of the oldest and most enduring parts of the internet, offers a vast range of discussion forums on topics from technology to hobbies, and even niche interests. The Tangysoft Usenet Client provides an intuitive interface for users to explore these newsgroups, read messages, post content, and engage in discussions.</p>
    <p>One of the standout features of Tangysoft's client is its emphasis on ease of use, making it accessible for both beginners and more experienced Usenet users. The client boasts a clean, well-organized layout with a minimal learning curve, ensuring that users can quickly navigate between newsgroups, search for specific topics, and manage their subscriptions. The software supports advanced functions, such as threaded conversations, efficient message filtering, and quick access to popular newsgroups, all while maintaining a simple, straightforward user experience.</p>
    <p>In addition to its usability, Tangysoft's Usenet Client supports advanced features necessary for power users. This includes integration with popular Usenet servers, full-text search capabilities, and the ability to handle large volumes of posts efficiently. The client is designed with performance in mind, ensuring smooth scrolling, quick loading of content, and minimal lag when navigating through extensive message threads.</p>
    <p>For those who wish to participate in Usenet's rich history of binary file sharing, the Tangysoft Usenet Client also supports the downloading of binary files, including images, videos, and software packages. The client handles multipart files and includes built-in features to assist with file management, ensuring a seamless experience for users who regularly download or share files via newsgroups.</p>
    <p>Overall, the Tangysoft Usenet Client is an excellent choice for anyone looking to dive into the world of Usenet, offering a balanced combination of user-friendly design and powerful features. Whether you're a casual user browsing discussions or an experienced participant downloading large files, Tangysoft provides a reliable, efficient platform to meet your needs.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>The main app window showing access to the Usenet</caption>
      <image type="source">https://www.tangysoft.net/img/zoomout_image.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="5.6.2" date="2013-10-21" type="stable"/>
  </releases>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.tangysoft.net/</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">usenext.desktop</launchable>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>usenet</keyword>
    <keyword>usenext</keyword>
  </keywords>
</component>
