<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>net.nymtech.NymVPN</id>
    <name>NymVPN</name>
    <url type="homepage">https://nymtech.net/</url>
    <developer id="net.nymtech">
        <name>PierreD</name>
        <name>Nym</name>
    </developer>
    <summary>Decentralized, mixnet, and zero-knowledge VPN</summary>
    <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LGPL-2.0-only</project_license>
    <description>
        <p>
            Use NymVPN and make your online activity safe.
            With our VPN app you can hide your IP address, encrypt your traffic,
            hide your identity online and much more.

            Many entities on the internet can spy on your activity and take your
            data.
            Governments, big tech, data brokers, internet service providers and
            advertisers can all try to monitor your online activity. Recent data
            leakage scandals made it clear that we can't even trust traditional
            VPN companies.

            Our VPN was born to make your internet activities private and a
            crucial part of this is not making activity logging and tracking
            possible.
            NymVPN is a new type of VPN designed in a way that makes it
            impossible for anyone to monitor or log your online activity, even
            for us. Our VPN operates on a decentralized network, with no trusted
            parties, centralized components, or single points of failure. All
            functionalities of NymVPN are performed in a decentralized and
            distributed way, and there is no possibility of enabling centralized
            logging.
            Our VPN encrypts data and shields metadata from traffic analysis
            through a decentralized Mixnet. Simply put: there is no way for us
            to log your activity, therefore no one can access it.

            But what exactly is a Mixnet? A Mixnet is a network of nodes that:
            1. Receive encrypted traffic
            2. Mix the traffic
            3. Redirect the traffic
            This process is done up to 5 times (5-hops) and makes it impossible
            for anyone to monitor or track your online activity.

            This is why you should choose our decentralized, secure, and private
            VPN

            Privacy
            Our dVPN was built with privacy in mind. We don't store logs
            (no-logs policy) nor track your activity. Even if someone wanted to
            steal your data from us, there would be nothing to steal.

            Censorship resistance
            Our VPN app makes your online activity completely anonymous. We
            encrypt your traffic, IP address, location and everything that
            someone with bad intentions could monitor. You are completely safe.

            Speed
            The speed of our VPN network grows by the minute thanks to many
            additional nodes joining the Mixnet network. Moreover, we use modern
            cryptographic algorithms and innovative protocols such as Sphinx and
            Loopix to make your connection as fast as possible.

            Location of choice
            With NymVPN you can choose to connect from hundreds of locations
            around the world.
            Download the app --> Choose the location --> Connect

            Crypto payments
            You are looking for a VPN that accepts crypto payments? Here we are.
            We are happy to accept payments with cryptocurrencies.

            No-ads
            Enjoy your VPN ads-free. Our main goal is to protect your privacy,
            also because of this you won't see any ads in our VPN app.

            Limitless usage
            Enjoy the internet as much as you want, NymVPN will never limit your
            traffic.

            Our VPN most beloved features:
            - 5-hop Mixnet: your internet traffic will be encrypted and sent to
            mixnodes that will mix it with other traffic packages 5 times,
            making it impossible for someone to track your online activity.
            - 2-hop dVPN: in this case your traffic is encrypted and sent to 2
            mixnodes that will mix it. The reduced number of hops results in
            higher speed.
            - No centralized logs: we don't store any activity logs, this makes
            it impossible for anyone to have access to your internet activity
            through us.
            - Money-back guarantee: if you are not happy with the product we
            offer a money-back guarantee policy. If you are not happy with
            something email us at support@nymvpn.com, we are always looking to
            improve.
            - Hide IP: our dVPN will hide all the information linked to you
            including your IP address.
        </p>
    </description>
    <releases>
        <release version="0.2.3" date="2024-10-11">
            <url type="details">
                https://github.com/nymtech/nym-vpn-client/releases/tag/nym-vpn-app-v0.2.3
            </url>
        </release>
    </releases>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">net.nymtech.NymVPN.desktop</launchable>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>
                https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nymtech/nym-vpn-client/09c9a18/nym-vpn-app/.pkg/screenshots/home-light.png
            </image>
            <caption>NymVPN app screenshot, home screen</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>
                https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nymtech/nym-vpn-client/09c9a18/nym-vpn-app/.pkg/screenshots/home-connected-light.png
            </image>
            <caption>NymVPN app screenshot, home screen connected</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>
                https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nymtech/nym-vpn-client/09c9a18/nym-vpn-app/.pkg/screenshots/home-countries-light.png
            </image>
            <caption>NymVPN app screenshot, countries selection screen</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>
                https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nymtech/nym-vpn-client/09c9a18/nym-vpn-app/.pkg/screenshots/home-dark.png
            </image>
            <caption>NymVPN app screenshot, home screen (Dark mode)</caption>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <image>
                https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nymtech/nym-vpn-client/09c9a18/nym-vpn-app/.pkg/screenshots/home-connected-dark.png
            </image>
            <caption>NymVPN app screenshot, home screen connected (Dark mode)
            </caption>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
