<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<component type="desktop">
  <!--Created with jdAppdataEdit 3.0-->
  <id>net.voltaicideas.dupeGuru</id>
  <name>dupeGuru</name>
  <summary>Find duplicate files on your computer</summary>
  <developer_name>Andrew Senetar</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.voltaicideas.dupeGuru.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>dupeGuru is a tool to find duplicate files on your computer. It can scan either filenames or contents. The filename scan features a fuzzy matching algorithm that can find duplicate filenames even when they are not exactly the same. dupeGuru runs on Mac OS X and Linux.</p>
    <p>dupeGuru is efficient. Find your duplicate files in minutes, thanks to its quick fuzzy matching algorithm. dupeGuru not only finds filenames that are the same, but it also finds similar filenames.</p>
    <p>dupeGuru is good with music. It has a special Music mode that can scan tags and shows music-specific information in the duplicate results window.</p>
    <p>dupeGuru is good with pictures. It has a special Picture mode that can scan pictures fuzzily, allowing you to find pictures that are similar, but not exactly the same.</p>
    <p>dupeGuru is customizable. You can tweak its matching engine to find exactly the kind of duplicates you want to find. The Preference page of the help file lists all the scanning engine settings you can change.</p>
    <p>dupeGuru is safe. Its engine has been especially designed with safety in mind. Its reference directory system as well as its grouping system prevent you from deleting files you didn’t mean to delete.</p>
    <p>Do whatever you want with your duplicates. Not only can you delete duplicates files dupeGuru finds, but you can also move or copy them elsewhere. There are also multiple ways to filter and sort your results to easily weed out false duplicates (for low threshold scans).</p>
  </description>
  <releases>
    <release version="4.2.1" date="2022-03-25" type="stable">
      <url>https://github.com/arsenetar/dupeguru/releases/tag/4.2.1</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Default to English on unsupported system language</li>
          <li>Fix image viewer zoom datatype issue</li>
          <li>Fix errors from window change event</li>
          <li>Fix deprecation warning from SQLite</li>
          <li>Enforce minimum Windows version in installer</li>
          <li>Fix help path for local files</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <url type="homepage">https://dupeguru.voltaicideas.net/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/arsenetar/dupeguru/issues</url>
  <url type="faq">https://dupeguru.voltaicideas.net/help/en/faq.html</url>
  <url type="help">https://dupeguru.voltaicideas.net/help/en/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://github.com/sponsors/arsenetar</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <recommends>
    <display_length compare="ge">medium</display_length>
  </recommends>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>deduplication</keyword>
  </keywords>
</component>
