<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.zdechov.app.xTactics</id>

  <name>xTactics</name>
  <summary>Risk like turn-based strategy game</summary>
  <developer id="net.zdechov.chronos">
    <name>Chronos</name>
  </developer>

  <url type="homepage">https://app.zdechov.net/xtactics</url>
  <url type="contact">https://app.zdechov.net/xtactics#Contact</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://app.zdechov.net/xtactics/browser</url>

  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>CC0-1.0</project_license>

  <description>
    <p>
       It is a highly configurable turn-based strategy game inspired by mechanics of Risk board game.
    </p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Zoom-able map.</li>
      <li>Map can be generated in cyclic mode to simulate world without borders.</li>
      <li>Application configuration stored in XML file.</li>
      <li>Allows to save and load game to game file in XML format with extension .xtg.</li>
      <li>Localization support (English, Czech)</li>
      <li>High DPI support.</li>
      <li>Multiple map cell shapes as hexagons, squares, triangles, isometric, and random mesh.</li>
      <li>Bridges between remote cells visible as lines.</li>
      <li>Multiple players support. Players can have different color and other starting properties.</li>
      <li>Application automatically open saved game file given as command line parameter after execution.</li>
      <li>Computer player settings to be low, medium or highly aggressive in attacking.</li>
      <li>Use Shift key during mouse click to attack maximum available power is moved without dialog confirmation.</li>
      <li>Use Control key during mouse click to move with maximum one time and repeated unit counts to selected target cell.</li>
      <li>Game option "Fog of war" which cause map to be covered to black and only explored cells will be visible.</li>
      <li>Auto save game to file option in settings.</li>
      <li>Map shape can be selected as Rectangular, Rounded or mask from image file.</li>
      <li>Support for symmetric map usable for two players game.</li>
      <li>Confirmation dialog for ending game.</li>
      <li>Support for switching large icons in toolbar.</li>
      <li>Support for cities. Cities can configured to be used as only growing cells.</li>
      <li>Allows to set grow rate as square root of cell power.</li>
      <li>Amount of inaccessible cells can be adjusted in New game dialog.</li>
      <li>Player mode human or computer.</li>
      <li>Graph window can be shown from menu which presents development of various statistic values during game turns.</li>
      <li>Load recent menu action to load recently opened/saved files.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.zdechov.app.xTactics.desktop</launchable>

  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#99c1f1</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#1a5fb4</color>
  </branding>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main window</caption>
      <image>https://svn.zdechov.net/xtactics/tags/1.4.0/Images/Screenshots/xTactics.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>World map</caption>
      <image>https://svn.zdechov.net/xtactics/tags/1.4.0/Images/Screenshots/xTactics%20world.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Dark theme</caption>
      <image>https://svn.zdechov.net/xtactics/tags/1.4.0/Images/Screenshots/xTactics%20dark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.4.0" date="2025-01-04">
      <url type="details">https://svn.zdechov.net/xtactics/tags/1.4.0/Release%20Notes.txt</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added: Application icon with 128x128 resolution.</li>
          <li>Added: Close button on more forms for better touch screen devices support.</li>
          <li>Added: Game systems action in Tools menu.</li>
          <li>Added: Allow to add building kinds to game system.</li>
          <li>Added: Allow to manage nations for each game system.</li>
          <li>Added: New map type hexagonal horizontal.</li>
          <li>Added: Limit allowed map type according selected game system.</li>
          <li>Added: Allow to load/save game system from/to file system as .xts file.</li>
          <li>Added: Allow to move units instantly during turn.</li>
          <li>Added: Game system parameter to play without possibility to merge/split units.</li>
          <li>Added: Show units shape to see in which cell units are placed.</li>
          <li>Added: Delete button to unit move dialog.</li>
          <li>Added: Map random preview in New game form.</li>
          <li>Added: New menu action show/hide map grid lines.</li>
          <li>Added: New win objective None to just play freely without any win objective.</li>
          <li>Added: New win objective to capture entire map.</li>
          <li>Added: New game systems to represent various game play systems of other existing games.</li>
          <li>Added: New game option to set cells without player units as neutral.</li>
          <li>Modified: Improved data directories detection.</li>
          <li>Modified: OK button moved to be on the left side of buttons.</li>
          <li>Modified: Added more action icons to main toolbar and main menu.</li>
          <li>Modified: Do not paint new game preview bellow form height.</li>
          <li>Modified: Automatically save running game on application exit and reopen it on next start.</li>
          <li>Modified: Automatic map zoom on new game.</li>
          <li>Modified: Show icons in shortcuts window.</li>
          <li>Modified: Improved dark theme support on Windows.</li>
          <li>Modified: End turn with space key.</li>
          <li>Modified: Allow to set nation in player settings.</li>
          <li>Modified: Allow to have only one player in the game.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Initialization of preset World image map.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Map image was not always loaded and applied.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Symetric map generation.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Store current player information to game save to be able to continue with different player.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Item list form minimal item count limit on items removal.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Store client form settings on close.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Workaround for incorrect client form drawing area size on Windows.</li>
          <li>Fixed: New game symetric map units calcualtion.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Map preview with cell and unit borders.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Allow to set preferred game system grid type.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Remember maximized main form state on Linux.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Main form was not visible on Windows task bar.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Size of buttons was too small in some cases.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Show toolbars hints.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Fully terminate the application on main form closure.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Error if players stats opened.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Clear correctly defender player from unit moves if his cell is captured.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Do not allow to remove too many players to have at least minimum players.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Bad cell links in Random map type causing problems on openning saved file.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Selection of unit moves.</li>
          <li>Fixed: Full screen mode under Windows and Linux.</li>		
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <categories>
    <category>Game</category>
    <category>StrategyGame</category>
  </categories>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
