<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.purrdata.PurrData</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+ and BSD-3-Clause</project_license>
  <name>Purr Data</name>
  <summary>An open source visual programming language for multimedia</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      This package contains Purr Data, which is a fork of Pure Data that
      bundles a lot of useful extensions, and brings a modern HTML5-based
      user interface.
    </p>
    <p>
        <em>IMPORTANT</em>: Running Pure Data under Flatpak is experimental.
        The following are known limitations.
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Realtime priority cannot be used.</li>
      <li>JACK audio backend cannot be used.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      Packages from https://www.purrdata.net/ do not have these limitations.
    </p>
    <p>
      Pure Data is an open source visual programming environment that runs on
      anything from personal computers to embedded devices (ie Raspberry Pi)
      and smartphones (via libpd, DroidParty (Android), and PdParty (iOS).
      It is a major branch of the family of patcher programming languages
      known as Max (Max/FTS, ISPW Max, Max/MSP, etc), originally developed
      by Miller Puckette at IRCAM.
    </p>
    <p>
      Pd enables musicians, visual artists, performers, researchers, and
      developers to create software graphically without writing lines of
      code. Pd can be used to process and generate sound, video, 2D/3D
      graphics, and interface sensors, input devices, and MIDI. Pd can
      easily work over local and remote networks to integrate wearable
      technology, motor systems, lighting rigs, and other equipment. It
      is suitable for learning basic multimedia processing and visual
      programming methods as well as for realizing complex systems for
      large-scale projects.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://git.purrdata.net/samthursfield/flatpak-net.purrdata.PurrData/raw/master/screenshots/pd-parody-2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <developer_name>The Purr Data developers</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.purrdata.PurrData.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.purrdata.net/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://git.purrdata.net/jwilkes/purr-data/issues</url>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="2.10.0" date="2019-10-02" />
  </releases>
</component>
