<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<releases>
    <release version="1.7.60" date="2026-02-11" urgency="low" type="stable">
        <description>
            <p>- Fixed a longstanding issue causing impact, roll, and skid sounds to not
  function.
- Fun easter-egg when clicking characters in inventory window (Thanks
  EraOSBeta!)
- It is no longer possible to capture the hill from below the platform in happy
  thoughts king of the hill (Thanks ZackerDC!)
- Added Japanese translation (Thanks internet stranger!!)
- Removed final remnants of the old store UI.
- Tweaked flag positions on Roundabout to reduce tossing-the-flag-across cheese
  (Thanks SoK!).
- Fixed an error that could occur when leaving solo mode elimination (Thanks
  FluffyPal0!).
- Asset-package versions now use a date-based version format instead of a
  numeric one. So instead of `a-0.bastdassets.5`, built-in assets will now come
  from something like `a-0.bastdassets.260116` (YYMMDD).
- Flatpak package name is now `net.froemling.bombsquad` instead of
  `net.froemling.BombSquad` along with improved package metadata.
  Installing new flatpak builds alongside old flatpak builds will create 2 
  seperate installs.
- Added `flatpak-generate-flathub-manifest` make target that will generate 
  manifest for flathub in `build/flathub`
- Updated Android audio stack to OpenALSoft 1.25.1 and oboe 1.10.0.
- Updated Mac and Window audio stack to OpenALSoft 1.25.1.
- Fixed an issue with overlapping widgets in the corner of the Plugins window
  when shown from within a game.
- Cleaned up some Makefile targets. Targets such as `check2` or `preflight2` are
  now called `check-ex`, `preflight-ex`, etc. These targets are slower but more
  complete than regular versions; ideal for things like CI where
  accuracy/consistency is more important than iteration speed. In line with
  this, the `test-fast` target is now `test` and the old regular `test` target
  is now `test-ex`.
- We now run Pylint in multiprocess mode for regular check targets but not for
  'ex' ones. When I last tried this years ago it gave somewhat flaky
  nondeterministic results, but apparently it is better now. We'll see. The 'ex'
  versions still run in a single-process so CI should catch anything that slips
  through interactive checks. This gives a pretty huge speedup so hopefully is a
  good tradeoff.
- Added a null audio device to prevent crash when no audio device is available
- Flatpak permissions adjusted to allow gamepads to be properly detected and the
  configuration directory to be created if it does not already exist.</p>
            </description>
        <url>https://github.com/efroemling/ballistica/releases/tag/v1.7.60</url>
        <artifacts>
            <artifact type="source">
                <location>https://github.com/efroemling/ballistica/archive/refs/tags/v1.7.60.tar.gz</location>
                </artifact>
            <artifact type="source" platform="x86_64-linux-gnu">
                <location>https://github.com/efroemling/ballistica/releases/download/v1.7.60/linux_build_env.tar</location>
                <checksum type="sha256">409727c39713b7382f2a6b0627b49f8923006659a911668f739e4272c48a21b1</checksum>
                </artifact>
        </artifacts>
    </release>
    <release version="1.7.59" date="2026-01-13" urgency="low" type="stable">
        <description>
            <p>This stable release fixes bugs.</p>
            </description>
    </release>
</releases>
