<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.gnome.OCRFeeder</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gnome.OCRFeeder.desktop</launchable>
  <name>OCRFeeder</name>
  <summary>The complete OCR suite</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <developer_name>Joaquim Rocha</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>OCRFeeder is a document layout analysis and optical character recognition system.</p>
    <p>Given the images it will automatically outline its contents, distinguish between what's graphics and text and perform OCR over the latter. It generates multiple formats being its main one ODT.</p>
    <p>It features a complete GTK graphical user interface that allows the users to correct any unrecognized characters, defined or correct bounding boxes, set paragraph styles, clean the input images, import PDFs, save and load the project, export everything to multiple formats, etc.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main window</caption>
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/OCRFeeder?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=ocrfeeder.jpeg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Unpaper Image Processor</caption>
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/OCRFeeder?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=ocrfeeder_unpaper.jpeg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Check spelling</caption>
      <image>https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/OCRFeeder?action=AttachFile&amp;do=get&amp;target=ocrfeeder_spellchecker.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.gnome.org/GNOME/ocrfeeder/issues</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://wiki.gnome.org/Apps/OCRFeeder</url>
  <update_contact>me@joaquimrocha.com</update_contact>
  <translation type="gettext">ocrfeeder</translation>
  <provides>
    <binary>ocrfeeder</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <releases>
    <release version="0.8.1" date="2014-12-22">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>The Preferences dialog is now smaller (the big contents are wrapped in a scrolled window).</li>
          <li>All dialogs are now centered to the main window.</li>
          <li>Use XDG user's configuration directory instead of .ocrfeeder.</li>
          <li>Fix Gtk thread related problems.</li>
          <li>Fix unicode issues when saving a project and exporting a document.</li>
          <li>Fix issue when exporting a picture in a document from a loaded project.</li>
          <li>Fix ODT exportation button's icon.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.8.0" date="2014-08-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add support for multiple image TIFFs.</li>
          <li>Port the application to GObject Introspection.</li>
          <li>Scan with 300 DPI and in color mode.</li>
          <li>Use the last visited directory when adding a new image.</li>
          <li>Warn when no OCR engines are found on startup or when performing the recognition.</li>
          <li>Update the box editor's OCR controls sensitiveness according to the existence of OCR engines.</li>
          <li>Fix PIL importation.</li>
          <li>Fix error when exporting a PDF with empty text areas.</li>
          <li>Fix PDF output options in ocrfeeder-cli.</li>
          <li>Fix getting engine name in ocrfeeder-cli.</li>
          <li>Fix the use of newer versions of Unpaper.</li>
          <li>Fix text in the pages icon view.</li>
          <li>Fix reordering pages in the icon view.</li>
          <li>Fix issues when no locale is set.</li>
          <li>Fix loading project with more than one page.</li>
          <li>Fix updating the OCR engines in the BoxEditor.</li>
          <li>New and updated translations: cz (Marek Černocký), es (Daniel Mustieles), gl (Fran Diéguez), el (Dimitris Spingos), he (Aharon Don), hu (Attila Hammer, Gabor Kelemen), pt_BR (Rafael Ferreira), sl (Martin Srebotnjak), sr (Мирослав Николић), uk (Piotr Drąg), zh_CN (Wylmer Wang).</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
