<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Danny van Heumen -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.claws_mail.Claws-Mail</id>
  <name>Claws-Mail</name>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-only</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <developer_name>The Claws Mail Team</developer_name>
  <summary>Claws Mail is an email client (and news reader), based on GTK+</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://claws-mail.org/</url>

  <description>
    <p>Claws Mail is an email client (and news reader), based on GTK+, featuring:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Quick response</li>
      <li>Graceful, and sophisticated interface</li>
      <li>Easy configuration, intuitive operation</li>
      <li>Abundant features</li>
      <li>Extensibility</li>
      <li>Robustness and stability</li>
    </ul>
    <p>The appearance and interface are designed to be familiar to new users coming from other popular email clients, as well as experienced users. Almost all commands are accessible with the keyboard.</p>
    <p>The messages are managed in the standard MH format, which features fast access and data security. You'll be able to import your emails from almost any other email client, and export them just as easily.</p>
    <p>Lots of extra functionality, like an RSS aggregator, calendar, or laptop LED handling, are provided by extra plugins.</p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable>claws-mail</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cobratbq/flathub-org.clawsmail.Claws-Mail/org.clawsmail.Claws-Mail/screenshot-main.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">
        https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cobratbq/flathub-org.clawsmail.Claws-Mail/org.clawsmail.Claws-Mail/screenshot-compose.png
      </image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="3.17.4" date="2019-07-26">
      <description>
        <p>New in this release:</p>
        <ul>
		      <li>New HTML viewer plugin: Litehtml viewer</li>
          <li>Added option 'Enable keyboard shortcuts' to the 'Keyboard shortcuts' frame on /Configuration/Preferences/Other/Miscellaneous</li>
          <li>Compose: implemented copying of attached images to clipboard</li>
          <li>Compose: images and text/uri-list (files) can now be attached by pasting into the Compose window</li>
          <li>Python plugin: window sizes are now remembered for the Python console, the 'Open URLs' and the 'Set mailbox order' windows</li>
          <li>Fancy plugin: the download-link feature now follows redirections</li>
          <li>MBOX export: the Enter key in the dialogue now starts the export</li>
          <li>The date (ISO format) has been added to log timestamps</li>
          <li>Updated translations: Brazilian Portuguese, Catalan, Czech, Danish, Dutch, French, German, Hungarian, Indonesian, Polish, Portuguese, Romanian, Russian, Slovak, Spanish, Swedish, Traditional Chinese, Turkish</li>
          <li>Bug fixes: <ul>
            <li>bug 1920, 'No automatic NNTP filtering'</li>
            <li>bug 2045, 'address book blocks focus on email window'</li>
            <li>bug 2131, 'Focus stealing after mail check'</li>
            <li>bug 2627, 'Filtering does not work on NNTP'</li>
            <li>bug 3070, 'misbehaving text wrapping when URL chars are present'</li>
            <li>bug 3838, 'Canceled right-click on message list leaves UI in inconsistent state'</li>
            <li>bug 3977, 'Fix crashes when some external APIs fail'</li>
            <li>bug 3979, 'Hang (with killing needed) during action which extracts attachments'</li>
            <li>bug 4029, 'segfault after deleting message in a window'</li>
            <li>bug 4031, 'fingerprint in SSL/TLS certificates for ... (regress error)'</li>
            <li>bug 4037, 'Fix some small issues'</li>
            <li>bug 4142, 'Translation error on Russian'</li>
            <li>bug 4145, 'proxy server for sending doesn't work'</li>
            <li>bug 4155, 'remember directory of last saving'</li>
            <li>bug 4166, 'corrupted double-linked list'</li>
            <li>bug 4167, 'Max line length exceeded when forwarding mail'</li>
            <li>bug 4188, 'STL file is sent not as an attachment but as its base64 representation in plaintext'</li>
            <li>CID 1442278, 'impossible to trigger buffer overflow'</li>
            <li>Make key accelerators from menu work in addressbook window</li>
            <li>save checkbox choices of display/summaries/defaults prefs</li>
            <li>Do not throw an error when cancelling 'Save email as...'.</li>
            <li>occasional crash on drag'n'drop of msgs</li>
            <li>possible stack overflow in vcalendar's Curl data handler</li>
            <li>crash when LDAP address source is defined in index, but LDAP support is disabled</li>
            <li>crash in Fancy plugin if one of the MIME parts has no Content-ID</li>
            <li>a few small memory leaks in scan_mailto_url()</li>
            <li>configure script for rare cases where python is not installed</li>
            <li>incorrect charset conversion in sc_html_read_line().</li>
            <li>markup in 'key not fully trusted' warning in pgpcore</li>
            <li>use after free in rare code path in rssyl_subscribe()</li>
            <li>several memory leaks</li>
            <li>verify_folderlist_xml() for fresh starts</li>
            <li>printf formats for size_t and goffset arguments.</li>
            <li>alertpanel API use in win32 part of mimeview.c</li>
            <li>pid handling in debug output of kill_children_cb()</li>
            <li>incorrect pointer arithmetic in w32_filesel.c</li>
          </ul></li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <update_contact>danny_AT_dannyvanheumen.nl</update_contact>
</component>
