<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.bzflag.BZFlag</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.bzflag.BZFlag.desktop</launchable>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1 or MPL-2.0</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>BZFlag</name>
  <summary>A 3D first person tank battle game</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      BZFlag is a 3D networked multi-player multi-platform tank battle game. It runs on Windows, macOS, Linux, BSD, and other platforms. It was one of the most popular games ever on Silicon Graphics machines and continues to be developed and improved to this day.
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.bzflag.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/BZFlag-Dev/bzflag/issues</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.bzflag.org/help</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.bzflag.org/images/screenshots/dantes_inferno_01.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.bzflag.org/images/screenshots/home_sweet_home_02.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.bzflag.org/images/screenshots/aa_bridge_crossing_01.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.4.14" date="2018-05-03">
      <description>
        <p>This release had several fixes and some new features.</p>
        <ul>
        <li>The mute/kill/kick/ban messages no longer display admin callsigns, and the ban message shows the remaining ban time.</li>
        <li>World weapon API has been revamped, including new bz_eServerShotFiredEvent and bz_eAllowServerShotFiredEvent events.</li>
        <li>New showMotto permission to control which players are allowed to set a motto.</li>
        <li>Custom BZDB variables defined by plugins no longer require using -setforced to set them from configuration file.</li>
        <li>The number pad keys are now treated uniquely for key mapping with SDL2.</li>
        <li>Antialiasing now works when starting the client windowed.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.4.12" date="2017-10-30">
      <description>
        <p>This release had a few additional features and some minor fixes.</p>
        <ul>
        <li>Multisampling (anti-aliasing) now works on all platforms with SDL</li>
        <li>The permission for running /poll set is no longer assigned by default</li>
        <li>The macOS build uses a newly released version of SDL that fixes an issue with retina macs when running in a scaled resolution</li>
        <li>It is possible to silence all unregistered players in your client by silencing - (the minus sign or hyphen), similar to how silencing * (asterisk) silences all players. Additionally, the /silence and /unsilence commands both work correctly now and support both special cases.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="2.4.10" date="2017-03-12">
      <description>
        <p>This release had a few additional features and some minor fixes.</p>
        <ul>
        <li>Multisampling support under SDL 2 on macOS</li>
        <li>Added an option to invert one or both joystick axes</li>
        <li>Add ability to reload badwords list with '/reload badwords'</li>
        <li>It is possible for bzfs plugins to register new types of polls</li>
        <li>Fix high DPI handling on Windows (again, since it broke when we switched to using SDL2)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>

