<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.buhocms.BuhoCMS</id>
  
  <name>BuhoCMS</name>
  <summary>A local CMS for Hugo static sites</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  
  <description>
    <p>
      BuhoCMS is a local Content Management System for static site generators like Hugo.
    </p>
    <p>
      See BuhoCMS as a GUI for static site generators (currently Hugo). Easily create or open a Hugo site, choose your Hugo theme and add your first posts. With BuhoCMS, adding and editing content is as easy as a few clicks. No more terminal commands, folder hunting or manual Front matter edits!
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>SSGs supported: Hugo</li>
        <li>Create or open a site</li>
        <li>Install Hugo themes for your site</li>
        <li>Add new posts and edit your Markdown content and Front matter with ease</li>
        <li>Edit content: Use the Markdown toolbar for quickly adding styles</li>
        <li>Markdown preview: Use the Markdown viewer to check your syntax</li>
        <li>Front matter: Graphical User Interface (GUI) for each field like a Text field, Switch, Date picker, Tag editor, and more</li>
        <li>Switch between GUI and raw text mode</li>
        <li>Start, open and stop your local Hugo server with a click</li>
        <li>Build your final Hugo site and open its &quot;public&quot; folder</li>
        <li>Privacy: BuhoCMS is a local program with no internet connection required – no ads, no tracking</li>
        <li>Free and open source: Licensed under the GPLv3</li>
        <li>Themes: Material Design with multiple color themes, both light and dark</li>
        <li>Fully responsive</li>
        <li>Multiple languages supported – Contribute translating your language!</li>
        <li>...and many more features planned</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.buhocms.BuhoCMS.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/iakmds/buhocms/master/.github/screenshot1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/iakmds/buhocms/master/.github/screenshot2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/iakmds/buhocms/master/.github/screenshot3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/iakmds/buhocms/master/.github/screenshot4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
