<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>org.kde.kjumpingcube</id>
    <name>KJumpingCube</name>
    <name xml:lang="ar">كي جمبينج كيوب</name>
    <name xml:lang="bn">কেজাম্পিংকিউব</name>
    <name xml:lang="es">CuboSaltador</name>
    <name xml:lang="hi">केजंपिंगक्यूब</name>
    <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Cubo Saltador</name>
    <summary>Develop a good strategy to conquer all the squares</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ar">قم بتطوير استراتيجية جيدة للإستيلاء على كل المربعات (المساحات).</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="bn">সকল বর্গক্ষেত্র জিতে নেবার জন্য একটি দক্ষ কৌশল ঠিক করে নিন</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="es">Conquista todas las plazas</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="fr">Développez une stratégie efficace pour conquérir tous les carrés</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="hi">सभी स्क्वायर्स को जीतने के लिए एक बेहतरीन रणनीति बनाएं</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="id">Susun strategi yang bagus untuk mengalahkan semua kotak</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Desenvolva uma boa estratégia para conquistar todos os espaços</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ro">Dezvolta o strategie buna pentru a cuceri toate patratele</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="th">พัฒนากลยุทธ์ดี ๆ เพื่อจะพิชิตสี่เหลี่ยมทั้งหมด</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="vi">Xây dựng chiến thuật tốt để chinh phục tất cả mọi lô đất</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">通过策略来攻占所有方格</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">制定良好的戰略以征服所有範圍</summary>
    <description><p>Practice your strategic thinking with this challenging dice-based game! You move by clicking on a vacant square or one you already own. If you click on a vacant square, its color changes to show that you now own it. Each time you click on a square, its value increases by one. Once a square has more points than immediate neighbors, its points are distributed among the neighbors (the points jump around). If a neighboring square is owned by your opponent, you take control of that square and all of its points. You will need to think carefully to control all the squares, and since dice can change hands very quickly, this game is sure to keep you engaged and on your toes!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ar"><p>تدرب على التفكير الاستراتيجي الخاص بك في هذه اللعبة المليئة بالتحديات والتي تعتمد على النرد! فأنت تتحرك بالنقر على المربع الشاغر أو على أحد المربعات التي تملكها. إذا قمت بالنقر على مربع شاغر، يتغير لونه ليُظهر ملكيتك له في حينها. في كل مرةٍ تنقر فيها على أحد المربعات، تزيد قيمته بواحد. بمجرد أن يكون بالمربع نقاط أكثر من الجيران المحيطين، فإن نقاطه يتم توزيعها بين هؤلاء الجيران (تقفز النقاط في جميع الأنحاء). إذا امتلك منافسك مربع مُجاورلك، تُسيطر أنت على هذا المربع وعلى ما جميع ما به من نقاط. ستحتاج إلى تفكيرٍ عميق لكي تستطيع السيطرة على جميع المربعات، ولأن النرد يمكنه تغيير الأوضاع بسرعة كبيرة، فهذه اللعبة بكل تأكيدٍ ستبقيك مشغولاً بها وستحفز انتباهك للغاية!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="bn"><p>আপনার কৌশলগত চিন্তার প্রক্রিয়া আরও শাণিত করুন এই রোমাঞ্চকর ডাইস গেমটির মাধ্যমে। কোন খালি বর্গে বা আপনার অধীন অংশে ক্লিক করে সরতে পারবেন। আপনি যদি একটি খালি বর্গে ক্লিক করেন, তবে এর রঙ বদলে গিয়ে দেখাবে যে এটি এখন আপনার অধীনে চলে গেছে। প্রতিবার আপনি কোনো বর্গে ক্লিক করলে তার মান এক বাড়বে। পাশের বর্গগুলো থেকে বেশি পয়েন্ট পেলে পাশেরগুলোতে ভাগ হয়ে যাবে (পয়েন্ট ঘুরে বেড়াবে)। পাশের বর্গগুলো আপনার প্রতিপক্ষের হলে সেগুলোর অধিকার এবং সকল পয়েন্টও আপনার হবে। বর্গগুলো নিজের দখলে রাখতে তাই আপনাকে কৌশলে চিন্তা করতে হবে, কারণ এগুলো দ্রুতই হাতবদল হবে। এই খেলাটি নিশ্চিতভাবেই আপনাকে প্রচণ্ড ব্যস্ত রাখতে সক্ষম হবে!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="es"><p>¡Practica tu pensamiento estratégico con este juego desafiante basado en los dados! Te puedes mover con hacer clic en un cuadrado vacante o en uno que ya tienes. Si haces clic en un cuadrado vacío, su color cambia para mostrar que ahora es tuyo. Cada vez que haces clic en un cuadrado, su valor aumenta por uno. Una vez que un cuadrado tiene más puntos que los que lo rodean, sus puntos son distribuidos entre ellos (los puntos saltan). Si un cuadrado vecino es propiedad de tu oponente, tomas el control de ese cuadrado y de todos sus puntos. Tendrás que pensar cuidadosamente para controlar todos los cuadrados, y porque los dados se pueden cambiar de manos muy rápidamente, este juego seguramente te mantendrá atento e interesado!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="fr"><p>Entraînez-vous à la pensée stratégique avec ce jeu exigeant basé sur des dés ! Vous vous déplacez en cliquant sur un carré libre ou un carré que vous possédez déjà. Si vous cliquez sur un carré libre, sa couleur change et devient la vôtre. Chaque fois que vous cliquez sur un carré, sa valeur augmente de un. Une fois qu&apos;un carré a plus de points que ses voisins immédiats, ses points sont distribués entre ses voisins (les points se déplacent). Si un carré voisin appartient à votre adversaire, vous en prenez le contrôle ainsi que tous ses points. Vous devrez bien réfléchir pour contrôler tous les carrés, et comme les dés peuvent changer de mains très rapidement, ce jeu vous gardera assurément en haleine !</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="hi"><p>इस चुनौतीपूर्ण डाइस-आधारित गेम के साथ अपने रणनीतिक सोच का अभ्यास करें! किसी खाली स्क्वायर या आपके पास पहले से मौजूद स्क्वायर पर क्लिक करके आप आगे बढ़ते हैं। यदि आप खाली स्क्वायर पर क्लिक करते हैं, तो इसका रंग बदल जाता है जो दिखाता है कि अब यह आपका है। हरेक बार जब आप किसी स्क्वायर पर क्लिक करते हैं, तो इसके वैल्यू में एक का इजाफा होता है। जब किसी स्क्वायर का प्वॉइंट इसके पड़ोस के स्क्वायर से अधिक होता है, तो इसके प्वॉइंट्स पड़ोस के स्क्वायर्स में वितरित होता जाते हैं (प्वॉइंट्स जम्प करते हैं)। यदि पड़ोस का स्क्वायर आपके विपक्षी का है तो उसपर आपका नियंत्रण हो जाता है और इसके सभी प्वॉइंट्स आपके हो जाते जाते हैं। सभी स्क्वायर्स पर कब्जा करने के लिए आपको ध्यान से सोचना होगा, और चूंकि डाइस हैंड्स को बहुत तेजी से बदल सकता है, इसलिए यह गेम आपको निश्चित रूप से बांध कर और अलर्ट रखेगा!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="id"><p>Praktikkan pemikiran strategis Anda dengan permainan berbasis dadu yang menantang ini! Anda bergerak dengan mengklik kotak kosong atau yang sudah Anda miliki. Jika Anda mengklik pada kotak kosong, warnanya yang berubah akan menunjukkan bahwa Anda sekarang memiliki kotak itu. Setiap kali Anda mengklik kotak, nilainya bertambah satu. Jika sebuah kotak memiliki poin lebih tinggi dari sebelah-sebelahnya, poinnya dibagikan di antara sebelah-sebelahnya (poinnya melompat-lompat). Jika kotak sebelah dimiliki oleh lawan, Anda mengambil alih kotak tersebut dan semua poinnya. Anda perlu berpikir dengan hati-hati agar dapat menguasai semua kotak, dan karena dadunya dapat berpindah tangan dengan sangat cepat, permainan ini pasti akan membuat Anda tetap sibuk dan sigap!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR"><p>Pratique seu pensamento estratégico com esse jogo desafiador. Se mova clicando nos espaços vazios ou que já sejam seus. Se você clicar em um quadrado vazio ele ganha a sua cor, mostrando que agora ele é seu. Cada vez que você clica no mesmo quadrado ele ganha mais um ponto. Uma vez que um quadrado tem mais pontos que os quadrados vizinhos, eles são distribuídos (os pontos pulam para os quadrados em volta). Se o quadrado vizinho for do adversário, você passa a ser o novo dono do espaço e dos pontos desse quadrado. Você precisa pensar cuidadosamente para controlar todos os quadrados pois os pontos mudam de mãos rapidamente e isso vai mantê-lo envolvido por um bom tempo!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ro"><p>Practica gandirea strategica cu acest joc provocator de zaruri! Vă mutați făcând clic pe un pătrat liber sau unul pe care deja îl dețineți. Dacă faceți clic pe un pătrat vacant, modificări de culoare se vor face pentru a arăta că acum il dețineți. De fiecare dată când faceți clic pe un pătrat, crește valoarea cu unu. Odată ce un pătrat are mai multe puncte decât vecinii sai, punctele sale sunt distribuite între vecini (punctele sari in jurul). În cazul în care un pătrat vecin este proprietatea adversarului, să preia controlul de acel pătrat și toate punctele sale. Veți avea nevoie să va gânditi cu atenție pentru a controla toate piețele.!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="th"><p>ฝึกการคิดเชิงกลยุทธ์ของคุณด้วยความท้าทายเกมที่ใช้ลูกเต๋านี้! คุณเคลื่อนที่โดยการคลิกที่ตารางว่างหรือตารางที่คุณเป็นเจ้าของแล้ว หากคุณคลิกที่ตารางว่างการเปลี่ยนแปลงสีของมันแสดงให้เห็นว่าตอนนี้คุณเป็นเจ้าของมัน ทุกครั้งที่คุณคลิกที่ตารางค่าของมันจะเพิ่มขึ้นทีละหนึ่ง เมื่อตารางมีคะแนนมากกว่าเพื่อนบ้านที่ติดกัน จุดขอมันจะกระจายไปยังเพื่อนบ้าน (จุดกระโดดไปรอบ ๆ ) ถ้าตารางเพื่อนบ้านเป็นเจ้าของโดยฝ่ายตรงข้ามของคุณคุณใช้การควบคุมของตารางที่และทุกจุดของมัน คุณจะต้องคิดอย่างรอบคอบในการควบคุมสี่เหลี่ยมทั้งหมดและเนื่องจากลูกเต๋ามือสามารถเปลี่ยนได้อย่างรวดเร็วเกมนี้มั่นใจว่าจะทำให้คุณทำงานและยืนบนเท้าของคุณ!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="vi"><p>Thực hành tư duy chiến thuật với trò chơi thảy xí ngầu đầy thử thách này! Bạn di chuyển bằng cách nhấp vào một lô đất trống hoặc đã có sẵn. Nếu bạn nhấp vào một lô đất trống, màu lô đất sẽ thay đổi cho biết bạn đã là chủ sở hữu. Mỗi lần bạn nhấp vào một lô đất, giá trị của nó sẽ tăng lên một lần. Khi một lô đất có nhiều điểm hơn lô kế bên, điểm của lô sẽ được chia đều cho các lô lân cận (điểm nhảy chung quanh). Nếu lô đất kế bên do đối thủ sở hữu, bạn phải kiểm soát lô đất đó và các điểm trong đó. Bạn sẽ cần suy nghĩ cẩn thận để kiểm soát tất cả mọi lô đất, vì hột xí ngầu có thể đổi mặt rất nhanh, trò chơi này đảm bảo bạn hào hứng đến từng ngón chân!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_CN"><p>这个以骰子为对象的挑战性游戏可以锻炼您的策略性思维！您只需通过点击空白的方格或者您已有的方格来完成游戏。如果您点击了空白方格，它的颜色会改变，归为您拥有。您每点击方格一次，它的点值会上升一点。一旦其中一个方块的点值大于其相邻方块，这个方块的点值会均匀分布到相邻的方块中。如果相邻的方块本来是属于对手的，那就改为归您所有，您可以控制其点值。所以您在操控所有方块时都要仔细想清楚啦。由于骰子可能一瞬间会在双方中转手，游戏十分紧张刺激，相信您一定会喜欢的！</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_TW"><p>在這款富挑戰性的骰子遊戲中磨練你的策略思考！點擊已擁有或空的方格以進行移動。若點擊空的方格，其顏色將會變化，顯示為你所擁有。每次點擊方格，其價值都會上升一。一旦方格分數高於相鄰者，將會分配給相鄰者（環繞）。如果相鄰的方格是由對手所擁有，你將可控制該方格及其所有點數。必須仔細思考以控制所有的方格，而由於骰子轉手速度很快，此遊戲一定會讓你投入其中，全力以赴！</p></description>
    <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/</url>
    <screenshots>
      <screenshot type="default">
        <image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Kjumpingcube/C/org.kde.kjumpingcube-screenshot1.jpg</image>
        <image type="source" xml:lang="es">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Kjumpingcube/es/org.kde.kjumpingcube-screenshot1.jpg</image>
        <image type="source" xml:lang="pt">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Kjumpingcube/pt/org.kde.kjumpingcube-screenshot1.jpg</image>
      </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
		<release version="18.08.0" date="2018-08-16"/>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  </component>