<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id type="desktop">org.jitsi.jitsi-meet</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">org.jitsi.jitsi-meet.desktop</launchable>
    <name>Jitsi Meet</name>
    <summary>Jitsi Meet - Secure, Simple and Scalable Video Conferences</summary>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>
    <developer_name>Jitsi Team</developer_name>
    <url type="homepage">https://jitsi.org</url>
    <description>
        <p>Jitsi Meet lets you stay in touch with all your teams, be they family, friends, or colleagues. Instant video conferences, efficiently adapting to your scale.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Unlimited users: There are no artificial restrictions on the number of users or conference participants. Server power and bandwidth are the only limiting factors.</li>
            <li>No account needed.</li>
            <li>Lock-protected rooms: Control the access to your conferences with a password.</li>
            <li>Encrypted by default.</li>
            <li>High quality: Audio and video are delivered with the clarity and richness of Opus and VP8.</li>
            <li>Web browser ready: No downloads are required of your friends to join the conversation. Jitsi Meet works directly within their browsers as well. Simply share your conference URL with others to get started.</li>
            <li>100% open source: Powered by awesome communities from all over the world. And your friends at Atlassian.</li>
            <li>Invite by pretty URLs: You can meet at the easy to remember https://MySite.com/OurConf of your choice instead of joining the hard to remember rooms with seemingly random sequences of numbers and letters in their names.</li>
        </ul>
    </description>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jitsi/jitsi-meet-electron/d16e6a7b68896c4958ac612918e21963d31f82d3/screenshot.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
        <release version="2.3.1" date="2020-07-29"/>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
        <content_attribute id="social-chat">moderate</content_attribute>
        <content_attribute id="social-audio">moderate</content_attribute>
    </content_rating>
</component>
