<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.davmail.DavMail.desktop</id>
  <name>DavMail</name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <summary>DavMail POP/IMAP/SMTP/Caldav/Carddav/LDAP Exchange Gateway</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Ever wanted to get rid of Outlook ? DavMail is a
      POP/IMAP/SMTP/Caldav/Carddav/LDAP exchange gateway allowing
      users to use any mail/calendar client (e.g. Thunderbird with
      Lightning or Apple iCal) with an Exchange server, even from the
      internet or behind a firewall through Outlook Web
      Access. DavMail now includes an LDAP gateway to Exchange global
      address book and user personal contacts to allow recipient
      address completion in mail compose window and full calendar
      support with attendees free/busy display. The main goal of
      DavMail is to provide standard compliant protocols in front of
      proprietary Exchange. This means LDAP for address book, SMTP to
      send messages, IMAP to browse messages on the server in any
      folder, POP to retrieve inbox messages only and Caldav for
      calendar support. Thus any standard compliant client can be used
      with Microsoft Exchange. DavMail gateway is implemented in java
      and should run on any platform. Releases are tested on Windows,
      Linux (Ubuntu) and Mac OSX. Tray does not work on MacOS and is
      replaced with a full frame. Tested successfully with the Iphone
      (gateway running on a server).
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://davmail.sourceforge.net</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://screenshots.debian.net/screenshots/000/015/485/large.png</image>
      <image>http://davmail.sourceforge.net/images/davmailArchitecture.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <developer_name>Mickaël Guessant</developer_name>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
    <release version="4.9.0" date="2018-09-05">
      <description>
        <p>
Includes a lot of enhancements, library upgrades, improved Linux desktop support, code cleanup
and a brand new Carddav distribution list support.
DavMail repository is now synced with Github, including Travis CI integration.

Enhancements:
- Update Jcharset to 2.0
- Upgrade JavaMail to 1.5.6
- Fix maven dependencies, reference local jars for libraries missing in main Maven repository
- Sample config to log connections in a separate log
- Provide command to launch DavMail without SWT
- Cleanup from audit
- Fix from audit: remove duplicate code
- Remove old repositories from Maven pom and add stax2-api dependency
- Remove dependency to xercesImpl-2.8.1.jar
- Drop jsmoothgen-ant-0.9.9-7-mgu2.jar, replaced with WinRun4J
- Upgrade to Woodstox 5.1.0, waiting for pull request to drop patch, see https://github.com/FasterXML/woodstox/pull/56
- Fix from code audit
- Allow console logging in server mode
- Implement -server command line option
- Implement compile target for Java 9 and later

Linux:
- Linux: Allow JDK 11 with Debian package
- Linux: disable system tray on Ubuntu 18

Carddav:
- Carddav: Add unit test to check CRLF conversion in multiline properties
- Carddav: by jbhensley, drop carriage returns from property value
- Carddav: distribution list / contacts unit tests
- Carddav: by jbhensley, fix vCard PHOTO property. Tested on iOS 11.2.6 and Outlook 2013 
- Carddav: Detect empty picture data
- Carddav: Use cn as default sn for distribution lists
- Carddav: avoid NullPointerException with empty distribution lists and prefer user provided photo
- Carddav: search for members on all email attributes
- Carddav: Merge contact and distribution list search
- Carddav: implement distribution list create and update
- Carddav: Merge DistributionList with Contact
- Carddav: First step at distribution list implementation, retrieve DL and members

Github:
- Add link to github repo
- Add Travis build status
- Fix old developerConnection and remove prerequisites according to Travis CI log
- First try at travis CI config
- Added : /trunk/README.md

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix from code audit
- IMAP: fix #689 Double space in UID FETCH response
- IMAP: include Conversation History in standard folder list
- IMAP: fix patch #49 mixed case INBOX select by google

EWS:
- EWS: fix duplicate bcc definition
- EWS: improve error handling, get field names on update item error

Caldav:
- Caldav: workaround for invalid RRULE with both COUNT and UNTIL values leading to ErrorMimeContentConversion failed error
- Caldav: cleanup from audit
- Caldav: fix timezone failover
- Caldav: unit test for Korganizer duplicate timezone bug
- Caldav: workaround for Korganizer duplicate timezone bug
- Caldav: Fix recurrence enumeration values

Documentation:
- Doc: add FAQ entry for Office 365
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.8.6" date="2018-06-14">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release with latest Caldav EWS enhancements, also includes fixes for old standing bugs in bug tracker.

IMAP:
- IMAP: Fix #631 IMAP SEARCH CHARSET US-ASCII fails

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix #687 can&#x27;t move event to trash in a shared mailbox
- Caldav: fix multivalued field update, send DeleteItemField instead of SetItemField with an empty value when field has no value, should fix bug #682
- Caldav: Detect X-MOZ-LASTACK and X-MOZ-SNOOZE-TIME updates to avoid sending notifications on dismiss with Thunderbird

Documentation:
- Doc: update roadmap

Enhancements
- Fix #476, try to avoid deadlock with a connection manager object lock
- Fix #456 longstanding proxy handling issue
- Update spec file
- Add GPLv2 license at root
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.8.5" date="2018-04-10">
      <description>
        <p>
More Caldav fixes, drop SWT on windows and try to improve tray support detection on various Linux distributions.

Caldav:
- Caldav: test notification dialog
- Caldav: do not throw exception on invalid email in getFreeBusyData
- Caldav: EWS isorganizer is Exchange 2013 and later only, switch to myresponsetype
- Caldav: fix #306, do not try to retrieve textbody on Exchange &lt; 2013
- Caldav: do not try to update etag if latest response item is empty
- Caldav: fix #679, invalid date exception on recurring event with an end date update
- Caldav: fix #346, map America/Chicago to Central Standard Time instead of Central America Standard Time

Enhancements:
- Drop redline library
- Disable tray on Gnome
- Drop platform specific Linux packages, drop SWT on windows, remove dist-rpm (user build.opensuse.org instead), upgrade SWT to 4.6 on Linux
- Upgrade htmlcleaner to 2.21, see https://bugs.debian.org/cgi-bin/bugreport.cgi?bug=891916
- Fix popMarkReadOnRetr setting save
- Update winrun4j wrappers

Linux:
- Refactor icon handling, automatically adjust color/size to match common default themes on Linux and add a new davmail.trayBackgroundColor setting to let users set their own theme color
- Make spec file compatible with RHEL 7 / Centos 7

Documentation:
- Doc: cleanup supported versions
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.8.4" date="2018-04-03">
      <description>
        <p>
The main change in this release is the new davmail.caldavAutoSchedule setting to let users choose between
client or server side calendar notification management. Most other fixes are also related to Caldav refactoring.

Caldav:
- Caldav: Add davmail.caldavAutoSchedule to GUI
- Caldav: introduce a new setting davmail.caldavAutoSchedule to enable or disable automatic scheduling in EWS mode
- Caldav: try to fix #674, do not send notifications on event update
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, avoid converting simple events to meetings
- Caldav: Restore calendar-schedule behavior in Webdav mode
- Caldav: in EWS mode, ignore urlcompname and always use itemid as item name, except if explicitly requested
- Caldav: isMeeting EWS flag is not reliable, check for attendees with displayto and displaycc
- Caldav: Fix isorganizer detection in deleteItem

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix regression on search NOT KEYWORD

Documentation:
- Documentation: fix typo in FAQ
- Doc: Improve Thunderbird LDAP documentation

Enhancements:
- EWS : cleanup from audit
- Exclude log files from build
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.8.3" date="2018-01-28">
      <description>
        <p>
More EWS Caldav refactoring, fix regressions noticed in 4.8.2 and merge a lot of user provided patches.
New calendar event handling is not yet enabled by default, please use davmail.caldavRealUpdate=true to 
check this new experimental implementation.

Caldav:
- Caldav: add cancelled translation
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, map status field, except CANCELLED not supported by Exchange
- Caldav: implement editable notifications on meeting cancel
- Caldav: do not send notifications if user canceled in edit dialog
- Caldav: Make sure we set all notification options on event update
- Caldav: Revert status conversion that triggers regressions and enable notifications on create
- Caldav: test multiline value handling in VCalendar
- Caldav: test case for loadVtimezone and searchTasksOnly
- Caldav: in loadVtimezone, delete existing temp folder first to avoid errors
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, make sure we send meeting notifications
- Caldav: fix #666 trailing &quot;nn&quot; added to tasks description synced from exchange
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, only update reminder info on meetings when not organizer
- Caldav: Fix meeting response body, send and save copy
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, implement edit notifications comment
- Caldav: fix task update regression

Enhancement:
- Merge #47, support soTimeout and connectionTimeout on exchange
- Merge patch #46: Maven patch to add resources in the target/davmail.jar
- Test: fix initial server and logging settings
- Copy release notes to dist on release
- Change test cases to load credentials from a separate test.properties file
- Remove old jsmooth config file
- Apply patch to fix #601 invalid davmail.server.certificate.hash format

Documentation:
- Doc: fix #320 Wrong link in documentation 

IMAP:
- IMAP: Accept US-ASCII as charset in search condition
- IMAP: fix #40 KEYWORD support for spring-integrations

OSX:
- OSX: Update universalJavaApplicationStub to 2.1.0

Windows:
- Windows: Create a 64 bits installer for windows

Carddav:
- Carddav: merge patch #44 Allow disabling reading photo from contact data
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.8.2" date="2018-01-02">
      <description>
        <p>
EWS Caldav refactoring in progress, enabled through new davmail.caldavRealUpdate setting
to avoid regressions as seen in 4.8.1.

Caldav:
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, handle mozilla alarm fields
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, implement modified occurrences
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, implement excluded dates (deleted occurrences)
- Caldav: optionally enable new EWS caldav implementation with davmail.caldavRealUpdate
- Caldav: Improve meeting response detection to avoid NullPointerException
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, implement reminder update
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.8.1" date="2017-12-12">
      <description>
        <p>
Last release before major EWS caldav refactoring, includes only the first behaviour change:
do not delete existing meeting on Accept/Decline, just send answer to organizer. Also includes
central directory photo handling in Carddav service, improved Java 9 support and many other
bug fixes.

Caldav:
- Caldav: temporarily disable EWS refactoring
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, implement multiple day recurrence and end date
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, first recurrence implementation step, improve ignore etag handling
- Caldav: EWS refactoring, manage attendees
- Caldav: prepare calendar refactoring, do not delete/add received meeting items, just send an Accept/Decline message
- Caldav: fix regression, busy status is case sensitive in EWS
- Caldav: fix #657 Tentative events shows as accepted in Thunderbird with user provided patch
- Caldav: experimental davmail.ignoreNoneMatchStar to let DavMail overwrite existing event automatically processed by Exchange.

Carddav:
- Carddav: implement get photo from Active Directory

Enhancements:
- update winrun4j wrappers
- Upgrade slf4j to 1.7.25 (patch #45)
- Fix 654: trim OWA/EWS url
- Ant: improve java version check
- Remove useless debug statement

Smartcard:
- Smartcard: improve Java 9 error handling, no longer need a temporary file
- Smartcard: try to implement code compatible with all java versions including Java 9

IMAP:
- IMAP: implement ON search filter
- IMAP: detect icedove header fetch to improve performance
- IMAP: make sure we never return null even with broken 0 uid message

POP:
- POP3: Improve documentation on trash/sent folders purge, change default value from 90 to 0 (disable)

Linux:
- Linux: check system tray with gtk_status_icon_get_geometry only with Unity to avoid regression with other window managers

SWT:
- SWT: wait 10s for tray icon to be created

OSX:
- OSX: fix Info.plist path
- OSX: fix JavaApplicationStub, do not expand folder classpath
- OSX: revert change to JavaX new key, does not work
- OSX: Update Info.plist to match new universalJavaApplicationStub
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.8.0" date="2017-03-23">
      <description>
        <p>
This new release includes a lot of fixes and enhancements from user feedback, including
improved Exchange categories handling, up to date TLS settings to match current requirements,
various Caldav enhancements, and a fix for a major bug on IMAP large message handling.
An experimental connection logging feature is also available.

Debian:
- Improve generated debian package to match official package, add keywords, move icon and adjust categories in desktop file

RPM:
- update RPM default config file
- Remove ant-antlr from spec file

Enhancement:
- Use Office365 url as default davmail.url value
- Remove Sun (Oracle) JDK dependency in unit test
- Experimental: compile Junit tests
- Change default url to https://outlook.office365.com/EWS/Exchange.asmx
- Log all connections disconnect
- Log all connections and logon success / failure
- Improve TLS settings: disable Client-initiated TLS renegotiation with jdk.tls.rejectClientInitiatedRenegotiation and force strong ephemeral Diffie-Hellman parameter with jdk.tls.ephemeralDHKeySize
- Remove sun.security.ssl.allowUnsafeRenegotiation=true system property as it&#x27;s hopefully no longer required by iCal
- Fix broken davmailservice64.exe

Documentation:
- Doc: document IMAP tags to Exchange categories custom mappings
- Doc: Add TLS settings documentation from support request #289
- Doc: fix maven generated site dash encoding

Caldav:
- Caldav: Fix #643 VTODO PRIORITY 0 fails, map it to Normal importance
- Caldav: accept all meeting item types in calendar (MeetingMessage, MeetingRequest, MeetingResponse, MeetingCancellation)
- Caldav: fix #639, task description is not visible in Thunderbird, try to get description from text body
- Caldav: fix #628, remove METHOD: PUBLISH from events retrieved from Exchange
- Caldav: make sure retrieved item name is always the same as requested item name (e.g. for tasks stored value ends with .EML when requested value ends with .ics)
- Caldav: Additional recurrence search test

IMAP:
- IMAP: flags to category conversion unit tests and make standard flags case insensitive
- IMAP: make IMAP flag to category lookup case insensitive
- IMAP: fix huge cache issue, chunk IMAP fetch triggers multiple full message download
- IMAP: fix regression after #41 IMAP wildcard LIST supportwith unit test
- IMAP: apply patch #41 IMAP wildcard LIST supportwith unit test
- IMAP: mark message seen only if unseen
- IMAP: fix #629 Read email doesn&#x27;t stay read. According to IMAP RFC: The \Seen flag is implicitly set
- IMAP: merge patch from #634, copy mail doesn&#x27;t preserve tag/category 
- IMAP: fix regression in mime message handling and rename mimeBody to mimeContent
- IMAP: Fix #633 Compatibility with javamail 1.5.6, store byte array instead of SharedByteArrayInputStream

Carddav:
- Carddav: do not send empty EmailAddresses collection tag

EWS:
- EWS: Change isrecurring property to PidLidRecurring (0x8223)
- EWS/Webdav: implement exists filter condition

SWT:
- SWT: Try to detect if system tray is indeed available

OSX:
- OSX: Update universalJavaApplicationStub to version 2.0.1
- OSX: Upgrade jarbundler to 3.3.0

SMTP:
- SMTP: append a line feed to avoid thunderbird message drop
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.7.3" date="2016-11-22">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bugfix release, mostly from user feedback. Also improve Windows installer to let users
choose whether they want to run DavMail automatically at logon.

Enhancement:
- Improve windows installer, make auto start at logon optional
- Update release guide with opensuse build env
- update icon cache
- Update winrun4j wrappers icon to 128x128

EWS:
- EWS: workaround for invalid cookie domain on Office365

DAV:
- DAV: merge patch from #232 Outlook-created appt does not go through. OWA-created one does

IMAP:
- IMAP: additional fix for #626, workaround for from: header not searchable over EWS
- IMAP: fix for #626, workaround for to: header not searchable over EWS

SMTP:
- SMTP: Merge patch 627 by Peter Chubb, server returns incorrect code on authentication failure
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.7.2" date="2016-04-09">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release, detect Exchange throttling to temporarily block requests and a few Carddav fixes.

EWS:
- EWS: handle Exchange throttling, suspend all requests according to server provided delay
- EWS: send DavMailException instead of authentication exception on EWS not available error

Enhancements:
- 128x128 DavMail icon
- Add a new davmail.httpMaxRedirects setting
- DAV: add a hidden davmail.disableNTLM setting

Carddav:
- Carddav: fix another regression on contact create with empty field
- Carddav: remove email over EWS unit test
- Carddav: fix email address removal over EWS
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.7.1" date="2015-12-19">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release, mainly for Carddav regression over EWS, also includes an NTLM support enhancement.

Enhancement:
- Improve NTLM support try to send hostname as workstation name instead of UNKNOWN
- Fix notification dialog message
- Prepare ExchangeSessionFactory refactoring
- Fix typo in french translation
- Fix broken Sourceforge link in About dialog

Carddav:
- Carddav: fix regression on contact update with empty field triggering DeleteItemField
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.7.0" date="2015-11-05">
      <description>
        <p>
This new release contains a lot of fixes from user feedback, a new -notray command line
option to force window mode and avoid tricky tray icon issues on Linux and native
smartcard support on Windows.

Caldav:
- Caldav: Map additional priority levels
- Caldav: fix missing LAST-MODIFIED in events

Enhancements:
- Improved tray icon with alpha blend
- Fix imports
- Prepare mutual SSL authentication between client and DavMail implementation
- Implement -notray command line option as a workaround for broken SWT and Unity issues
- Change warning messages to debug in close method
- Improve client certificate dialog, build description from certificate
- Exclude client certificates not issued by server provided issuers list

IMAP:
- IMAP: Additional translations and doc for new IMAP setting
- IMAP: Merge patch by Mauro Cicognini, add a new setting to always send approximate message in RFC822.SIZE to avoid downloading full message body
- IMAP: fix regression with quotes inside folder names
- IMAP: handle quotes inside folder names correctly

OSX:
- OSX link local address on loopback interface
- Exclude arguments starting with dash to avoid patch 38 regression on OSX

Documentation:
- Doc: Document -notray option
- Switch to OpenHub instead of Ohloh

EWS:
- EWS: prepare distribution list implementation
- Fix #254 davmail.exchange.ews.EWSException: ErrorIncorrectUpdatePropertyCount

Linux:
- Refresh davmail.spec, make RPM noarch
- Handle missing or broken SWT library

Windows:
- Windows: Make MSCAPI keystore type available in Settings for Windows native smartcard support
- Instantiate MSCAPI explicitly to access Windows Smartcards
- Enable native Windows SmartCard access through MSCAPI (no PKCS11 config required)

Carddav:
- Carddav: Test case for comma in ADR field
- Carddav: Do not replace comma on ADR field, see support request 255
- Caldav: Ignore missing END:VCALENDAR line on modified occurrences
- CardDav: Add empty property test case
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.6.2" date="2015-08-19">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bug fix release with some efforts on packaging.

Packaging:
- Compute distribution packages checksums
- Maven: set mimimum Maven version and fix FindBugs filter
- Maven: add Gtk lib in repo to avoid ClassNotFound
- Maven: exclude non DavMail classes from FindBugs report
- Maven: Update POM to Maven 3
- Separate prepare-dist ant task
- Separate jar ant task
- RPM: Change log for 4.6.1 and remove ant-nodeps dependency for Fedora &gt;=19 compatibility
- RPM: first step to a noarch package, externalize SWT dependency
- RPM: Add rcdavmail link, mark logrotate config file
- RPM: Fix License and URL

Enhancements:
- Fix davmailconsole.exe
- Switch to TLS in DavGatewaySSLProtocolSocketFactory
- Improve refresh folder logic, ctag stamp is limited to second, check message count
- Try to support Citrix NetScaler authentication form
- Improve Java version check
- Update compile level to 1.6
- Remove unneeded catch section

WebDav:
- DAV: avoid NullPointerException trying to access Exchange 2013 in Dav mode

IMAP:
- IMAP: refactor IMAP test cases
- IMAP: ignore Draft flag on update, Draft is readonly after create
- IMAP: fix new IMAP tokenizer
- IMAP: rewrite tokenizer to manage quoted folder names and complex search
- IMAP: Fix #591 Properly escape quotes in folder names
- IMAP: additional IMAP test cases

EWS:
- EWS: davmail.enableChunkedRequest default value is now false, as IIS does not support chunked requests
- EWS: Make chunked content optional in CreateItemMethod with new davmail.enableChunkedRequest property
- Use EWS path in davmail.properties template file

Doc:
- Doc: add Indicator SystemtrayUnity to linux doc
- Fix Javadoc

OSX:
- OSX: merge patch 38, allow commandline options to run multiple instances.

SMTP:
- SMTP: use content chunk to send large messages
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.6.1" date="2015-02-17">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release to fix recent regression with Office 365,
also includes a few Linux and IMAP enhancements.

Linux:
- RPM: exclude Growl library from RPM package
- Add genericname to desktop entry
- RPM: Fix warning the init script refers to runlevel 4 which is admin defined. No distribution script must use it
- Detect and log message for Unity users
- RPM: Fix JAVA HOME detection for openSUSE_13.2
- RPM: update spec file from OpenSuse build by Dmitri Bachtin and  Achim Herwig

SWT:
- SWT: improve tray init, preload image and add a delay on first message

Enhancements:
- Add a few more logging statements

IMAP:
- Fix #36 Endless loop when using IMAP IDLE feature with SSL sockets, replaced thread sleep with a short timeout on socket read

EWS:
- EWS: update checkEndPointUrl, send get root folder request instead of static wsdl request no longer available on Office365
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.6.0" date="2015-01-27">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release with many IMAP enhancements over EWS, implement batch move items,
also includes a brand new generic OSX package to handle new OSX java behaviour.

OSX:
- OSX: refactor OSX package based on universalJavaApplicationStub
- Replace Java application stub with https://github.com/tofi86/universalJavaApplicationStub/blob/master/src/universalJavaApplicationStub

Doc:
- Doc: update OSX setup documentation
- Doc: additional Linux instructions for Ubuntu 14
- Fix #31 A typo in davmail.properties example

EWS:
- EWS: improve main calendar folder test
- EWS: fix batch move
- EWS: Adjust paged search for folders
- EWS: implement batch move items
- EWS: improve folder paged search
- Prepare batch move implementation
- EWS: force NTLM in direct EWS mode
- EWS: implement batch move method
- EWS: switch to GetMethod to check endpoint
- EWS: take paging into account in appendSubFolders
- EWS: fix ErrorExceededFindCountLimit on FindFolder requests
- EWS: avoid NullPointerException in fixAttendees

Linux:
- Allow Java 8 and default jre in debian package

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix 587 log and skip broken messages

Caldav
- Caldav: fix #98 Support of Contacts in CardDav REPORT 
- Fix #35 duplicates in updated reoccurring events 

Enhancements
- Fix potential CVE-2014-3566 vulnerability
- From audit: remove throws statement
- Adjust KerberosHelper logging message
- Fix for #534 Kerberos Authentication doesn&#x27;t seem to be work cross domain

LDAP:
- LDAP: reset icon after search
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.5.1" date="2014-07-20">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release to fix Exchange 2013 regressions and wrong Europe/London timezone mapping.

DAV:
- DAV: Another email address failover

Caldav:
- Caldav: Fix GMT Standard Time mapping to Europe/London
- More timezones
- Caldav: do not request additional properties for MeetingCancellation and MeetingResponse
- Caldav: merge 33, apply myresponsetype partstat on all Exchange versions
- Caldav: fix 569 and patch 32, avoid NullPointerException with Exchange 2013

EWS:
- EWS: Avoid null in log message

Enhancements:
- Merge patch 34: Fix false positive when searching for user alias and email 

Doc:
- Update FAQ on EWS endpoint not available error
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.5.0" date="2014-06-03">
      <description>
        <p>
Includes EWS performance enhancements, improved Exchange 2013 support and many fixes detected by Coverity audit tool

EWS:
- EWS: adjust declined item handling
- EWS: used paged search with static search condition, send a single request when folderSizeLimit is enabled
- EWS: Allow Item and PostItem elements in message folders
- EWS: Improve Exchange 2013 support
- EWS: avoid mime content String conversion
- EWS: Improve javadoc and make ItemId serializable
- EWS: expect UTF-8 in options responses
- EWS: remove unused field
- EWS: Force encoding in mimeContent decode
- EWS: Avoid /owa form request in direct EWS mode

Documentation:
- Add davmail.defaultDomain to template properties file
- Doc: Change default port in Thunderbird directory config screenshot
- Update settings image

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix 564, Moving / copying messages in public mailbox 
- IMAP: implement separate thread folder load on STATUS request to avoid client timeouts
- IMAP: fix 209, use isEqualTo instead of contains to search keywords on Exchange 2010
- IMAP : various enhancements from audit, switch to enum and avoid NullPointerException

OSX:
- OSX: force working directory to application root

Enhancements:
- Upgrade svnkit to 1.8
- Update WinRun4J wrappers
- Upgrade WinRun4J to 0.4.5
- Kerberos: make sure access to client login context is synchronized
- Kerberos: synchronize access to clientLoginContext
- Make MessageWrapper static
- Revert Java 7 only changes
- Do not try WebDav mode if owa url ends with /ews/exchange.asmx
- Additional code fixes from audit, do not try to get time zone from options page in direct EWS mode
- Force encoding in message create thread
- Prepare WoodStox Xml10AllowAllEscapedChars setting implementation
- Apply Base64 refactoring to all classes
- Apply new base64 methods to CaldavConnection
- Refactor base64 encode/decode methods
- Improve contact picture error handling
- Improve session factory log statements
- Avoid null in log statement
- New experimental davmail.exchange.maxConnections setting to limit concurrent connections to Exchange server

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix bug in VCalendar dtend check

POP:
- Refactor PopConnection, use enumeration instead of int

Coverity:
- From coverity: listFiles may return null
- From coverity: avoid null dereference in VProperty
- From coverity: avoid null dereference in getFolderPath
- From coverity: check null image in FrameGatewayTray
- From coverity: more encoding fixes
- From coverity: synchronize HttpClient cookies access
- From coverity: synchronize FileAppender creation
- From coverity: URI.getPath may return null
- From coverity: ImageIO.read may return null
- From coverity: trayItem.getImage may return null
- From coverity: client.getInetAddress() may return null
- From coverity: createSaslServer may return null
- From coverity: use UTF-8 encoding in Hex conversion methods
- From coverity: force encoding to UTF-8 on socket output stream
- From coverity: set encoding on String to bytes conversion
- From coverity: use getParamValue instead of getParam().getValue() to avoid null dereference
- From coverity: editor pane font can be null
- From coverity: check null after ImageIO.read

UI:
- UI: small fixes on ui code from audit
- Refactor SWT tray dispose management on exit
- Handle missing resource in loadSwtImage

DAV:
- DAV: decode base64 content as ASCII
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.4.1" date="2014-01-30">
      <description>
        <p>
Includes mostly EWS support enhancements, Sogo carddav issue workaround, new
IMAP uid based paging implementation to handle concurrent folder changes
and a few other bug fixes.

Documentation:
- Doc: update donation link to let user choose currency
- Doc: Update iCal Caldav setup for OSX Mavericks
- Doc: update server setup documentation, use noinstall package on Windows
- Doc: Update news url in release guide

EWS:
- EWS: workaround for user reported issue, less strict filter in isItemId
- EWS: Override authentication mode test: EWS is never form based
- EWS: new paging implementation based on imap uid sort to avoid issues on concurrent changes on searched folder
- EWS: in direct EWS mode, try to use ResolveNames to get current user email address
- EWS: Another try for checkEndPointUrl, head on /ews/exchange.asmx and follow redirects to wsdl
- EWS: improve ItemId vs user provided item name detection

Enhancements
- From coverity: avoid null dereference when no network interface is available
- From coverity: set encoding on byte array to String conversion
- From coverity: fix resource leak
- Update svnant libraries
- Fix reauthentication issue: separate domain from username in credentials
- Fix NullPointerException in thread &quot;Shutdown&quot; - tray disposal - server mode
- Fix authentication failure after session expiration

Caldav:
- Caldav: Fix 555 another broken Israeli timezone
- Caldav: ignore invalid BEGIN line inside object (Sogo Carddav issue)
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.4.0" date="2013-11-13">
      <description>
        <p>
Added folder size limit setting to let users avoid IMAP timeouts and reduce memory footprint.
Also contains many documentation updates, including updated OSX instructions for Mavericks and
some more bugfixes on IMAP, Caldav (iOS 7 user agent) and SMTP.

Documentation:
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: reference Marcin Dulak as contributor (RPM package maintainer)
- Doc: Document OSX Mavericks IMAP account creation
- Doc: improve FAQ
- Doc: Fix OSX download instructions
- Doc: Update OSX doc
- Doc: additional FAQ comment on shared calendar hierarchy
- Doc: update smtp screenshot
- Doc: update more Thunderbird screenshots
- Doc: update Lightning screenshots
- Doc: document calendar.caldav.sched.enabled in main Lightning setup doc

Enhancements:
- Additional IMAP unit tests
- Add davmail.folderSizeLimit to UI and documentation
- Fix AbstractConnection.readContent, see https://sourceforge.net/p/davmail/bugs/538/

SMTP:
- SMTP: create a new davmail.smtpStripFrom boolean property to force From: header removal 

IMAP:
- IMAP: Make flags case insensitive on append
- IMAP: improve uidNext implementation
- Italian IMAP flag translation thanks to puntogil@libero.it
- IMAP: fix 538, send capabilities untagged response to avoid timeout on large message APPEND
- IMAP: Implement davmail.folderSizeLimit

Caldav:
- Caldav: change user agent test to include all iOS versions
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.3.4" date="2013-09-09">
      <description>
        <p>
Added a new OSX Java7 package, IMAP header management regression fixes.
Also fixed a few bugs reported by users and improved documentation.

Documentation:
- Doc: Reference Alexandre Rossi as Debian package maintainer
- Doc: Update FAQ shared mailbox path
- Doc: update svn repository location in build doc
- Force language on donations link
- Doc: OSX LaunchDaemon

Enhancements:
- Add trust=&quot;true&quot; to scp command
- Italian translation from  gil cattaneo https://bugzilla.redhat.com/show_bug.cgi?id=894413
- Allow identical username/userid in multiple factor authentication form
- Rethrow DavMailException on connect exception
- Fix NullPointerException on server unavailable
- New experimental davmail.popCommonDeleted flag to switch to a different property on old Exchange 2003 servers

Caldav:
- Caldav: flag ORGANIZER participant status as ACCEPTED instead of NEEDS-ACTION
- Caldav: do not overwrite X-MICROSOFT-CDO-BUSYSTATUS if TRANSP is not provided
- Merge patch to set sensitivy on VTODO

OSX:
- OSX: Get application path from library path with Java7 launcher
- OSX: move libgrowl to library path
- OSX: build Java 7 package
- Customized OSX app launcher messages
- Java7 OSX app launcher

EWS:
- EWS: fix 537, detect 507 Insufficient Storage

WebDav:
- DAV: set SO timeout on connection

IMAP:
- IMAP: new header fix, do not rely on messageheaders attribute on full headers request, load message
- IMAP: improve invalid message header test
- IMAP: fix invalid message header filter
- IMAP: write message without headers on BODY[TEXT] fetch
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.3.3" date="2013-06-13">
      <description>
        <p>
Make keep alive optional new davmail.enableKeepalive setting and fix regressions in IMAP handler.

Enhancements:
- Update Maven POM to new Sourceforge project site
- Rename new setting to davmail.enableKeepalive and include in settings GUI

IMAP:
- IMAP: make keepalive spaces optional with new davmail.imapEnableKeepalive setting
- IMAP: interrupt EWS folder load on client timeout
- IMAP: fix missing headers with Outlook
- IMAP: Detect invalid content in message header field
- IMAP: skip Microsoft Mail Internet Headers Version 2.0 in message headers field
- IMAP: remove additional logging
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.3.2" date="2013-06-06">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bugfix release.

IMAP: Fix regression on IMAP select folder with thunderbird
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.3.1" date="2013-06-05">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release to fix regressions with some IMAP clients and enhanced FetchMail support.

OSX:
- OSX: switch back to single archive and add a comment

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix double header content and optimize header fetch with Fetchmail
- IMAP: fix regression in append envelope
- IMAP: fix multithreaded folder load implementation to support more IMAP clients

POP:
- POP: fix 3613743, remove additional +OK during message RETR

Linux:
- dos2unix on davmail.spec
- Update davsvn
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.3.0" date="2013-05-21">
      <description>
        <p>
New keep alive mechanism to avoid most IMAP and POP client timeouts: load large messages
in a separate thread and send a character on client connection every ten seconds. Also
includes some bug fixes, documentation enhancements and experimental Exchange 2013 support.

OSX:
- OSX: Add a readme.txt file to OSX package to help users temporarily disable Gatekeeper

Documentation:
- Doc: improve OSX setup doc for Mountain Lion
- Update SSL doc, spaces in library path may break Sun PKCS11
- Update linux setup doc for Ubuntu 13 users
- Update server setup doc with detailed davmail.properties file

Caldav:
- Caldav: New workaround for Lightning bug: sleep for 1 second on server unavailable error

IMAP:
- Interrupt message load thread on client connection exception
- IMAP: try to avoid timeout on large message FETCH with a KeepAlive space character
- IMAP: try to avoid timeout on folder SELECT with a KeepAlive space character
- Improve message list count implementation
- Always sort by IMAP uid desc

POP:
- POP: load big messages in a separate thread

EWS:
- EWS: Fix regression in checkEndPointUrl, get /ews/services.wsdl
- Fix for Exchange 2013 support
- EWS: implement SortOrder

Enhancements:
- Improve DavMail shell scripts
- Set default file path to /var/log/davmail.log in reference davmail.properties
- Set a default log file size in reference davmail.properties
- Use reference davmail.properties in war file
- Disable broken dist-rpm
- Reference server davmail.properties file
- Add disableUpdateCheck to default davmail.properties file
- Exclude WinRun4J from debian package
- Exclude libgrowl and winrun4J from war package
- Exclude winrun4J from linux packages
- Set davmail.logFileSize to 0 to use an external rotation mechanism, e.g. logrotate
- Merge latest changes from Marcin Dulak
- Archive jsmooth wrappers
- Fix version in spec file
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.2.1" date="2013-04-11">
      <description>
        <p>
Improved Kerberos support and a few bug fixes reported on tracker.

Kerberos:
- Add enable Kerberos checkbox to DavMail GUI
- Kerberos read KRB5CCNAME environment variable to set ticket cache path
- Kerberos implement graphical callback on missing token
- Kerberos: Renew almost expired tickets and detect expired TGT in cache =&gt; try to relogin 
- Kerberos: Handle client context timeout, try to recreate context
- Improve KerberosHelper implementation, prepare credential delegation support

Enhancements:
- Try to fix 3606267: New debian dependency with wrong package name
- Fix 3602588, allow oracle-java7-jre
- Fix regression: disable console appender in gui mode
- Use NewIbmX509 on IBM JDK instead of NewSunX509 SSL algorithm implementation
- Fix 3602351, detect missing item

EWS:
- EWS: do not catch socket exception in executeMethod
- EWS: workaround for Nokia N9 Caldav implementation bug

DAV:
- DAV: throw error on broken connection

SMTP:
- SMTP: do not allow send as another user on Exchange 2003

IMAP:
- IMAP: exclude Mutt header request from size optimization
- IMAP: change kerberos login error message
- IMAP send error on authentication failed

Documentation:
- Doc: Additional Kerberos documentation
- Initial Kerberos documentation

Caldav:
- Caldav: do not send 401 on authentication error in Kerberos mode
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.2.0" date="2013-02-26">
      <description>
        <p>
Contains some enhancements on iOS 6 support, Debian package encoding issue fix
and partial Kerberos support (workstation mode) to provide transparent Exchange
authentication.

Kerberos:
- Kerberos: implement server side security context and token handling
- Kerberos: server side login module
- Improve Kerberos logging and implement command line callback
- Do not set preemptive authentication in Kerberos mode
- Enable Kerberos authentication scheme with davmail.enableKerberos setting
- Kerberos authentication implementation: SpNegoScheme to implement Negotiate authentication scheme, KerberosHelper to handle ticket access and KerberosLoginConfiguration to replace JAAS configuration file

Enhancements:
- Fix accept certificate message
- Make davmail.sh executable in platform independent package
- Update desktop entry comment
- Update RPM spec file from build.opensuse.org (marcindulak)
- Add libswt-cairo-gtk-3-jni to debian package dependencies
- Clear cookies created by authentication test
- Upgrade jackrabbit-webdav and htmlcleaner in davmailconsole wrapper
- Upgrade jackrabbit-webdav to 2.4.3
- Upgrade htmlcleaner to 2.2
- Exclude Jsmooth, nsi, OSX and contribs (with binary) from source only package
- Prepare source only package

Bugfix:
- Check file encoding in build file
- Refactor StringUtil and encode ~ in urlcompname

IMAP:
- IMAP: Implement custom IMAP flags to keywords mapping in settings

Caldav:
- Caldav: add iOS6 user agent
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.1.0" date="2012-09-26">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release with improved IMAP support, including IMAP flags mapping to Outlook categories,
enhanced IMAP noop/idle support, fixed emClient Caldav support and many Caldav and EWS fixes.

Documentation:
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: new FAQ entry, Exchange RSA two factor authentication form

Caldav:
- Caldav: do not try to load tasks MIME body
- Caldav: workaround for 3569922: quick fix for broken Israeli Timezone issue
- Caldav: remove urlencoding workaround for emClient &gt;= 4
- Caldav: Ignore 401 unauthorized on public event, return 200
- Caldav: Rename TZID also in RECURRENCE-ID
- Caldav: force 403 forbidden instead of 401 on unauthorized update to public folder item
- Caldav: Fix 3569934 NullPointerException on broken PROPFIND request
- Caldav: Fix 3567364, regression on from/to/cc handling in calendar related to IMAP search enhancement. Separate mapping for message fields/headers

IMAP:
- IMAP: send updated flags on folder refresh
- IMAP: fix keyword handling to avoid sending \Seen as keyword
- IMAP: retrieve message count on folder
- IMAP: apply flag to keyword conversion in SEARCH, refresh folder before search
- IMAP: improve keyword support, map $label1 to 5 from Thunderbird to Outlook categories
- IMAP: fix keywords implementation, make it case insensitive, implement KEYWORD search
- IMAP: implement generic FLAGS mapping to Outlook categories
- IMAP: fix 3566412, range iterator is on folder messages, not messages returned from search

EWS:
- EWS: Get primary smtp email address with ResolveNames in direct EWS mode

Enhancements:
- Allow Java 7 to build DavMail
- Prepare message keywords/categories support

WebDav:
- Dav: implement multivalued property suppord in ExchangeDavMethod

Web:
- Web: Fix 3566941 Imap protocol is not activated by default in .war
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="4.0.0" date="2012-09-10">
      <description>
        <p>
Includes full Exchange 2007 and 2010 support with EWS implementation, 
fixed OSX Mountain Lion support, switched Windows wrappers to WinRun4J 
and additional enhancements and bugfixes.

IMAP:
- IMAP: workaround for broken message headers on Exchange 2010
- IMAP: log content if less than 2K
- IMAP: improve Exchange 2010 header search, use direct header names to implement substring search on some headers
- IMAP: additional fix for Exchange 2010 header search, use PR_TRANSPORT_MESSAGE_HEADERS
- IMAP: Exchange 2010 does not support header search, workaround to avoid duplicate items in Drafts folder with Thunderbird
- IMAP: fix 3553942, unexpected imap NIL response
- IMAP: detect and ignore missing message to avoid NullPointerException
- IMAP: improve bodystructure error handling

Documentation:
- Doc: fix image swap
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: add Developed with Intellij Idea link

Caldav:
- Caldav: encode semicolon in urlcompname
- Caldav: fix attendees in modified occurences
- Caldav: additional timezone names for Exchange 2010
- Caldav: additional timezones available in Exchange 2007
- Caldav: Partial fix for missing items on Exchange 2010
- Caldav: fix OSX Mountain Lion (iCal 6) support

Enhancement:
- Merge patch 3488553: Make davmail.jar executable
- Merge patch from 3562031, advanced noProxyFor handling
- Display released version in about frame when different from current version
- Fix 3562031, implement davmail.noProxyFor setting to exclude hosts from proxy settings
- Merge preauthentication page patch
- Prepare pre authentication page merge in ExchangeSession
- Implement javascript redirect in executeFollowRedirects
- Prepare javascript redirect merge (multiple authentication pages)
- Try to improve shutdown hook

Windows:
- Update download url in 64 bit wrappers to http://java.com/en/download/manual.jsp
- Add davmailservice64.exe WinRun4J service wrapper
- Replace 64 bits jsmoothgen with WinRun4J wrapper
- 64 bits Winrun4J wrapper
- Fix Winrun4J service wrapper implementation, launch a non daemon thread
- Win: switch to Winrun4J wrappers

OSX:
- OSX: Add a note on Gatekeeper for OSX Mountain Lion users

EWS:
- EWS: fix davmail.acceptEncodingGzip setting handling
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.9" date="2012-07-10">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release with major IMAP changes to improve sync performance,
many Caldav enhancements and bugfixes and some documentation updates.

Caldav:
- Caldav: encode ? in urlcompname
- Caldav: fix 3534615, patch allday dates only on Exchange 2007
- Caldav: implement full contact folder dump at /users/&lt;email&gt;/contacts/
- Caldav: implement task priority over EWS
- Caldav: remove unsupported attachment reference to avoid iPhone/iPad crash
- Caldav: reintroduce davmail.caldavDisableTasks setting to disable tasks support
- Caldav: fix encode pipe | to %7C in urlcompname
- Caldav: encode pipe | to %7C in urlcompname
- CalDav: Fix 3512857, avoid double path encoding in DavExchangeSession.loadVtimezone()
- Caldav: improve Exchange 2007 EWS meeting support
- Caldav: rebuild meeting attendees only for Exchange 2007, Exchange 2010 ics parser is correct

Enhancements:
- Fixes from audit
- store davmail.log in user home folder to avoid crash on first start when current directory is not writable by user
- Add WinRun4J to Maven POM and update windows service documentation
- Switch to WinRun4J for Windows service wrapper
- Fix 3494770: Add missing antlr runtime
- Upgrade svnkit for subversion 1.7 compatibility

IMAP:
- IMAP: Fix 3534801, workaround for missing From header
- IMAP: fix 3441891, workaround for Exchange 2003 ActiveSync bug
- IMAP: experimental implementation of header only FETCH, do not download full message content and send approximate RFC822.SIZE (MAPI size)
- IMAP: avoid full message download on OSX Lion flags request with content-class header
- IMAP: exclude IDLE from infinite loop detection
- IMAP: add date header to rebuilt message
- IMAP: Force UTF-8 on message rebuild
- IMAP: implement RFC822 fetch request

GUI:
- GUI: force alwaysOnTop on dialogs to make sure they are visible
- GUI: always bring dialog windows to front

Documentation:
- Doc: add a new FAQ entry on shared mailbox access over IMAP
- Doc: Update doc to include Java 7
- Doc: small fix in Linux setup doc
- Doc: Update Linux instructions for Ubuntu 12 Natty
- Doc: New review
- Doc: update Thunderbird POP account setup doc
- Doc: Update SSL setup documentation on PKCS12 passwords
- Doc: add a note on hidden folders on OSX Lion
- Doc: Fix new thunderbird doc

OSX:
- OSX: new hide from Dock setting available directly in UI (DavMail restart needed)

Carddav:
- Carddav: Fix 3511472, implement fileas over EWS
- Carddav: Skip carriage return in ICSBufferedWriter

EWS:
- EWS: disable gzip encoding if WIRE logging is at DEBUG level
- EWS: fix 3263905 ErrorInvalidPropertyRequest, do not update message:IsRead on appointments
- EWS: make isMainCalendar case insensitive
- EWS: revert chunked inputstream inside gzip and create new setting davmail.acceptEncodingGzip
- EWS: handle chunked inputstream inside gzip
- EWS: improve error message handling, log error description
- EWS: improve error handling on socket exception
- EWS: avoid NullPointerException in broken message rebuild

WebDav:
- Dav: decode permanenturl to avoid double urlencoding issue
- Dav: decode url returned on saveappt cmd in DavExchangeSession.loadVtimezone()
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.8" date="2012-02-21">
      <description>
        <p>
Prepare 4.0 release with improved Exchange 2010 support, added IMAP MOVE extension support,
include a new windows noinstall package and implement captcha authentication support.

Documentation:
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: add a statement on adding NSIS to system path in build instructions
- Doc: update Thunderbird IMAP setup instructions for Thunderbird 10
- Doc: update java package reference
- Doc: update address book setup instructions for OSX Lion
- Doc: add Growl reference in OSX setup

Enhancements:
- Fix nsis script: delete stax api jar on uninstall
- Fixes from audit
- New redline ant task definition fix
- Exclude Junit from binary packages
- Create Windows noinstall package
- Implement a new davmail.clientSoTimeout setting to adjust or disable connection timeout
- Improve message on invalid OWA uri
- Fix notification dialog test
- Improve Pinsafe captcha display
- workaround for broken form with empty action
- Implement ISA server PINsafeISAFilter support (captcha image)
- Upgrade Redline RPM
- Add StreamScanner.java from Woodstox 4.1.2
- Upgrade to Woodstox 4.1.2
- Fix 3454332: davmail.sh script missing shebang 
- add trust=true in upload-site

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix search date format for Exchange 2010 support (ErrorInvalidValueForProperty)
- IMAP: implement SEARCH TEXT on from, to, cc, subject and body
- IMAP: send error on COPY/MOVE when message iterator is empty
- IMAP: implement MOVE RFC draft http://tools.ietf.org/id/draft-krecicki-imap-move-00.html
- IMAP: fix 3480516, () instead of NIL on empty envelope header
- IMAP: Fix 3479993, backslash in header

SMTP:
- SMTP: fix 3489007, Sparrow AUTH PLAIN authentication support

Caldav:
- Caldav: force context Timezone on Exchange 2010
- Caldav: add missing timezones from Exchange 2007 over WebDav
- Caldav: let users edit outgoing notifications for meeting requests
- Caldav: fix NullPointerException on addressbook request
- Caldav: workaround for broken items with \n as first line character

POP:
- POP: add a new setting to mark messages read after RETR

EWS:
- EWS: fix ErrorInvalidValueForProperty on search undeleted with Exchange 2010, set type Integer on PidLidImapDeleted and junk 0x1083
- EWS: new fix to improve failover on error retrieving MimeContent
- EWS: improve failover on error retrieving MimeContent
- EWS: Fix 3471671, workaround for Exchange invalid chars

LDAP:
- LDAP: improve invalid dn message

OSX:
- OSX: make nodock mode the default
- OSX: make sure davmail.jar is first in classpath

DAV:
- Dav: set contact email type to SMTP
- Dav: add email type MAPI properties

Carddav:
- Carddav: avoid NullPointerException on broken contact
- Carddav: fix regression on address book handling on Snow Leopard
- Carddav: decode urlcompname before search to retrieve contacts with &amp; in url
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.7" date="2012-01-10">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bugfix release with new stax based webdav search method implementation to reduce memory footprint with large folders,
exclude non event items from calendar to avoid errors, some EWS fixes on tasks handling and a few documentation updates

WebDav:
- Dav: fix regression in new Stax implementation
- Dav: new stax based WebDav requests implementation to reduce memory usage, enabled on Search requests
- Dav: switch back to mailbox path on Exchange 2003 for CmdBasePath

Caldav:
- Caldav: Experimental patch to support spaces in calendar or contacts path on OSX, see 3464086
- Caldav: Create a new davmail.caldavEnableLegacyTasks to allow access to tasks created in calendar folder by previous DavMail versions
- Caldav: drop davmail.caldavDisableTasks setting, retrieve only events from calendar
- Caldav: Change field update order for Exchange 2007 over EWS
- Caldav: apply date filter to tasks
- Caldav: new timezone for Mexico
- Caldav: fix 3433584, encode comma in LOCATION field

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix double slash in folder path
- IMAP: return all search results uids on a single line for Wanderlust
- IMAP: new davmail.imapIncludeSpecialFolders setting to access all folders including calendar and tasks over IMAP
- IMAP: fix wanderlust support, allow lower case fetch params

Documentation:
- Doc: Added DavMail hangs on 64-bit Linux FAQ entry
- Doc: add documentation for davmail.logFileSize option

Enhancements:
- Change default use system proxies value to false
- Avoid NullPointerException on WebdavNotAvailableException
- Fix upload-version target site

EWS:
- EWS: fix Exchange 2010 SP1 support
- EWS: use archivemsgfolderroot as archive root
- EWS: enable preemptive authentication on non NTLM endpoints
- EWS: add Exchange2010_SP1 support for online archive

LDAP:
- LDAP: avoid NullPointerException during SASL authentication

Carddav:
- Carddav: encode star in urlcompname
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.6" date="2011-10-30">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bugfix release to improve iPad 2 and Debian based Linux support. 
Also includes new protocol mode options (EWS, WebDav or Auto), experimental Exchange online archive 
support, IMAP UTF-8 search parameter and many Caldav fixes

Enhancements:
- Add a new upload-version ant target to upload version.txt
- Workaround for broken servers that send invalid Basic authentication challenge
- Add exchangecookie to the list of authentication cookies for direct EWS access
- Add a new auto value to davmail.enableEws setting to avoid unwanted switch from WebDav to EWS on temporary Exchange connection issue
- Encode # in urlcompname
- Fix bug on ITEM_PROPERTIES value on EWS/WebDav mode switch
- Add new Default button to reset log levels
- Implement a new option to let users disable all GUI notifications
- Additional exception trace exclusion 
- Revert 1.7 test on SWT, tray implementation is still broken on Linux

Documentation:
- Doc: reformat urls in FAQ
- Doc: add a note to help users with broken Unity desktop manager on Ubuntu
- Doc: Fix typo in project description
- Doc: additional note on Caldav setup in Thunderbird and new external review
- Doc: document new disable balloon notifications setting
- Doc: Update roadmap
- Doc: New reviews
- Doc: Update iCal doc to match both Snow Leopard and Lion
- Doc: Update FAQ
- Doc: Update DavMail settings screenshot

Linux
- Allow openjdk-7-jre dependency in deb package 
- Fix 3418960: Update dependencies for Ubuntu 11.10, add libswt-gtk-3-java

Caldav:
- Caldav: apply iCal 5 workaround to iOS 5
- Caldav: new timezone in rename table
- Caldav: try to merge Exchange 2010 and 2007 filters
- Caldav: additional unit tests
- Caldav: fix 3426148 decode and encode comma in RESOURCES field value
- Caldav: Fix complex timezones sent by clients, leave only latest STANDARD and DAYLIGHT definition
- Caldav: Fix 3420240, retrieve description from tasks over Dav

EWS:
- EWS: add new DistinguishedFolderId value for Exchange archive support
- EWS: throw exception on 400 Bad request answer

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix 3426383, implement CHARSET in SEARCH command, allow ASCII and UTF-8
- IMAP: fix 3353862, long file names encoding in BODYSTRUCTURE

SMTP:
- SMTP: adjust workaround for misconfigured Exchange server that return 406 Not Acceptable on draft message creation, look inside multipart messages
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.5" date="2011-10-03">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release to avoid Growl plugin crash on OSX, make DavMail work with both
Snow Leopard and Lion. Also includes DIGEST-MD5 implementation for OSX Lion
Directory Utility support, however iCal attendee completion is still broken.

OSX:
- Fix crash in Growl plugin on OSX: do not sent SSL content to Growl

EWS:
- EWS: rebuild broken message (null MimeContent) from properties
- EWS: improve error logging on invalid character
- EWS: fix tasks field order, send Extended Properties first to match EWS schema
- EWS: replace extension before looking for items in task folder
- EWS: Fix 3407395, do not set mailbox on FolderIds returned by Exchange

LDAP:
- LDAP: fix DIGEST-MD5 authentication and adjust dn context for OSX Lion, still experimental
- LDAP: fix DIGEST-MD5 SASL authentication for OSX Lion
- LDAP: experimental SASL DIGEST-MD5 implementation for OSX Lion Directory Utility support

Caldav:
- Caldav: need to send principal-URL on principal path, only for OSX Lion
- Caldav: allow direct access to task folder

Enhancements:
- Force toFront and requestFocus to bring windows to front
- Additional proxy selector logging
- Fixes from audit
- Upgrade Log4J to 1.2.16

Documentation
- Doc: Add saveInSent reference in FAQ
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.4" date="2011-09-13">
      <description>
        <p>
First release with full Exchange tasks (VTODO) support, automatically convert VTODOs to tasks
inside default task folder. Also includes many bugfixes on iCal OSX Snow Leopard support
(note: need to recreate the calendar to fix sync), mixed Exchange 2010/2003 architecture support and
IMAP DRAFT and UNDRAFT search condition support

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix regression
- Caldav: implement update folder
- Caldav: fix regression on Snow Leopard
- Caldav: more general fix for misconfigured Exchange server, replace host name in url also over Caldav
- Caldav: additional fix for CRLF in urlcompname
- Caldav: additional task fields over EWS and fix urlcompname decoding
- Caldav: implement task categories over EWS
- Caldav: update additional MAPI properties for tasks
- Caldav: implement startdate and duedate on tasks
- Caldav: implement task categories
- Caldav: Need to encode % in urlcompname
- Caldav: implement task percent complete and status over WebDav
- Caldav: improve task support over WebDav, rename .ics to .EML and implement priority (importance)
- Caldav: do not try to get ICS content from tasks
- Caldav: encode @ in path only for iCal 5 (OSX Lion)
- Caldav: implement supported-report-set

Enhancements:
- Do not always log stacktrace in handleNetworkDown
- Fix IllegalArgumentException in fixClientHost when scheme is null
- Temporary fix: log exception stack trace in handleNetworkDown
- Temporary fix: log exception in handleNetworkDown
- Another init script
- Small failover fix
- Improve client host update fix
- Test various event count

IMAP:
- IMAP: implement DRAFT and UNDRAFT search conditions, fix 3396248
- IMAP: fix failover for misconfigured Exchange server, replace host name in url
- IMAP: fix regression in EwsExchangeSession.createMessage
- IMAP: Fix 3383832, set ItemClass to send read receipt over EWS to avoid ErrorObjectTypeChanged 

EWS:
- EWS: Allow null value in StringUtil.decodeUrlcompname
- EWS: use isrecurring with Exchange 2010 and instancetype with Exchange 2007
- EWS: revert 3317867 XML1.1 header workaround to fix 3385308

DAV:
- Dav: check checkPublicFolder calls
- Dav: Avoid returning null in getCmdBasePath

Documentation:
- Doc: fix OSX iCal setup documentation for OSX Lion

LDAP:
- LDAP: send error on DIGEST-MD5 bind request
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.3" date="2011-07-31">
      <description>
        <p>
New release with improved iCal 5 (OSX Lion) support, partial VTODO conversion to Outlook tasks
 and many other bugfixes including event move item url encoding and event filter over EWS fix

Caldav:
- Caldav: new fix for @ encoding
- Caldav: fix regression, do not encode @ in calendar-user-address-set
- Caldav: fix principal-URL response
- Caldav: encode @ in current-user-principal
- Caldav: force @ encode to %40 for iCal 5
- Caldav: new CRLF in urlcompname patch for EWS, use _x000D__x000A_ as encoded value
- Caldav: implement merged folder ctag over WebDav
- Caldav: fix noneMatch handling over WebDav
- Caldav: implement tasks delete over WebDav
- Caldav: implement tasks support over WebDav
- Caldav: send principal-URL for OSX Lion
- Caldav: first duedate implementation on tasks, fix delete task and concat ctag to detect changes on both calendar and tasks folders
- Caldav: implement percent complete and status VTODO updates
- Caldav: implement task support over EWS
- Caldav: decode destination path on move
- Caldav: encode LF to %0A in urlcompname
- Caldav: check Depth before search
- Caldav: Task folder flag
- Caldav: move remove quotes for Evolution to EWS mode only
- Caldav: fix regression on iCal FreeBusy handling
- Caldav: implement PROPFIND on single item
- Caldav: remove quotes on etag for Evolution
- Caldav: first Task (VTODO) implementation step
- Caldav: allow infinity as Depth value

Enhancements:
- Fix DoubleDotInputStream
- Improve system proxies and move item logging
- Refactor buildSessionInfo to use /public first and mailbox path as failover for galfind requests
- Fix bug in removeQuotes
- Fix 3315942, patch cleanup
- Fix server certificate label
- Fixes from audit
- Upgrade SWT to 3.7
- Fix 3315942, merge patch provided by Jeremiah Albrant: Ask user to select client certificate
- Improve message download progress logging, switch icon every 100KB
- Remove unused SwtAwtEventQueue class
- Implement davmail.smtpSaveInSent option and reorganize tabs
- Fix 3153691: Username with apostrophe
- Patch by Manuel Barkhau: exclude private events flag
- Reformat and fixes from audit

EWS:
- EWS: new recurring event filter implementation, exclude recurrence exception in results
- EWS: fix new Exchange 2010 ItemId length support
- EWS: Fix for some Exchange 2010 ItemIds different length
- EWS: workaround for Exchange bug, replace xml 1.0 header with xml 1.1 and log message download progress
- EWS: implement gzip encoding on response

Dav:
- Dav: update httpClient host after login

IMAP:
- IMAP: need to include base folder in recursive search, except on root
- IMAP: Fix 3151800, force UTF-8 in appendEnvelopeHeaderValue

Documentation:
- Doc: Add davmail.smtpSaveInSent description in doc
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.2" date="2011-06-07">
      <description>
        <p>
This release includes some documentation updates, implement IMAP Recent flag, 
Caldav support enhancements, 64 bits wrapper on windows, hanging issue with SWT 
on Linux 64 and many other bugfixes.

LDAP:
- LDAP: cancel search threads on connection close

Enhancements:
- Adjust system proxy log statement
- Jsmooth patch with 64 bits skeletons
- Additional statement on proxy load
- SWT: register error handler early
- Serialize session creation in workstation mode to avoid multiple OTP requests
- SWT: register error handler to avoid application crash on concurrent X access from SWT and AWT
- Revert LookAndFeel changes, switch to System.setProperty to set default LAF
- SWT: make sure we don&#x27;t start AWT threads too early
- Update Jsmooth patch with 64bits exe support
- SWT: delayed AWT frames creation to reduce memory usage
- Experimental 64 bits windows exe
- Add a log file size field in UI

DAV:
- Dav: back to old path in Destination header behavior
- DAV: switch icon on large message download
- Dav: Log message download progress
- Dav: new patch to reset session timeout with a GET method on /owa/
- Dav: experimental, try to reset session timeout with a GET method
- Dav: do not try property update failover on 507 SC_INSUFFICIENT_STORAGE

OSX:
- OSX: Avoid sending empty message to Growl

IMAP:
- IMAP: test custom header search
- IMAP: workaround for Exchange 2003 search deleted support
- IMAP: fix 3303767, do not send line count for non text bodyparts
- IMAP: another fix for 3297849, ENVELOPE formating error/bogus quotes
- IMAP: fix 3297849, ENVELOPE formating error/bogus quotes
- IMAP: Fix nullpointer in broken message handling
- IMAP: fix infinite loop detection
- IMAP: detect infinite loop on the client side
- IMAP: implement Recent flag on new messages based on read flag and creation/modification date
- IMAP: fix 3223513 default flags on append

Documentation:
- Doc: How to run multiple instances of DavMail
- Doc: FAQ note, iCal does not support folder names with spaces or special characters
- Doc: Add reference to default windows domain setting in FAQ
- Doc: additional Thunderbird and DavMail review
- Doc: add Duplicate messages in Sent folder FAQ entry
- Doc: add Piwik code to DavMail site
- Doc: New (french) review
- Doc: document custom certificate authority handling
- Doc: improve initial setup documentation
- Doc: describe the usual paths to use in OWA url field
- Doc: update imapAutoExpunge flag doc
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: document public folder access in Lightning

Caldav:
- Caldav: allow tab as folding character, see RFC2445
- Caldav: Fix NullPointerException in getTimezoneIdFromExchange
- Caldav: instancetype is null on Exchange 2010, switch to isrecurring in EWS FindItem
- Caldav: Disable schedule-inbox for all Lightning versions
- Caldav: prepare xmoz custom property support over DAV

EWS:
- EWS: fix UID and RECURRENCE-ID, broken at least on Exchange 2007 with recurring events
- EWS: fix 3105534 GetUserAvailability default timezone compatibility with Exchange 2010
- EWS: new failovers on Timezone settings: use davmail.timezoneId setting or default to GMT Standard Time
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.1" date="2011-03-22">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bugfix release, mainly on EWS Caldav support (fix 404 not found).
Also implemented Microsoft Forefront Unified Access Gateway support.

Documentation:
- Doc: additional FAQ entry on shared calendars

Caldav:
- Caldav: first check that email address is valid to avoid InvalidSmtpAddress error on FreeBusy request and new timezone name mapping
- Caldav: New fix for fix 3190219, regression on quote encoding since 3165749 fix
- Caldav: rethrow SocketException to avoid event not available on client connection close or DavMail listener restart
- Caldav: Fix timezone name
- Caldav: fix 3190219, regression on quote encoding since 3165749 fix

Exchange Web Services:
- EWS: fix 3190774, LDAP galfind email address handling, use Mailbox value instead of EmailAddress1/2/3
- EWS: fix NullPointerException in item getContent
- EWS: fix 404 not found with Exchange 2010 calendars

Enhancements
- Convert shell script to unix LF
- Implement Microsoft Forefront Unified Access Gateway logon form compatibility

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix 3201374 envelope superflous space
- IMAP: fix LOGOUT implementation to improve SquirrelMail compatibility

OSX:
- OSX: Avoid sending null message to Growl
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.9.0" date="2011-02-22">
      <description>
        <p>
Making progress towards 4.0 and full EWS support, some issues remaining on recurring
events. This is mainly a bugfix release, with some Caldav enhancements, huge memory usage fix
on IMAP and a workaround for Linux 64 bits futex issue (deadlock on first connection).

POP:
- POP: test new double dot implementation
- POP: Fix from Stefan Guggisberg, handle invalid CR or LF line feeds in DoubleDotOutputStream

Caldav:
- Caldav: additional timezone names in table
- Caldav: 3132513, implement well-known url, see http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-daboo-srv-caldav-10
- Caldav: implement a new setting to disable task (VTODO) support: davmail.caldavDisableTasks and probably exclude most broken events
- Caldav: throw exception on empty event body (EWS)
- Caldav: fix multivalued param support in VProperty and always quote CN values

Documentation:
- Doc: Update release guide
- Doc: Additional FAQ entry on public calendar access with iCal
- Doc: Add Manchester wiki review

LDAP:
- LDAP: dump BER content on error
- LDAP: fix 3166460, do not fail on NOT (0xa2) filter

Bugfix:
- New workaround for bug 3168560, load system proxy settings in static block
- Fix 3161913 klauncher says davmail.desktop misses trailing semicolon
- Restore stax-api jar for Java 1.5 compatibility
- Fix 3150426 huge memory usage with IMAP
- Workaround for bug 3168560, synchronize system proxy access
- New NTLMv2 patch: provide fake workstation name and adjust Type3 message flags

EWS:
- EWS: Fix 3165749, exception with quotes in meeting subject and EWS

Webdav:
- Dav: log search response count
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.8" date="2011-01-11">
      <description>
        <p>
Yet another bugfix release with many EWS support enhancements and fixes,
many documentation improvements (still need to update Thunderbird/OSX instructions
to latest versions though).

Documentation:
- Doc: change Maven site plugin version
- Doc: additional external links
- Doc: Add anew reviews page
- Doc: Update POM and release guide
- Doc: move advanced settings to a separate page to keep getting started page simple
- Doc: add SWT bug reference to FAQ, on Ubuntu, notify text conflicts with default theme
- Doc: full iPhone setup instructions
- Doc: update war deployment description
- Doc: Additional smartcard PKCS11 setup instructions with NSS and Coolkey examples

Caldav:
- Caldav: Additional timezone mappings
- Caldav: workaround for Exchange 2010 bug, \n in timezone name generates invalid ICS content
- Caldav: improve timezone rename error message
- Caldav: fix floating timezone in iCal: rename TZID for maximum iCal/iPhone compatibility
- Do not send Exchange 2003 appointment creation request to Exchange 2007

EWS:
- EWS: return HttpNotFoundException on event not found to trigger Lightning workaround
- EWS: fix instancetype field definition: Integer instead of String (fix Caldav filter over EWS)
- EWS: improved email/alias failover fix
- EWS: fix regression in comment
- EWS: additional failover mail build on logon form failure
- EWS: store X-MOZ-SEND-INVITATIONS property to fix no notification issue with Lightning
- EWS: fix Caldav inbox handling over EWS
- EWS: improve timezone handling
- EWS: Update Field list
- EWS: fix 3098008, implement result paging to handle message folders with more than 1000 messages 
- EWS: exclude non message types from searchMessages
- EWS: fix email mapping on LDAP response
- EWS: add BusinessCountryOrRegion contact field

Enhancements
- Additional session create log statement
- New multiple user fields implementation: expect userid|username as login value
- Improve connection pool handling: do not pool simple checkConfig and getVersion connections.
- Implement OTP form with multiple username fields (username and userid)
- Contribution from Geert Stappers: start/stop script
- Improve NTLM authentication detection
- Always use private connection manager to avoid session conflict
- Fixes from audit
- Update javamail to 1.4.3
- Adjust Mime decoder settings (fix)
- Adjust Mime decoder settings
- Workaround for space in cookie name
- Use a_sLgnQS instead of a_sLgn first to support new OWA 8.3.83.4
- Additional NTLM flags to match Firefox flags
- Add UTF-7 support with jcharset
- Failover for misconfigured Exchange server, replace host name in url

SMTP:
- SMTP: fix 3132569, always remove From header to avoid 403 error on send
- SMTP: workaround for misconfigured Exchange servers: failover on Draft message creation through properties. Warning: attachments are lost

IMAP:
- IMAP: Fix 3137275 Imap header fetch bug

WebDav:
- Dav: make sure Destination contains full url and not only path, may fix SMTP send and IMAP copyMessage on Exchange 2003

Carddav
- Carddav: Update contact test
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.7" date="2010-11-24">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix and performance release with new Woodstox parser to reduce memory
footprint in EWS mode, more Caldav broken events fixes and IMAP regression
fixes.

Documentation:
- Doc: Update Carddav setup doc
- Doc: ssl setup doc update from kerstkonijn

Enhancements
- Unzip contribs content
- Update rpm ant task parameters to create valid rpm package
- Workaround for malformed cookies with space in name
- From Geert Stappers: add includeantruntime=&quot;false&quot; to avoid ant 1.8 warning
- Workaround for invalid redirect location
- Improve error handling: detect redirect to reason=0 as session expired
- Suggestion from Geert Stappers: add svn:ignore property
- RPM spec from Marko Myllynen

Caldav:
- Caldav: Fix timezone support with Exchange 2010 SP1
- Caldav: use rebuild event from MAPI properties failover in all error cases
- Caldav: add requestFocus() to bring notification dialog to foreground
- Caldav: added edit notifications checkbox in settings frame

IMAP:
- IMAP: include current folder in recursive search
- IMAP: encode source path in copyMessage
- IMAP: new test case to show Thunderbird perf issue
- IMAP: Fix 3109303 Handle null string during mail fetch
- IMAP: fix nullpointerException in header fetch
- IMAP: fix 3106803, IMAP client stuck scanning Inbox, fix header and body fetch in same request
- IMAP: throw error on 440 Login Timeout to avoid message corruption

LDAP:
- LDAP: do not log error on OSX groups request

EWS:
- EWS: Upgrade woodstox version to use enhanced base64 conversion (reduced memory usage)
- EWS: allow autodiscover after authentication failure
- EWS: fix contact email update

OSX:
- OSX: search and replace on existing file, spotted by Geert Stappers
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.6" date="2010-11-07">
      <description>
        <p>
First release with automatic EWS mode detection, also includes many bugfixes
on LDAP support over EWS, IMAP enhancements, Exchange 2010 SP1 cookie bug workaround
and a brand new UI frame to let users edit Caldav notifications.

LDAP:
- LDAP: fix galfind search: add uid in response and use cn in fullsearch filter
- LDAP: additional EWS attributes
- LDAP: additional attributes for iPad

Enhancements:
- Fix 3103349: Cannot login if display name contains [brackets], regression after first patch
- Fix 3103349: Cannot login if display name contains [brackets]
- configFilePath is null in some test cases
- Added passcode as token field for RSA support
- Add DavMail version in welcome IMAP and SMTP header
- Update test case
- Handle exceptions on invalid UTF-8 characters or unexpected content triggered by XmlStreamReader.getElementText (based on patch 3081264)
- Add exchange 2010 PBack cookie in compatibility mode
- Novell iChain workaround

POP:
- POP: add version in welcome banner

Caldav:
- Caldav: Fix bug in Dav mode with broken events dtstart -&gt; dtend
- Caldav: fix french notification message
- Caldav: protect &#x27;:&#x27; in VCALENDAR property params
- Caldav: initial edit notification implementation
- Caldav: Create fake DTEND on broken event
- Caldav: fix nullpointer in VCalendar on missing DTEND
- Caldav: implement main calendar folder rename
- Caldav: use i18n calendar name as display name for iCal
- Caldav: avoid renaming default calendar to null

EWS:
- Ews: improve ResolveNames implementation, parse addresses and phone attributes
- EWS: implement failover on OWA authentication failure (e.g. with outlook.com)
- Ews: improve invalid item in calendar error handling
- EWS: improve resolveNames logging
- EWS: add enableEws flag in UI settings frame
- EWS: automatically detect Webdav not available and set davmail.enableEws flag

IMAP:
- IMAP: failover in message copy on 404 not found
- IMAP: Fix append with no optional parameters
- IMAP: additional test cases
- IMAP: fix from kolos_dm: implement fake line count in BODYSTRUCTURE and [] block in IMAPTokenizer
- IMAP: fix from kolos_dm: implement attachment name in BODYSTRUCTURE
- IMAP: improve logging, do not log message content on 404 or 403
- IMAP: fix from kolos_dm: In-Reply-To is not email header and unfold header to remove CRLF in ENVELOPE response
- IMAP: merge fix from Kolos, search command with message sequence set
- IMAP: implement index (non uid) COPY
- IMAP: workaround for broken message (500 error), rebuild mime message from properties
- IMAP: send error on idle command without selected folder (Outlook)

Documentation:
- Doc: fixes and updates on ssl setup and build
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: Update architecture image
- Doc: update ssl server certificate doc
- Doc: Document PKCS12 self signed certificate creation to enable SSL in DavMail
- Doc: iPhone screenshots

SWT:
- SWT: Custom AWT event queue to trap X errors and avoid application crash
- SWT:enable debug mode
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.5" date="2010-09-27">
      <description>
        <p>
Includes much progress on Caldav over EWS support, a few regression fixes 
and improved IMAP BODYSTRUCTURE implementation for complex messages.

Bugfixes:
- Fix regression in Exchange 2007 over Dav session

Enhancements:
- Detect and submit language selection automatically
- More fixes from audit
- Fixes from audit
- Restore cookies on error
- Improve buildSessionInfo failover
- Fix ssl trustmanager error handling
- Enable Webdav/Galfind failover on Exchange 2007
- Workaround for basic authentication on /exchange and form based authentication at /owa

Caldav:
- Caldav: detect invalid events with empty dtstart property
- Caldav: implement mozilla alarm flags X-MOZ-LASTACK and X-MOZ-SNOOZE-TIME over EWS
- Caldav: EWS, rebuild attendee list from properties
- Caldav: test principal request
- Caldav: fix 3067915 getRangeCondition too restrictive
- Caldav: implememnt Busy flag over EWS and refactor create code
- Caldav: fix create allday event over EWS and check if current user is organizer
- Caldav: Fixed regression in allday event handling
- Caldav: improve EWS implementation
- Caldav: improve timezone error handling
- Caldav: remove empty properties
- Caldav: avoid invalid X-CALENDARSERVER-ACCESS and CLASS
- Caldav: avoid empty X-CALENDARSERVER-ACCESS and CLASS
- Caldav: reinsert the deleteBroken check
- Caldav: fix VProperty parser
- Caldav: additional VCalendar properties for rebuilt item: VALARM (reminder)
- Caldav: additional VCalendar properties for rebuilt item: RRULE, EXDATE, CLASS
- Caldav: failover for broken event, rebuild VCalendar content from raw properties
- Caldav: fix 3063407, regression in sendPrincipal

Carddav:
- Carddav: fix null value in email address
- Carddav: fix email address handling over EWS

Exchange Web Services:
- EWS: fix 3047563 double inbox
- EWS: more caldav ews fixes

SMTP:
- SMTP: rewrite getAllRecipients to disable strict header check
- SMTP: new try at encoding fix: set mailOverrideFormat and messageFormat

Documentation:
- Upgrade maven site-plugin and update release guide

IMAP:
- IMAP: fix 3072497 Imap server too picky about case
- IMAP: improve BODYSTRUCTURE implementation, make it recursive
- IMAP: implement partial header fetch

LDAP:
- LDAP: new attribute mapping
- LDAP: cache current hostname value in sendComputerContext to improve iCal address completion performance
- LDAP: additional ignore attributes
- LDAP: add gidnumber to attribute ignore list
- LDAP: fix regression on iCal 3 search completion

SWT:
- SWT: allow libswt-gtk-3.6-java on debian, available from ppa:aelmahmoudy/ppa
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.4" date="2010-09-08">
      <description>
        <p>
Yet another bugfix release with more regressions fixes on SMTP,
a few LDAP fixes and a caldav timezone update. 

Documentation:
- Doc: Update release guide
- Doc: Update swt version in maven pom

SMTP:
- SMTP: try to force IMS encoding mode according to message contenttype
- SMTP: switching back to Draft then send mode over DAV for calendar messages
- SMTP: switching back to Draft then send mode over DAV
- SMTP: new duplicate message-id detection implementation, no need to search Sent folder

LDAP:
- LDAP: improve EWS filter support
- LDAP: another gallookup detection fix to improve address completion in thunderbird

Carddav:
- Carddav: improve OSX client detection

Enhancements
- Fixes from audit

Caldav:
- Caldav: accept login as alias in caldav principals path
- Caldav: basic move item implementation
- Caldav: adjust Lightning bug workaround
- Caldav: yet another timezone fix, adjust Outlook created event time before allday conversion
- Caldav: fix regression on meeting response subject
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.3" date="2010-09-02">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bugfix release with major regressions fixed:
missing calendar meeting messages and delivery status notification on
some external addresses. Also includes improved autodiscover support.

Enhancements:
- Disable broken rpm generation
- Fix test cases
- Upgrade swt to 3.6
- workaround for TLS Renegotiation issue, 
  see http://java.sun.com/javase/javaseforbusiness/docs/TLSReadme.html    
- Switch back to StreamReader.next instead of nextTag
- Fix autodiscover support
- Merge patch 3053324: Implement per service SSL flag (patch provided by scairt)
- Fix XMLStreamUtil regression
- Refactor XMLStreamUtil

Exchange Web Services:
- EWS: improve autodiscover implementation
- EWS: fix possible NullPonterException
- EWS: implement autodiscover to find actual EWS endpoint url

Caldav:
- Caldav: extend Lightning broken tests to all 1.* versions
- Caldav: switch back to contentclass to get calendarmessages over webdav
- Caldav : revert previous changes and fix meeting cancel support (IPM.Schedule.Meeting.Canceled)
- Caldav: move to trash on processItem
- Caldav: fix request parser regression on nextTag
- Caldav: improve filter handling, support VTODO/VEVENT comp-filter
- Caldav: make timezone name retrieval more robust

SMTP:
- SMTP: make duplicates check optional with davmail.smtpCheckDuplicates setting
- SMTP: always remove From header with Exchange 2007 and 2010
- SMTP: Improve message on MAIL FROM without authentication
- SMTP: experimental, advertise 8BITMIME

IMAP:
- IMAP: implement shared mailbox access

Documentation:
- minor doc fix
- Doc: Additional Exchange Webdav setup documentation
- Add ohloh widget on home page
- Doc: a few doc fixes and update roadmap
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.2" date="2010-08-25">
      <description>
        <p>
Bugfix release with improved Exchange 2010 IMAP support, CardDav fixes and
improved error handling

Enhancements:
- Disable SWT on Java 7
- Update debian package description and categories
- fix 2995990: Add support for already authenticated users
- Fix missing hide password in log over IMAP
- More session creation enhancements, fix public folder test when /public is 403
- Refactor email and alias retrieval: always use options page with Exchange 2007
- Improve socket closed error handling
- Try default form url on authentication form not found
- Add Java Service Wrapper contribution from Dustin Hawkins

Caldav:
- Caldav: move delete broken event logic to DavExchangeSession
- Caldav: delete broken events when davmail.deleteBroken is true
- Caldav: improve event logging, include subject

IMAP:
- IMAP: handle 507 InsufficientStorage error
- IMAP: fix regression in NOT DELETED filter

Documentation:
- Doc: Update OSX directory setup documentation

DAV:
- DAV: Encode apos in urlcompname used in DAV search request

EWS:
- EWS: fix single message in folder with Exchange 2010 bug
- EWS: implement loadVTimezone for Exchange 2010

SMTP:
- SMTP: fix regression on bcc handling
- SMTP: convert Resent- headers, see 3019708

LDAP:
- LDAP: avoid galLookup in iCal searches

Carddav:
- Carddav: Fix email update over EWS
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.1" date="2010-08-18">
      <description>
        <p>
Includes a full refactoring of Vcalendar content handling, much progress on
Exchange Web Services support, LDAP optimizations and many other bufixes.

Exchange Web Services:
- EWS: hard method: delete/create on update
- EWS: Fix DeleteItem for CalendarItem
- EWS: implement loadVtimezone, get user timezone id from OWA settings
- EWS: Fix FieldURIOrConstant test
- EWS: separate domain from userName in NTLM mode
- EWS: MultiCondition galFind
- EWS: implement basic galFind search
- EWS: implement resolvenames response parsing
- EWS: fix subfolder search on Exchange 2010
- EWS: implement user availability (freebusy) and shared folder access
- EWS: implement sendEvent
- EWS: force urlcompname only on create
- EWS: implement ResolveNames method
- EWS: Apply workaround to events
- EWS: workaround for missing urlcompname on Exchange 2010, use encoded ItemId instead
- EWS: rename equals to isEqualTo and format search date
- EWS: dynamic version detection
- EWS: Exchange 2010 message handling
- EWS: Exchange 2010 folder handling
- EWS: Exchange 2010 compatibility: add test cookie, access /ews/exchange.asmx endpoint

Caldav:
- Caldav: Fix missing TZID in DTSTART from iPhone
- Caldav: return reoccuring events on time-range request
- Caldav: Fix METHOD on create from iPhone
- Caldav: need to encode colon (:) in urlcompname search, implement a last failover on item search
- Caldav: implement 2899430, change the subject line when replying to invites
- Caldav: workaround for Lightning 1.0b2 bug
- Caldav: disable caldav inbox with Lightning 1.0b2
- Caldav: fix regression in fixVCalendar (missing organizer)
- Caldav: skip empty lines
- Caldav: Fix regressions in Vcalendar handling
- Caldav: fix nullpointer in VCalendar
- Caldav: fix regressions and do not filter on outlookmessageclass
- Caldav: major refactoring of event content handling and notifications
- Caldav: switch to new VCalendar parser/patcher
- Caldav: implement VALARM in VCalendar
- Caldav: more vcalendar patches
- Caldav: start new VCalendar fixICS implementation
- Caldav: call fixICS on download
- Caldav: reenable Lightning 1.0b2 bug workaround
- Caldav: failover for 404 not found on items containing &#x27;+&#x27; in url, search item by urlcompname to get permanenturl

LDAP:
- LDAP: create a separate thread only for person/contact searches
- LDAP: implement galFind MultiCondition over webdav and improve search by mail
- LDAP: need to galLookup when search attribute is not in galfind result
- LDAP: another search attribute mapping fix
- LDAP: code cleanup and some galfind search fixes
- LDAP: fix 3043659, include entries starting with Z
- LDAP: Improve sizeLimit handling and ignore attributes
- LDAP: a few more attribute fixes
- LDAP: move galLookup to DavExchangeSession
- LDAP: progress on EWS LDAP implementation and refactoring
- LDAP: fix regression on OSX directory request on iCal start: filter invalid imapUid condition
- LDAP: use sizeLimit in contactFind
- LDAP: Fix OSX directory search on uid

Enhancements:
- Improve error handling
- Add custom cookie policy to support extended host name
- Fixes from audit

Bugfixes:
- Fix regression in getAliasFromMailboxDisplayName
- Deb: Fix regression in debian desktop link

Dav:
- Dav: disable galFind on error

SMTP:
- SMTP: compare actual email address, not email with alias
- SMTP: no need to remove From header with new sendMessage implementation

SWT:
- SWT: fix 2992428, hide instead of dispose on close

Carddav:
- Carddav: refactor VCard handling to merge with VCalendar code
- Carddav: disable contact picture handling on Exchange 2007
- Carddav: implement range search
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.0b2" date="2010-07-26">
      <description>
        <p>
Fixes the most obvious regressions in 3.8.0b1 and some documentation
updates on Carddav. Note for EWS only users: add davmail.enableEws=true in
davmail.properties

Caldav: fix sendEvent regression, conflict on outbox notifications
Caldav: improve HttpNotFound message
Caldav: Refactor getItem
Doc: fix carddav thunderbird doc
Doc: update left menu
Doc: set source encoding to UTF-8 in maven pom
Doc: update roadmap
Doc: Basic OSX setup instructions
Doc: thunderbird carddav setup with SOGO connector
Doc: Update homepage and project description
Carddav: additional TEL properties
Caldav: fix MKCALENDAR http status code: return 201 instead of 207
Carddav: add fburl field
Caldav: Another request parsing bug: handle empty elements
Caldav: fix regression in REPORT requests parsing
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.8.0b1" date="2010-07-25">
      <description>
        <p>
First public release after major refactoring to implement Exchange 2010 and Exchange 2007 without
Webdav support. This implementation is based on Exchange Web Services. EWS support is not yet
complete: global address list search and free/busy support is missing.
This release includes the new Carddav service sponsored by French Defense / DGA through 
project Trustedbird. OSX notifications will now use Growl if available.

Carddav:
- Carddav: another urlcompname encoding fix
- Carddav: generate OSX compatible VCARD photo and change addressbook-home-set with OSX Address Book
- Carddav: use new ExchangePropPatchMethod in full contact create/update
- CardDav: use new ExchangePropPatchMethod to create haspicture boolean property
- Carddav: improve error logging on photo update failure
- Carddav: use email1 as default email on update
- Carddav: fix multiple mail MAPI properties handling
- Carddav: fix GET request on folder support for SOGO
- Carddav: encode contact picture url
- Carddav: return 404 not found on missing folder
- Carddav: fix line folding in generated VCARD
- Carddav: Fix regression in single value multiline properties
- Carddav: add gender property
- Carddav: adjust bday to timezone
- Carddav: another anniversary property candidate
- Carddav: Add Anniversary support
- Carddav: Fix bday generation
- Carddav: fix iPhone BDAY parser
- Carddav: adjust fields accepting multiple values
- Carddav: fix semicolon encoding in compound value
- Carddav: workaround for iPhone categories encoding
- CardDav: do not encode simple (not compound) properties
- Carddav: fix regression in VCardWriter
- Carddav: always encode values
- Carddav: protect semicolon
- Carddav: iPhone personalHomePage support
- Carddav: ignore key prefix in VCARD
- Carddav: resize contact picture
- Carddav: Fix lower case param names
- Carddav: add contact create or update log statement
- Carddav: handle param values as parameter list
- Carddav: encode photo href
- Carddav: fix regression on VCARD photo detection
- Carddav: use urlcompname value instead of path to get contact details
- Carddav: fix case insensitive param values
- Carddav: add haspicture to test case
- Carddav: Implement picture delete and private flag over EWS
- Carddav: handle picture delete
- Carddav: fix boolean field handling
- Carddav: Remove missing properties on update
- Carddav: implement CLASS (private) flag
- Carddav: convert image to jpeg over EWS
- Carddav: implement photo update over WebDav
- Carddav: implement photo handling over EWS
- Carddav: implement categories support in EWS mode
- Carddav: implement categories
- Carddav: get SMTP email address
- Carddav: move value decoding back to VCardReader
- Carddav: decode multiline values
- Carddav: encode comma and \n in values
- CardDav: make getContactPhoto more robust
- Carddav: iPhone iOS4 compatibility
- Carddav: implement contact photo support (readonly)
- Carddav: implement quoted param value support
- Carddav: bday, assistant, manager and spouse properties
- Carddav: other address and homeposteofficebox properties
- Carddav: instant messaging and role properties
- Carddav: more properties
- Carddav: Implement phone, address and email properties
- Carddav: handle multiple values on a single line and add new properties
- CardDav: fix contact folder path handling and add create contact unit test
- Carddav: refactor Contact creation and create VCardReader
- CardDav: move Contact getBody to ExchangeSession and add more attributes support
- CardDav: map contact fields
- CardDav: improve automatic address book setup for OSX
- CardDav: implement OSX AddressBook requests: current-user-privilege-set property, current-user-principal on root request, addressbook-home-set on principal request, addressbook-multiget REPORT request with address-data response, urn:ietf:params:xml:ns:carddav namespace

Enhancement:
- Disable preemptive authentication when adding NTLM scheme
- Fixes from audit
- Force log file encoding to UTF-8
- Add new davmail.logFileSize setting
- Use linux friendly path separator in jsmooth config files
- Fixes from audit
- Major refactoring: use straight inpustream instead of reader everywhere
- Disable ConsoleAppender in gui mode
- Add missing Junit jar
- Cleanup: System.setProperty of httpclient.useragent no longer needed
- Improve item not found logging
- Log gateway stop at info level
- Improve empty keystore password handling to avoid NullPointerException
- Fix 2999717 redirect console to /dev/null in desktop file

Exchange Web Services:
- EWS: fix urlcompname encoding issues
- EWS: fix folder name ampersand encoding issue
- EWS: return 403 forbidden on ErrorAccessDenied
- EWS: xml encode values
- EWS: use UTF-8 to decode request on error
- EWS: send extended properties first on update
- EWS: format datereceived date
- EWS: fix bug in UnindexedFieldURI
- EWS: update createMessage bcc handling to match sendMessage 
- EWS: implement bcc support in sendMessage
- EWS: implement send message (SMTP)
- EWS: fixes from audit
- EWS: fix CalendarItem creation, no need to wrap ics in a MIME message
- EWS: implement calendar event create or update, processed field, subfolder path handling 
- EWS: fix internaldate conversion
- EWS: convert read flag to boolean and noneMatch/etag to detect create or update on items
- EWS: use UnindexedFieldURI for read flag
- EWS: fixes for Caldav and Carddav compatibility
- EWS: fix folder id regression
- EWS: fix country contact property mapping
- EWS: implement getItem and various contact handling fixes
- EWS: map all contact properties
- EWS: implement more contact and event methods
- EWS: implement copy method
- EWS: datereceived flag support
- EWS: handle bcc field
- EWS: various flag handling fixes, implement message delete
- EWS: implement getContent
- EWS: fix iconIndex flag property
- EWS: implement create and update message
- EWS: fix single value in MultiCondition handling
- EWS: rely on uid (PR_SEARCH_KEY) instead of permanentUrl to detect imap uid changes
- EWS: implement searchMessages
- EWS: fix bug in MultiCondition search
- EWS: fix from audit
- EWS: implement folder handling, including the new MoveFolderMethod
- EWS: move mailbox folder urls to DavExchangeSession
- EWS: use searchContacts in contactFind
- EWS: fix regression in deleted flag handling
- EWS: refactor contactFind, use new Condition API
- EWS: still more WebDav code to DavExchangeSession
- EWS: move more WebDav code to DavExchangeSession
- EWS: Various fixes after refactoring on DASL request generation
- EWS: in progress refactoring of contacts and events handling
- EWS: implement folder ctag, remove deprecated foldername property
- EWS: move WebDav message write and delete to DavExchangeSession
- EWS: move WebDav code to DavExchangeSession
- EWS: refactor IMAP search, use Conditions classes instead of string search filder
- EWS: Use int values to create ExtendedFieldURI propertyTags
- EWS: map folder path to and from IMAP
- EWS: implement NotCondition and public folder access
- EWS: implement IndexedFieldURI and InternetMessageHeader
- EWS: refactor search to use classes instead of String filters
- EWS: implement MultipleOperandBooleanExpression (And, Or, Not conditions)
- EWS: refactor folder search, create abstract getFolder methods
- EWS: start ExchangeSession refactoring to extract Dav calls
- EWS: refactor options, use enums
- EWS: implement basic SearchExpression restriction
- EWS: Implement CreateFolder, DeleteFolder and CreateItem, refactor options
- EWS: retrieve and decode MIME content
- EWS: add standard field additional property, implement IncludeMimeContent in GetItem, add DeleteItemMethod
- EWS: Generic item property mapping
- EWS: refactor EWS code
- EWS: experimental HttpClient based EWS methods

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix time-range filter support in EWS mode
- Caldav: move calendar on displayname update
- Caldav: partial MKCALENDAR implementation
- Caldav: implement time-range request
- Caldav: add missing dtstart field
- Caldav: improve 404 error handling
- Caldav: fix regression in processItem
- Caldav: UTF-8 encode report body
- Caldav: catch any exception in reportItems
- Caldav: Process request before sending response to avoid sending headers twice on error
- Caldav: Workaround for Lightning/1.0b2 href encoding bug in REPORT requests
- Caldav: move processItem logic back to CaldavConnection
- Caldav: Workaround for emClient broken href encoding
- Caldav: remove buildCalendarPath method
- Caldav: allows mixed case contentType in event MIME message (fix Unable to get event error)
- Caldav: fix 3014204 missing timezone
- Caldav: fix 2902372 private flag handling undex iCal 4 (OSX 10.6 Snow Leopard)
- Caldav: send current-user-principal on principals folder for iCal
- Caldav: workaround for iCal bug: do not notify if reply explicitly not requested
- Caldav: add CRLF after END:VCALENDAR to comply with RFC
- Caldav: fix regression in getItem, allow urn:content-classes:calendarmessage contentClass
- Caldav: Fix Carddav etag handling (additional Head request) and implement card delete
- Caldav: Implement Carddav create (only a few attributes mapped)
- Caldav: Implement basic Carddav search requests

Dav:
- Dav: more property update fixes
- Dav: patch filter on invalid Exchange Webdav response
- Dav: new ExchangePropPatchMethod to handle custom exchange propertyupdate and invalid response tag names
- Dav: refactor getContentReader and fix regression on null date value
- Dav: fix nullpointer in DavExchangeSession
- Dav: handle null properties with new createMessage
- Dav: another datereceived fix
- Dav: switch back to DAV:uid, used mainly in POP service (case sensitive)
- Dav: fix bug 3022451 in new search filter implementation with empty sub conditions
- Dav: Add folder unit tests
- Dav: add private and sensitivity fields
- Dav: implement timezone mapping for Exchange 2007, should fix the allday issue with Outlook
- Dav: use search expression to request ishidden
- Dav: fix regression in deleteItem
- Dav: fix regression 3020385 on folder handling
- Dav: Refactor folder search to use searchItems
- Dav: use Email1EmailAddress mapi property to get mail attribute, add uid attribute
- Dav: fix from audit
- Dav: add unit tests, move buildCalendarPath logic to getFolderPath

Bug fixes:
- Use private MultiThreadedHttpConnectionManager with NTLM to avoid persistent authentication on connection issues
- Fix regression in AbstractConnection: return null instead of empty string on closed connection
- Fix 3001579: improve NTLM support

IMAP:
- IMAP: add uidNext MAPI property (not available under Exchange 2003)
- IMAP: fix deleted flag handling over Webdav
- IMAP: fix flag handling in createMessage
- IMAP: new seen flag test case
- IMAP: fix regression on imap uid restore
- IMAP: fix 3023386, support BODY.PEEK[1.MIME] partial fetch
- IMAP: new unit tests and fix $Forwarded flag removal
- IMAP: implement deleted/undeleted search as condition instead of post filter
- IMAP: add IMAP unit test
- IMAP: fix 3014787 remove property over WebDav
- IMAP: implement last message (simple *) fetch range
- IMAP: send required &quot;* SEARCH&quot; on empty search response
- IMAP: Add a new hidden davmail.deleteBroken setting to delete broken messages
- IMAP: implement a new imapAutoExpunge setting to delete messages immediately over IMAP

SMTP:
- SMTP: send message directly without creating a Draft message to preserve Message-id
- SMTP: fix log message
- SMTP: fix 3024482, avoid duplicate messages with gmail
- SMTP: Fix DoubleDotInputStream pushback size
- SMTP: last CRLF is not included in message content

Documentation:
- Doc: javadoc and code cleanup
- Doc: fix default domain label
- Doc: new FAQ entry on OSX auto start &quot;Login Items&quot;
- Doc: typos fixes from Raphael Fairise
- Doc: update release guide
- Doc: add a new mail.strictly_mime FAQ entry to enable quoted-printable

POP:
- POP: fix regression in TOP command
- POP: fix message termination, append CRLF only when necessary
- POP: replace deprecated write method, use DoubleDotOutputStream instead
- POP: allow space in username

LDAP:
- LDAP: fix contact attributes reverse mapping
- LDAP: improve contact attribute mapping and add a few new properties
- LDAP: fix attribute map
- LDAP: fix regression after EWS refactoring
- LDAP: use imap uid as ldap uid
- LDAP: use PR_SEARCH_KEY instead of DAV:uid as uid string

OSX:
- Exclude growl from non OSX packages
- Fix growl build project name
- OSX: implement growl support
- include jnilib in OSX package
- libgrowl-0.2 with libgrowl.jnilib compiled on OSX Snow Leopard
- set libgrowl version to 0.2
- rename generated jar with version, exclude test classes and create Manifest with Michael Stringer author
- Improve Growl exception handling, remove System.out and a few fixes from audit
- Initial growl import from http://forums.cocoaforge.com/viewtopic.php?f=6&amp;t=17320
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.6.6" date="2010-05-04">
      <description>
        <p>
This release is mainly focused on IMAP enhancements, including IDLE (RFC2177)
aka &quot;Push Mail&quot; support and other protocol compliance fixes, particularly on
partial fetch. NTLMv2 is also supported thanks to the JCIFS library.

Documentation:
- Doc: update doc and roadmap
- Doc: adjust settings message
- Doc: improve server/client certificates description
- Doc: new FAQ entry on message deleted over IMAP still visible through OWA
- Doc: fix maven site generation

IMAP:
- IMAP: send BAD instead of BYE on exception
- IMAP: fix 2992976, implement complex index and uid range in SEARCH
- IMAP: Handle exception during IDLE
- IMAP: add a new setting to enable/disable IDLE
- IMAP: use getRawInputStream instead of writeTo to avoid MIME message changes, cache message body in SharedByteArrayInputStream
- IMAP: poll folder every 30 seconds in IDLE mode, clear cached message
- IMAP: implement IDLE extension (RFC2177)
- IMAP: fix 2971184, do not decode content in partial fetch (replace getDataHandler with PartOutputStream)

Enhancements:
- Exclude redline lib from distribution packages
- Use https in default Exchange url
- Make sure log messages are not localized
- Remove unused messageId field
- Do not shutdown connection manager on restart
- Allow Exchange server to use gzip compression
- Sample SocketAppender configuration
- Improve NTLM mode detection
- JCIFS based NTLMv2 implementation
- Hardcode /owa/ path in getAliasFromOptions and getEmailFromOptions for Exchange 2007, improve failure message
- Improve xmlEncode, use compiled static patterns

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix 2992811, missing timezones
- Caldav: fix 2991030 tasks disappeared
- Caldav: add VTODO to supported-calendar-component-set response
- Caldav: fix regression in getAllDayLine()
- Caldav: make shared calendar test case insensitive
- Caldav: 0 or no value in caldavPastDelay means no limit
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.6.5" date="2010-04-13">
      <description>
        <p>
This release includes a major refactoring of the IMAP FETCH implementation
to improve performance and provide RFC compliant partial fetch. The Carddav
support sponsored by french DGA through project TrustedBird is now included
in the roadmap. Private events filter on shared calendar is also available
and DavMail can now retrieve proxy settings directly from system configuration.

SMTP:
- SMTP: implement AUTH LOGIN username (with optional initial-response, see RFC2554)

IMAP:
- IMAP: Keep a single message in MessageList cache to handle chunked fetch, reenable maxSize in ImapConnection.
- IMAP: implement subparts partial fetch
- IMAP: Fix message write, double dot only for POP, not IMAP
- IMAP: Do not advertise not yet supported custom flags
- IMAP: fix from audit
- IMAP: major FETCH implementation refactoring, make code simpler and more efficient
- IMAP: add BODY.PEEK[index] support
- IMAP: improve partial fetch support
- IMAP: fix 2962071, quote folder names in STATUS response
- IMAP: allow partial part fetch
- IMAP: fix regression on unknown parameter handling
- IMAP: implement part fetch (BODY[1]) 
- IMAP: detect unsupported parameter
- IMAP: fix 2973213, escape quotes in subject
- IMAP: fixes to improve JavaMail support

Doc:
- Doc: move CardDav reference before architecture schema
- Doc: update project description in Maven pom and ant package
- Doc: update project description and RoadMap, announce CardDav support sponsored by french DGA through project Trustedbird
- Doc: update roadmap

Enhancements:
- Add a new setting to disable startup notification window (contribution from jsquyres)
- Improve getAliasFromOptions to retrieve alias with custom dn
- Workaround for NTLM authentication only on /public
- Add a new setting to retrieve proxies from system configuration
- Fix empty setting behavior: return null instead of empty string
- Sort properties file
- Fix new RPM ant task definition
- Improve public folder url check
- Experimental rpm package build

Carddav:
- Carddav: refactor folder handling code to prepart CardDav support

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix broken inbox, missing instancetype in search request and add is null in search query
- Caldav: do not try to access inbox on shared calendar (to avoid 440 login timeout errors and session reset)
- Caldav: exclude private events on shared or public calendar PROPFIND
- Caldav: fix regression on invalid events handling, just warn on broken events
- Caldav: drop timezone when converting allday events to client
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.6.4" date="2010-02-21">
      <description>
        <p>
Well, yet another bugfix release, with improved IMAP support,
SMTP enhancements to support Eudora, NTLM proxy authentication
support and other bug fixes

SMTP:
- SMTP: fix 2953552, allow RSET in AUTHENTICATED state
- SMTP: bug id 2953554, implement NOOP

LDAP:
- LDAP: Enable tray icon on LDAP connection

Bug fixes:
- Fix regression in 3.6.3: basic authentication broken in checkConfig
- GUI: Fix client certificate setting switch

Enhancements:
- Change debian package dependence to accept openjdk-6-jre and libswt-gtk-3.5-java
- Fix from audit
- Improve log message on HTTP header error
- Implement NTLM HTTP proxy support
- Improve logging of expired sessions
- Support multiple forms in form based authentication logon page
- Catch error on SWT exit
- Enable NTLM on Proxy-Authenticate return code with only NTLM available

Documentation:
- Doc: Document davmailservice.exe usage
- Doc: Document Force ActiveSync setting in Getting Started
- Doc: Add an FAQ entry on DavMail settings location
- Doc: Update release notes and guide

IMAP:
- IMAP: new patch from Gellule to fix disappearing messages issue
- IMAP: rethrow SocketException after error in handleFetch

Caldav:
- Caldav: new fix for invalid events
- Caldav: add a hidden davmail.caldavDisableInbox to allow users to disable Caldav Inbox with Thunderbird 3 and Lightning
- Caldav: improve broken events logging
- Caldav: Follow redirects on GET with permanentUrl
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.6.3" date="2010-01-24">
      <description>
        <p>
Another bugfix release, mostly documentation updates, some regressions
in 3.6.2 in error handling fixed, a new IMAP workaround to completely
hide the uid change issue, emacs IMAP support and new UI settings for
previously hidden parameters.

Bug fix:
- Fix logging settings handling in webapp mode

Enhancements:
- Improve error handling: detect SocketException to avoid client socket closed errors
- Implement file based (PKCS12 and JKS) client certificates in addition to smartcard support

Documentation:
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: remove replace token and search page
- Doc: added Gellule as Java Contributor
- Doc: add a security section in the FAQ
- Doc: update FAQ with Exchange prerequisites details
- Document client keystore file settings

IMAP:
- IMAP: brand new IMAP uid workaround and refresh folder on Expunge from Gellule
- IMAP: implement LIST &quot;&quot; &quot;*%&quot; for emacs
- IMAP: another fix for the message uid bump issue
- IMAP: fix 2934922, implement (NOT DELETED) in search filter
- IMAP: extend thunderbird changed uid workaround to all contexts

GUI:
- Add new setting davmail.defaultDomain to set default windows domain
- Prepare new advanced options

Caldav:
- Caldav: add davmail.forceActiveSyncUpdate option to the settings frame
- Caldav: add davmail.caldavAlarmSound option to the settings frame (used to force conversion of Caldav alarms to AUDIO supported by iCal)
- Caldav: fix 2884864, send notifications to all participants on CANCEL
- Caldav: Fix invalid event handling, exclude events from returned list

SMTP:
- SMTP: implement RSET (reset) command to avoid connection timeout with Evolution
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.6.2" date="2010-01-11">
      <description>
        <p>
New bugfix release, with improved OSX tray icon, Kontact
support, a new workaround for thunderbird IMAP no message error,
public folders on a separate server support, improved ActiveSync
support and some documentation enhancements.

LDAP:
- LDAP: fix bug 2919463, escape quotes in search filter
- LDAP: fix Kontact ldap filter parsing, allow LDAP_FILTER_PRESENT in subfilter

Documentation:
- Doc: fix script replace
- Doc: new download and build pages
- Doc: update roadmap
- Doc: update doc
- Doc: add search icon
- Doc: Update roadmap
- Doc: Add roadmap to site menu

IMAP:
- IMAP: workaround for thunderbird random issue with no message found, keep previous message list to cope with recent message uid change.
- IMAP: try to support public folders hosted on a separate server (302 redirect on PROPFIND)
- IMAP: fix date parsing error, see bug 2878289
- IMAP: fix 2878289, implement extended MIME header search in http://schemas.microsoft.com/mapi/string/{00020386-0000-0000-C000-000000000046}/ namespace
- IMAP: improve error logging on 500 internal server error
- IMAP: Improve error handling, do not fail on message retrieval error, just send error message
- IMAP: implement EXPUNGE untagged response on NOOP to avoid NO message not found on Exchange message message uid change
- IMAP: implement RFC822.HEADER for Sylpheed

Caldav:
- Caldav: do not send fake inbox for public calendars to iCal
- Caldav: id 2900599, implement optional attendees in notifications
- Caldav: fix bug 2896135, iCal login fails at iCal startup
- Caldav: Send root instead of calendar href as inbox to fix iCal regression
- Caldav: Exclude events with a null instancetype and no ICS content
- Caldav: Workaround for Lightning 1.0pre public calendar, send calendar href as inbox/outbox urls
- Caldav: Convert DISPLAY to AUDIO only if user defined an alarm sound in settings (davmail.caldavAlarmSound)
- Caldav: fix NullPointerException in notifications
- Caldav: Fix bug 2907350, multiple calendar support issue with iCal
- Caldav: another timezone fix
- Caldav: Improve error handling on invalid events
- Caldav: another timezone fix
- Caldav: do not return invalid message content
- Caldav: move failover for Exchange 2007 plus encoding issue to Exchange session
- Caldav: a brand new ActiveSync fix, set contentclass to make ActiveSync happy, but also set PR_INTERNET_CONTENT to preserve custom properties. Also get etag from updated event.
- Caldav: major refactoring, move all ICS methods to Event inner class
- Caldav: fix bug 2902358, encode messageUrl in PropPatch with forceActiveSyncUpdate=true
- Caldav: improve MIME message headers in createOrUpdateEvent

Bugfixes:
- Fix last open session failover: do not append @hostname when alias contains @
- Revert to message url as default, use permanentUrl as failover
- Always use NTCredentials for proxy authorization
- Another NTLM fix: activate NTLM only on 401 unauthorized in executeGetMethod

Enhancements:
- Fix from audit (spelling errors)
- Add search page and change default package name for default svn builds
- Improve message logging
- Fixes from audit
- Additional Jsmooth settings
- Force flags parameter to 4 in Form Based Authentication
- Jsmooth patch to allow -X jvm options

OSX:
- OSX: replace inverted active icon
- OSX: new Mac OS X only icons
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.6.1" date="2009-11-24">
      <description>
        <p>
This is a bugfix release with fixed regressions from 3.6.0
and a few enhancements from user feedback.

Documentation:
- Doc: switch download links to generic link
- Doc: Update roadmap
- Doc: add roadmap

Bugfixes:
- Fix regression in Form Based Authentication: detect Exchange 2007 UserContext cookie
- Host is mandatory for NTLMScheme, get current hostname for proxy authentication

Enhancements:
- Experimental: reactivate NTLM authentication but leave authentication preemptive mode to allow basic authentication.
- Move PKCS11 registration to a separate class to avoid ClassNotFoundException
- Experimental OTP (token) based authentication
- Vista png icons support for JSmooth
- Fix from audit
- New upload-dist ant task to upload new release files

Caldav:
- Caldav: failover for Exchange 2007 plus encoding issue, search event by displayname to get permanent Url
- Caldav: Additional timezones
- Caldav: Revert commit 765, VTODO events have a null instancetype
- Caldav: additional timezone
- Caldav: Remove MAILTO: in addition to mailto: in getFreeBusy
- Caldav: Bug 2898469 do not UrlEncode draft url twice to avoid 404 not found on send event message
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.6.0" date="2009-11-15">
      <description>
        <p>
This release contains a lot of enhancements, both bug fixes
and new features from user feedback on 3.5.0, including improved
Evolution LDAP support, LDAP abandon support (faster searches with
Evolution and OSX), experimental windows service wrapper, improved
form based authentication support and ENVELOPE IMAP command support.  
I wish to thank Dan Foody for his valuable contributions on
OSX Snow Leopard support (attendee completion in iCal and complex
LDAP filters handling).
Also added an architecture schema on DavMail home page to quickly
describe DavMail features.

LDAP:
- LDAP: implement cn=* filter for Evolution
- LDAP: run searches in separate threads to implement ABANDON, will make searches faster with some clients (Evolution and OSX address book)
- LDAP: implement startsWith on Contact search, only objectclass=* is a full search
- LDAP: fix for iCal4 attendee completion,  send localhost if current socket is local, else send fully qualified domain name
- LDAP: major refactoring from Dan Foody to improve complex filters handling
- LDAP: improve contact search, reencode uids to hex to avoid case sensitivity issues

Documentation:
- Doc: Set Dan Foody as main java contributor
- Doc: improve DavMail logo
- Doc: add new Logo, improve internet explorer compatibility
- Doc: Add an architecture schema on site welcome page
- Doc: Improve getting started documentation, explain Exchange 2003 and 2007 paths (/exchange/ and /owa/) 
- Doc: fix site style
- Doc: fix maven site title

SMTP:
- SMTP: fix by Marc Macenko, case sensitive RCPT TO: 
- SMTP: allow lower case commands
- SMTP: experimental: remove Content-Type on create message to avoid 406 not acceptable with some Exchange servers.

Bugfixes:
- Fix 2887947: Exchange server with a username hidden field

Enhancements:
- Check for released version in a separate thread and set timeout to ten seconds
- Refactor message url encoding
- Upgrade Jmooth wrappers, add -Xrs jvm option to davmailservice wrapper to avoid service stop on user session logout (http://sourceforge.net/projects/jsmooth/forums/forum/297041/topic/2370742)
- Fix regression from revision 811
- Refactor ExchangeSession, use StringUtil to simplify code
- Remove username duplicate check, as formLogin now resets values before POST
- Start refactoring: StringUtil class
- Fix classpath in jsmooth wrappers to use new javamail
- Allow custom form with userid/pw fields in form based authentication
- Improve form based authentication, look for Exchange session cookies sessionid and cadata
- Fix test
- Upgrade JavaMail to 1.4.1
- New create folder method
- Fix FBA authentication, reset query string in getAbsoluteURI()
- New abstract JUnit test case class
- Detect redirect form instead of logon form, follow redirect to logon form
- Add an upload-site ant task
- Fixes from audit
- Fix settings default values and update doc
- Drop icon activity switches under 250ms to avoid fast flickering on OSX, add new switch icon in IMAP fetch iterations
- Improve script based form redirect to handle more cases
- Refactor ExchangeSession to allow independent session creation.
- Allow directory in logFilePath settings, add /davmail.log suffix in this case
- Allow follow redirects on /public GET requests

Caldav:
- Caldav: use permanenturl for Caldav to avoid encoding issues
- Caldav: do not close connection on 401 authorization required, may help iCal authentication
- Caldav: Additional Allday fix for Exchange 2007 and Outlook, implement a failover with a new davmail.timezoneId setting.
- Caldav: fix regression on create event, missing CRLF in mime message
- Caldav: Fix regression on public calendar folders linked to multiple calendar support for iCal
- Caldav: use chunked response to send calendar folder content as ICS to avoid timeout
- Caldav: Experimental GET ics on folder and fix regression on public folder access
- Caldav: get current VTIMEZONE body from OWA to create Allday events compatible with Outlook. Users still need to select the same Timezone in Outlook and OWA.
- Caldav: Fix Timezone value
- Caldav: Create a new setting davmail.forceActiveSyncUpdate to let users choose to force ActiveSync event. Note: custom iCal or Lightning ICS properties are lost if this option is enabled.
- Caldav: Some Exchange servers redirect to a different host for freebusy, use wide auth scope
- Caldav: Another fix from Dan Foody: improve dumpICS debug option
- Caldav: need to check session on each request, credentials may have changed or session expired
- Caldav: fix regression after ActiveSync patch, PROPPATCH on contentClass removes all custom ICS properties
- Caldav: improve getICSValue, do not return values inside VALARM section
- Caldav: do not send events with a null instancetype (may be the cause of iCal failure)
- CalDav: Send sub folders for multi-calendar support under iCal
- Caldav: fix path translation to Exchange for calendars in sub folders under /calendar
- Caldav: Added supported-calendar-component-set to calendar response
- Caldav: added a debug trace when requested calendar is not user calendar (maybe shared, but often url mistake in Caldav client)
- Caldav: fix Bug 2686125, PROPPATCH event after PUT to trigger activeSync PUSH, tested with iPhone 3 using activeSync

IMAP:
- IMAP: use permanenturl instead of href to avoid url encoding issues
- IMAP: Revert convert absolute IMAP path to relative path, breaks Caldav
- IMAP: Convert absolute IMAP path to relative path and detect ISA server cookie starting with cadata (instead of equals cadata)
- IMAP: use upper case NIL in ENVELOPE
- IMAP: improve MimeMessage handling, drop after fetch to avoid keeping full message in memory
- IMAP: fix new ENVELOPE feature, must return encoded values
- IMAP: implement store by id and ENVELOPE
- IMAP: update message flag only if changed to avoid unneeded message uid bump, may fix Evolution and Apple Mail constant reload issue
- IMAP: implement search by id
- IMAP: send default BODYSTRUCTURE on MIME encoding error
- IMAP: improve complex content-type handling in BODYSTRUCTURE
- IMAP: fix deleted flag handling, switch to official Exchange IMAP property http://schemas.microsoft.com/mapi/id/{00062008-0000-0000-C000-000000000046}/0x8570
- IMAP: detect HttpNotFoundException on folder select
- IMAP: improve public folder error handling
- IMAP: fix space at end of folder name
- IMAP: Fix regression on LIST INBOX
- IMAP: experimental public folder access
- IMAP: switch to http://schemas.microsoft.com/exchange/contentstate to handle deleted flag (DAV:isdeleted did not work with some Exchange servers).
- IMAP: implement undelete message
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.5.0" date="2009-09-22">
      <description>
        <p>
This release improves OSX Snow Leopard support, thank to
contributions from Dan Foody. Contact searches are also
available now in addition to global address book searches
over LDAP. IMAP with iPhone should now work correctly with
most messages, Evolution IMAP read flag is fixed.
Also added an experimental windows service support
and a lot of other bug fixes and enhancements. 

Doc:
- Doc: Fix FAQ whitespaces
- Doc: improve javadoc and code cleanup
- Doc: New OSX settings screenshot
- Doc: update release guide
- Doc: improve index and build doc
- Doc: detailed WIRE debug log file creation

Windows:
- Windows: Include DavMail service in windows package
- Windows: create windows service exe
- Windows: create windows service exe

IMAP:
- IMAP: test session expiration on each command, get a new session on expiration
- IMAP: improve error logging on network down
- IMAP: fix bug 2845530 implement FLAGS.SILENT command
- IMAP: fix absolute (public) path handling
- IMAP: fix BODYSTRUCTURE, build message on full buffer, do not rely on partial buffer (header, body, ...)
- IMAP: fix bug 2835529 FETCH with unordered range
- IMAP: send default BODYSTRUCTURE on mime parsing failure
- IMAP: Improve IMAP bodystructure error logging
- IMAP: Send bodystructure with headers for iPhone request (BODYSTRUCTURE BODY.PEEK[HEADER]) 
- IMAP: send BODY[TEXT] for BODY.PEEK[TEXT] request, may improve iPhone support
- IMAP: First fix for bug 2840255, do not follow redirects on message FETCH

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix conflict between X-MICROSOFT-CDO-BUSYSTATUS, X-MICROSOFT-CDO-ALLDAYEVENT and ORGANIZER ics patches
- Caldav: check credentials on each request
- Caldav: Disable broken sub calendar folders code
- Caldav: Do not fail on Inbox access denied, just return an empty folder
- Caldav: fix multi calendar Exchange path for sub folders
- Caldav: Experimental, fix sub calendar folders path
- Caldav: Experimental, send sub calendar folders on propfind with depth 1
- Caldav: Handle multi line description in calendar message body
- Caldav: merged contribution from Dan Foody,
- Caldav: convert sound to display alarms and back
- Caldav: remove additional organizer attendee line
- Caldav: remove RSVP=TRUE if PARTSTAT is not NEEDS-ACTION
- Caldav: add dump ICS logging feature
- Caldav: add a text/plain body to calendar messages
- Caldav: create a subject for calendar messages
- Caldav: fixed some encoding issues in Dan&#x27;s code
- Caldav: Additional timezones
- Caldav: failover to DAV:comment instead of CALDAV:schedule-state on some Exchange servers

LDAP:
- LDAP: iCal fix to suit both iCal 3 and 4:  move cn to sn, remove cn
- LDAP: iCal: do not send LDAP_SIZE_LIMIT_EXCEEDED on apple-computer search by cn with sizelimit 1
- LDAP: copy uid to apple-generateduid for iCal attendee search 
- LDAP: Make sure we do not send empty description field, replace &quot; \n&quot; with null
- LDAP: fix thread name
- LDAP: exclude non contact entries from search, fiw map key and sn copy for iCal
- LDAP: fix contact search, do not send unrequested attributes
- LDAP: improve Contact search filter support
- LDAP: Additional Contact attributes
- LDAP: refactor contact find, generic attribute mapping
- LDAP: experimental contact search support

OSX:
- OSX: Prepare hide from Dock option
- OSX: crazy workaround from Dan Foody to fix attendee search on OSX Snow Leopard
- OSX: iCal4 (OSX Snow Leopard fixes)

Bug Fixes:
- Fix regression in Form Based Logon: fix script based logon URI creation with path and query
- Another network down fix: DavMailException is not network down
- Improve Form Based Logon: fix script based logon URI creation
- Improve Form Based Logon: use full URI instead of path in PostMethod, also force trusted=4
- Simplify HttpClient creation to avoid password decoding bug in commons httpclient (&#x27;+&#x27; in password decoded as &#x27; &#x27;)

Enhancements:
- Improve HttpException error logging
- Fixes from checkStyle audit
- Adjust checkStyle settings
- Improve error handling on invalid URL
- Various fixes from FindBugs audit
- Fix from audit: synchronize access to HttpConnectionManager
- Refactor ExchangeSession: do not follow redirects with GET methods
- Fix from audit
- Do not pass DavMailAuthenticationException to handle network down
- Custom form (txtUserName, tstUserPass) support
- Another network down fix from Dan Foody
- Merged another patch from Dan Foody on network down detection
- New settings method: return log file directory
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.4.0" date="2009-08-14">
      <description>
        <p>
This release includes iPhone 3 Caldav support, upgrade to SWT 3.5,
Palm Pre IMAP fixes, improved shared/public calendar support
and a lot of bug fixes.

Doc:
- Doc: Code cleanup and improve javadoc
- Doc: Update doc
- Doc: Upgrade maven site plugin and improve style
- Doc: Update maven pom inceptionYear

Bug:
- Bug: Do not try to set Nimbus Look And Feel on Linux with Gtk

Enhancements:
- Remove NTLM authentication, breaks Basic authentication (missing domain in username)
- Set NTLM as last authentication scheme
- Experimental: reenable NTLM authentication
- Upgrade SWT to 3.5
- Use getFolderPath in getSubFolders
- Make API more consistent: createMessage must get a folder path, not URL
- Enhancement: Patch 2826966 from Eivind Tagseth, Make davmail.sh work from any location

IMAP:
- IMAP: Need to reset index for Palm pre
- IMAP: case insensitive search operators
- IMAP: Fix bug 2835529, implement SEARCH ALL SINCE for Palm Pre

Caldav:
- Caldav: improve error handling, 440 means 403 forbidden on Exchange
- Caldav: Fix shared calendar support for Lightning
- Caldav: additional patch for Outlook created recurring events
- Caldav: set X-MICROSOFT-CDO-BUSYSTATUS according to TRANSP field
- Caldav: implement a timezone translation table for iPhone 3, revert organizer patch (breaks notifications with Lightning)
- Caldav: another iPhone fix, remove organizer line if user is organizer
- Caldav: generic timezone patch for iPhone 3
- Caldav: remove empty ics properties
- Caldav: Remove calendar-proxy, only used for delegate calendars
- Caldav: try to improve responses for iCal
- Caldav: fix bug 2833044 Event not found error on dismissing reminders with events created in Outlook with a plus sign in subject
- Caldav: Experimental, add calendar-proxy DAV option and version in server header
- Caldav: Add missing allow OPTIONS header
- Caldav: improve public (shared) calendar support, accept calendars at any depth
- Caldav: set caldav logging to davmail logging level
- Caldav: updated fix, remove organizer line if event has no attendees for iPhone
- Caldav: remove organizer line if current user is organizer for iPhone, will not remove line for events with attendees
- Caldav: Improve principal -&gt; actualPrincipal detection: use session alias instead of login
- Caldav: fix bug 2819028, case insensitive email in sendPrincipal test
- Caldav: iPhone compatibility, remove &lt;C:comp name=&quot;VTODO&quot;/&gt;
- Caldav: iPhone workaround: send calendar subfolder
- Caldav: revert @ encoding, breaks iCal
- Caldav: iPhone fix, encode @ in Caldav response hrefs
- Caldav: untested, extended PROPFIND / response for iPhone 3.0
- Caldav: fix infinite loop with Sunbird 1.0pre with invalid credentials

SMTP:
- SMTP: fix bug 2791607, do not patch message body (breaks electronic signature), no longer needed with latest Thunderbird
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.3.0-623" date="2009-07-22">
      <description>
        <p>
This is a bug fix release after two beta releases,
including PKCS11 (smartcard) client certificate support,
gateway encryption (SSL) support, the new jackrabbit and httpclient libraries
and I18N support (french and english available).

- Caldav: updated caldav response headers according to gmail, added Expires and Cache-control HTTP headers
- POP3: implement NOOP command
- Doc: Update documentation header
- Doc: Add GPLv2 header to all source files
- Doc: Remove Apache license from checkstyle config file header
- IMAP: fix DELETED/UNDELETED SEARCH parameters
- IMAP: Fix bug 2822625: support index range in IMAP SEARCH
- Enhancements: Merged network down (with firewall) code from Dan Foody
- Caldav: Additional properties and ignore cases for Sunbird
- Caldav: Fix empty organizer field in ICS (active sync support) and another getParticipants bug
- GUI: Fix OSX menu default ActionListener
- GUI: Try to set Nimbus Look And Feel on Linux with Gtk
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.3.0-609" date="2009-06-29" type="beta">
      <description>
        <p>
This is a bug fix release, with nonetheless one main new feature:
PKCS11 (smartcard) client certificate support !
Tested with ActivIdentity ActivClient and Mozilla soft token, should
work with any PKCS11 module.

Security:
- (RFE 2800206) PKCS11 (smartcard) client certificate support

Server (daemon) mode:
- Fix server mode: now all listener threads are daemon, avoid main thread exit and add a shutdown hook
- Name shutdown thread

Caldav:
- Move wire debug log with headers
- Fix NoSuchMethodError with Java 5
- revert supported-calendar-component-set on root and improve logging
- fix regression on iCal calendar color change
- only include attendees with RSVP=TRUE or PARTSTAT=NEEDS-ACTION for notifications (avoid iCal additional notifications)
- Improve error handling on FreeBusy failure
- add supported-calendar-component-set property requested by iPhone 3.0
 Sunbird compatibility, exclude events with empty names
- Fix for iCal: send etag on GET and HEAD requests
- Send empty response instead of error on freebusy with unknown attendee

IMAP:
- revert refreshFolder calls that break Outlook

OSX:
- Remove default trayIcon listener on OSX
- Fixed logFilePath logic on OSX

Enhancements:
- Update ExchangeSession test
- Exclude optional log4j maven dependencies
- Added a logFilePath setting to set log4j file appender path, this appender is now added dynamically to avoid davmail.log file create failure
- Upgrade Log4J to 1.2.15
- Make sure we do exit: catch exceptions before System.exit

Doc: 
- Document build process in FAQ

Known issues :
- Does not - yet - work with iPhone 3.0 Caldav
- Still issues with Exchange activeSync mode
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.3.0-584" date="2009-06-10" type="beta">
      <description>
        <p>
This release is mainly a deep refactoring: replaced deprecated 
jakarta slide library with jackrabbit and upgrade httpclient.
Also added client to gateway encryption (SSL) support, started I18N
(french and english available) and many bug fixes and enhancements.

I18N:
- I18N: FrameGatewayTray
- I18N: Format port numbers and add missing message
- I18N: improve startup log message
- I18N: remove Locale.ROOT not available under Java 1.5
- I18N: externalize and translate exception messages
- I18N: Do not apply i18n on log file
- I18N: french localization
- I18N: externalize all DavGatewayTray log statements for i18n
- I18N: ldap package
- I18N: davmail package
- I18N: start internationalization conversion

POP:
- POP: Defer message list after login phase and load only uid and size attributes
- POP: make sure the url is encoded correctly on delete

IMAP:
- IMAP: Detect fetch of a missing (probably deleted) message to avoid infinite loop with Thunderbird
- IMAP: reset icon after each command

SMTP:
- SMTP: fixed two bugs, header ignored because of Exchange 2007 from patch and bccbuffer 
 double xml encoding (=&gt; Delivery status notification)

LDAP:
- LDAP: improve ldap search logging

Doc:
- Add Mitchell V. Oliver as Java Contributor
- SSL certificate settings documentation in getting started
- Update OSX doc: credentials are mandatory in Directory Utility settings
- Add Eivind Tagseth as Java Contributor

Enhancements:
- Check java version in ant build.xml
- Fix ExchangeSession test
- Refactor DavProperty handling with new jackrabbit library
- Close idle connections to exchange after one minute
- Avoid 401 roundtrips
- Remove deprecated HttpException api
- Replace deprecated setRequestBody with setRequestEntity
- Refactor DavProperty handling with new jackrabbit library
- Update packaging and Maven POM after library update
- Major refactoring: replace deprecated jakarta slide with jackrabbit and upgrade httpclient
- Upgrade svnkit library
- Sort properties and display version in startup message
- Use interactive console certificate accept in headless and/or server mode
- Append svn build number to release name
- Additional login failover : get email from options page
- Replace greyscale inactive icon with a color icon
- Avoid nullpointerexception in Settings.setProperty
- Reinsert System.exit after clean shutdown to make sure we do exit
- Make all threads daemon and remove System.exit calls
- Patch 2790299 by Mitchell V. Oliver: Add support for SSL to client connections
- Remember previous checkConfig status to detect network down
- Fixes from audit
- Refactor email retrieval : do not throw IOException in failovers
- Implement BundleMessage.toString() for direct usage in Log4J logger
- Revert to simple class names in thread names
- Catch unknown host on session login
- Workaround for post logon script redirect
- Workaround for Exchange server misconfiguration: move galfind requests to mailPath or /exchange instead of /public
- Enhancements from audit
- Fix exchangeSession test class
- Improve BindException error message
- Cleanup from audit
- Improve exception handling
- Implement a last resort failover to build email from alias and domain name
- Limit redirects to 10 instead of 100
- Replace hardcoded strings
- Refactor SimpleDateFormat usage
- Reorganize packages

OSX:
- OSX: replace JavaApplicationStub link with actual file
- OSX: Move davmail.log to Library/Logs/DavMail on OSX
- OSX: Improve Mac OSX Java6 support
- OSX: fix regression on OSX Quit handler

Bugs fixed:
- Fix bug 2797272: Add disable update check
- Do not localize port numbers
- Replaced localhost check with the isLoopbackAddress() method, should be IPV6 compatible
- Fix regression : /exchange/ does not work for galfind under Exchange 2007
- Fixed 2717547: Unsupported filter attribute: apple-group-memberguid
- URI encode alias in getEmail()
- Fix SSLProtocolSocketFactory with HttpClient 3.1
- Reenable limited timeout on getReleasedVersion
- Always exclude NTLM authentication, not only for proxy authorization
- Fix 2717446 from Eivind Tagseth

Caldav:
- Caldav: fix unknown recipient message
- Caldav: do not send freebusy info if attendee is unknown
- Caldav: Improve calendar-color patch answer
- Caldav: implement HEAD request
- Improve network down detection for Caldav
- Caldav: No need to check connectivity on HTTPS
- Caldav: Fix Bug 2783595, allow empty lines in ICS content
- Caldav: Exclude RSVP=FALSE from notifications recipients list for Outlook 2003 compatibility
- Caldav: exclude invalid attendees address from recipient list
- Caldav: avoid duplicate / in event path
- Caldav: implement public shared calendar
- Caldav: In progress multi calendar support
- Caldav: fix regression in FreeBusy date handling
- Caldav: switch icon during event report
- Caldav: refactor CaldavConnection, prepare /public context
- Caldav: another special characters handling improvement
- Caldav: iCal decodes hrefs, not lightning =&gt; detect client in CaldavRequest
- Caldav: replace etag by resourcetag in getCalendarEtag
- Caldav: Send events back to the client after each get on REPORT request (avoid iCal timeout)
- Caldav: no inbox/outbox for delegated calendars
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
