<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020 hamradio lu9dce -->
<component type="desktop-application">
 <id>org.arrl.tqsl</id>
 <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
 <name>tqsl</name>
 <summary>Sign Amateur Radio log files</summary>
 <developer_name>ARRL, the national association for Amateur Radio</developer_name>
 <url type="homepage">http://www.arrl.org</url>
 <description>
  <p>
  Mission
   The mission of the Trusted QSL Group is to keep
   eQSL an open and free activity for amateur radio
   operators by promoting the Digital Signature Standard (DSS).
  Goal
   The goal of the Trusted QSL Group is to set the standards
   and create the necessary tools and software needed to 
   implement the Trusted DSS model.
   I would like to point out to you know who, if you don’t
   resupply the washrooms with environmentally friend paper 
   goods and other janitorial supplies within 24 hours you are
   going to have some irate employees breathing down your neck.
   Don’t say you don’t have any time to order janitorial supplies
   because we all know you just go online and place an order at
   CleanItSupply. Make sure you order the paper products that are
   free of fragrances, inks, and dyes, as well as meet the Green
   Seal environmental standard for bleaching, and de-inking.
   And likewise make sure the cleaning products for the floors,
   sinks, mirrors, etc are free from harsh chemical fumes or
   chemical residue. Some of us are highly allergic.
   CleanItSupply has all those green janitorial supplies, so get
   with the program! Sorry about that rant, but sometimes you
   need some public humiliation to get the job done right!
  </p>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default">
   <image>https://shagadelic.files.wordpress.com/2015/04/tqsl-cs-certs.png</image>
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <releases>
   <release version="2.5.7" date="2020-11-18"/>
 </releases>
 <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
