<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kmplayer</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">كي ام بلاير</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KMplayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMPlayerxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KMPlayer</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KMPlayer</name>
  <summary>Interface for MPlayer by KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">واجهة كدي لبرنامج MPlayer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Interfície per al MPlayer, creada per la comunitat KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Interfície per a MPlayer, creada per la comunitat KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Rozhraní pro MPlayer od KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Oberfläche für MPlayer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Περιβάλλον χρήσης για το MPlayer από το KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Interface for MPlayer by KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Interfaz para MPlayer creada por KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">KDE MPlayeri liides</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KDEk egindako MPlayer-rentzako interfazea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">KDE:n MPlayer-käyttöliittymä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Interface pour MPlayer par KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Interface para MPlayer de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Interfacie de KDE per MPlayer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Antarmuka untuk MPlayer oleh KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Interfaccia per MPlayer di KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE MPlayer 인터페이스</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Interface voor MPlayer door KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Brukargrensesnitt laga av KDE for MPlayer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Interfejs dla MPlayera w ramach KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Interface para o MPlayer do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Interface do KDE para o MPlayer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Интерфейс к MPlayer от KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Rozhranie pre MPlayer od KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">KDE vmesnik za MPlayer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Gränssnitt för Mplayer av KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">MPlayer için bir KDE arayüzü</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інтерфейс для MPlayer від KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxInterface for MPlayer by KDExx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE 的 MPlayer 界面</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">來自 KDE 的 MPlayer 介面</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KMPlayer is a simple frontend for MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">برنامج كي ام بلاير هو واجهة أمامية بسيطة لـ MPlayer / FFMpeg / Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KMPlayer és un frontal senzill per al MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMPlayer és un frontal senzill per a MPlayer/FFmpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KMPlayer ist eine einfache Benutzeroberfläche für MPlayer, FFMpeg oder Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KMPlayer είναι ένα απλό περιβάλλον χρήσης για τα MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KMPlayer is a simple frontend for MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KMPlayer es una sencilla interfaz para MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KMPlayer on MPlayeri/FFMpeg/Phononi lihtne kasutajaliides.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KMPlayer MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon-entzako aurrealdeko erraz bat da.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KMPlayer on yksinkertainen MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon-käyttöliittymä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KMPlayer est une interface simple pour MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KMPlayer é unha interface sinxela para MPlayer, FFMpeg e Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KMPlayer adalah sebuah frontend sederhana untuk MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KMPlayer è una semplice interfaccia per MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KMPlayer는 MPlayer/FFmpeg/Phonon 프론트엔드입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMPlayer is een eenvoudige frontend voor MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KMPlayer er eit enkelt brukar­grensesnitt til MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KMPlayer jest prostą nakładką na  MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMPlayer é uma interface simples para o MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KMPlayer é uma interface simples para o MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KMPlayer je jednoduchý frontend pre MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KMPlayer je preprosto začelje za MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KMplayer är ett enkelt gränssnitt för Mplayer, FFMpeg och Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KMPlayer, MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon için yalın bir ön yüzdür.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMPlayer є простим інтерфейсом до MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMPlayer is a simple frontend for MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KMPlayer 是一款 MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon 简易前端程序。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KMPlayer 是個 MPlayer/FFMpeg/Phonon 的簡易前端。</p>
    <p>Some features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">بعض المزايا:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Algunes característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Algunes característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Einige Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ορισμένες λειτουργίες</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Some features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Algunas funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Mõned omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Eginbide batzuk:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Joitakin ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Quelques fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Algunhas funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Beberapa fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Alcune funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">주요 기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Enkele mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Nokre funksjonar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Niektóre z możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Algumas funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Alguns recursos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Niektoré funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Nekaj zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Några funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Bazı özellikleri:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Деякі з можливостей:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSome features:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">部分特性：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">部份功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>play DVD/VCD movies (from file or url and from a video device)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تشغيل أفلام DVD / VCD (من ملف أو عنوان ومن جهاز فيديو)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">reprodueix pel·lícules en DVD/VCD (des d'un fitxer o URL i des d'un dispositiu de vídeo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">reproduïx pel·lícules en DVD/VCD (des d'un fitxer o URL i des d'un dispositiu de vídeo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Wiedergabe von DVD/VCD-Filmen aus einer Datei oder URL und von Videogeräten</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">αναπαραγωγή ταινιών DVD/VCD (από αρχείο ή url και από συσκευή βίντεο)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">play DVD/VCD movies (from file or URL and from a video device)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Reproducir películas de DVD/VCD (desde archivos, URL o dispositivos de vídeo).</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">DVD/VCD filmide esitamine (failist või URL-ilt või videoseadmest)</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">DVD/VCD filmak jotzea (fitxategi edo URL-tik eta bideo gailu batetik)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">DVD/VCD-toisto (tiedostosta, verkko-osoitteesta tai videolaitteelta)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">lecture de films DVD/VCD (depuis un fichier ou une « URL » et depuis un lecteur vidéo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">reproducir películas de DVD ou VCD (desde un ficheiro, URL ou dispositivo de vídeo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">putar film DVD/VCD (dari file atau url dan dari peranti video)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">riproduci film su DVD/VCD (da file o URL o da un dispositivo video)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">DVD/VCD 재생(파일이나 비디오 장치 URL에서)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">dvd/vcd films afspelen (uit bestand of URL en vanaf een videoapparaat)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Avspeling av DVD- og VCD-filmar (frå fil, nettadresse eller fysisk plate)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">odtwarzanie filmów DVD/VCD (z pliku lub adresu URL oraz z urządzenia obrazu)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">reproduzir filmes em DVD/VCD (de ficheiros, URL's ou de um dispositivo de vídeo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">reproduz filmes em DVD/VCD (a partir do arquivo ou URL e de um dispositivo de vídeo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">prehrávať DVD/VCD filmy (zo súboru alebo URL a z video zariadenia)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">predvaja filme DVD/VCD (iz datoteke ali spletnega naslova in iz video naprave)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Spela DVD- och VCD-filmer (från fil eller webbadress, och från videoenhet)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">DVD/VCD filmlerini izle (dosyadan, URL'den veya bir video aygıtından)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">відтворення відео з DVD/VCD (з файла або адреси та з пристрою для читання носіїв відео)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxplay DVD/VCD movies (from file or url and from a video device)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">播放 DVD/VCD 影片 (来自文件、URL 或来自视频设备)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">播放 DVD/VCD 影片（從檔案或網址，及從影片裝置）</li>
      <li>embed inside konqueror (movie is played inside konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تضمين داخل كونكيور (يشغل الفيلم داخل كونكيور)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">incrustat dins el Konqueror (la pel·lícula es reprodueix dins el Konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">incrustat dins Konqueror (la pel·lícula es reproduïx dins Konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Eingebettet in Konqueror, der Film wird in Konqueror abgespielt</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">ενσωμάτωση στον konqueror (η ταινία αναπαράγεται μέσα στον konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">embed inside konqueror (movie is played inside konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Integración con Konqueror (las películas se reproducen desde dentro de Konqueror).</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Lõimimine Konqueroriga (filmi esitamine Konqueroris)</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Konqueror-ren barruan txertatua (filma Konqueror-ren barruan jotzen da)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">upotus Konqueroriin (videotoisto Konqueror-ikkunassa)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">intégration au sein de konqueror (lecture du film au sein de konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">incrustar en konqueror (a película reprodúcese dentro de konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">tertanam di dalam konqueror (film diputar di dalam konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">integrato in konqueror (il film viene riprodotto dentro konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">Konqueror 내장(Konqueror 내에서 동영상 재생)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">ingebed in konqueror (film wordt afgespeeld binnen konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Kan byggjast inn i Konqueror (filmen vert avspela inni programmet)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">osadzanie wewnątrz konqueror (obraz jest odtwarzany wewnątrz konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">pode ser incorporado dentro do Konqueror (o vídeo é reproduzido dentro do mesmo)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">embutido no Konqueror (o filme é reproduzido dentro do Konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">vložiť do kontajnera (film sa prehráva cez Konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">vdelan v konqueror (film se predvaja v konquerorju)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inbäddning inne i Konqueror (filmen spelas inne i Konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">konqueror içine göm (film, konqeror içinde oynatılır)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вбудовування до kKnqueror (відтворення відео безпосередньо у вікні Konqueror)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxembed inside konqueror (movie is played inside konqueror)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">嵌入到 konqueror 中 (在 konqueror 中播放影片)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在 Konqueror 嵌入（在 Konqueror 中播放影片）</li>
      <li>embed inside khtml (movie playback inside a html page)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">التضمين داخل khtml (تشغيل الفيلم داخل صفحة html)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">incrustat dins el «khtml» (la pel·lícula es reprodueix dins una pàgina HTML)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">incrustat dins «khtml» (la pel·lícula es reproduïx dins una pàgina HTML)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Eingebettet in KHTML, der Film wird in einer HTML-Seite abgespielt</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">ενσωμάτωση σε khtml (η ταινία αναπαράγεται μέσα σε σελίδα html)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">embed inside khtml (movie playback inside a html page)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Integración con khtml (las películas se reproducen dentro de las páginas HTML).</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Lõimimine KHTML-iga (filmi esitamine HTML-leheküljel)</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">khtml barruan txertatua (filma atzera-jotzea html orri baten barruan)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">upotus khtml:ään (videotoisto HTML-sivulla)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">intégration au sein de khtml (lecture du film au sein d'une page html)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">incrustar en khtml (reprodución da película nunha páxina html)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">tertanam di dalam khtml (film diputar di dalam halaman khtml)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">integrato in khtml (il film viene riprodotto in una pagina html)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">KHTML 내장(HTML 페이지 내에서 동영상 재생)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">ingebed in khtml ( film afspelen binnen een html-pagina)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Kan byggjast inn i KHTML (filmen vert avspela inni ei HTML-nettside)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">osadzanie wewnątrz khtml (obraz jest odtwarzany wewnątrz strony html)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">pode ser incorporado dentro do khtml (reprodução do vídeo dentro de uma página HTML)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">embutido dentro do KHTML (o filme é reproduzido dentro de uma página HTML)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">vložiť do KHTML (film sa prehráva cez HTML stránku)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">vdelan v khtml (film predvaja znotraj strani html)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inbäddning inne i KHTML (uppspelning av fil på en HTML-sida)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">khtml içine göm (film, bir html sayfası içinde oynatılır)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вбудовування до khtml (відтворення відео на сторінках HTML)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxembed inside khtml (movie playback inside a html page)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">嵌入到 khtml 中 (在 html 页面中播放影片)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在 khtml 中嵌入（在 html 頁面中播放影片）</li>
      <li>Movie recording using mencoder (part of the mplayer package)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تسجيل الفيلم باستخدام Mencoder (جزء من حزمة mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Enregistrament de pel·lícules usant el «mencoder» (part del paquet «mplayer»)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gravació de pel·lícules utilitzant «mencoder» (part del paquet «mplayer»)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Filmaufnahme mit dem Programm mencoder, einem Bestandteil des Pakets MPlayer</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Η εγγραφή της ταινίας γίνεται με mencoder (τμήμα του πακέτου mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Movie recording using mencoder (part of the mplayer package)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Grabación de películas mediante mencoder (que es parte del paquete mplayer).</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Filmi salvestamine mencoder'i abil (see kuulub tarkvarapaketti mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Filma-grabatzea mencoder erabiliz (mplayer paketearen zati bat da)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">videotallennus mencoderilla (osa mplayer-pakettia)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Enregistrement de films à l'aide de mencode (faisant partie du paquet mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Gravación de películas con mencoder (parte do paquete mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Perekaman film menggunakan mencoder (bagian dari paket mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Registrazione dei file utilizzando mencoder (parte del pacchetto mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">mencoder로 동영상 녹화(mplayer 패키지의 일부)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Film opnemen met mencoder (onderdeel van het pakket mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Filmopptak med Mencoder (del av «mplayer»-pakken)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Nagrywanie obrazu przy użyciu mencoder (części pakietu mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gravação de filmes com o 'mencoder' (parte do pacote 'mplayer')</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Gravação de filme usando o mencoder (parte do pacote mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nahrávanie filmov pomocou mencodera (časť balíka mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Snemanje filma s programom mencoder (del paketa mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Filminspelning med användning av Mencoder (som ingår i Mplayer-paketet)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">mencoder kullanarak film kaydı (mplayer paketinin bir parçası)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">запис відео за допомогою mencoder (є частиною пакунка з mplayer)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxMovie recording using mencoder (part of the mplayer package)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">使用 mencoder 录制影片 (mencoder 是 mplayer 软件包的一部分)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">使用 memcoder 錄製影片（mplayer 軟體包的一部分）</li>
      <li>No video during recording, but you can always open a new window and play it</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">لا يوجد فيديو أثناء التسجيل، ولكن يمكنك دائمًا فتح نافذة جديدة وتشغيلها</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">No hi ha vídeo durant l'enregistrament, però sempre es pot obrir una finestra nova i reproduir-lo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">No hi ha vídeo durant la gravació, però sempre es pot obrir una finestra nova i reproduir-lo</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Keine Video-Wiedergabe während einer Aufnahme, aber Sie können immer ein neues Fenster zur Wiedergabe öffnen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Δεν υπάρχει βίντεο κατά την εγγραφή, αλλά μπορείτε πάντα να ανοίξετε ένα νέο παράθυρο για αναπαραγωγή</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">No video during recording, but you can always open a new window and play it</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Sin vídeo durante la grabación, aunque siempre se puede abrir una nueva ventana para reproducirlo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kuigi salvestamise ajal videot ei näe, võib alati avada uue akna ja seda seal vaadata</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bideorik ez grabatu bitartean, baino beti ireki dezakezu leiho berri bat eta hura jo</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">ei tallennuksen aikaista videota, mutta toistoa varten voi avata uuden ikkunan</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Pas de vidéo durant l'enregistrement, mais vous pouvez toujours ouvrir une nouvelle fenêtre et le jouer</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Non hai vídeo mentres se grava, pero pode abrir unha nova xanela e reproducilo</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tidak ada video selagi merekam, tetapi kamu selalu bisa membuka window baru dan memutarnya</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Nessun video durante la registrazione, ma puoi sempre aprire una nuova finestra e riprodurlo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">녹화 중에는 영상을 자동으로 재생하지 않지만 새 창으로 영상을 볼 수 있습니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Geen video gedurende opnemen, maar u kunt altijd een nieuw venster openen en het afspelen</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Kan ikkje visa video ved opptak, men du kan opna eit nytt vindauge av spela han av der</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Brak obrazu podczas nagrywania, lecz zawsze można otworzyć nowe okno i odtworzyć go</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Não há vídeo durante a gravação, mas poderá abrir uma nova janela e reproduzi-lo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nenhum vídeo durante a gravação, mas você pode sempre abrir uma nova janela e executá-lo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Žiadne video počas nahrávania, ale vždy môžete otvoriť nové okno na jeho prehranie</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Med snemanjem sicer ni videoposnetka, a vedno lahko odprete novo okno in ga predvajate</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ingen video under inspelning, men det går alltid att öppna ett nytt fönster och spela upp den</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kayıt sırasında video yoktur; ancak her zaman yeni bir pencere açıp onu oynatabilirsiniz</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">вимикання показу відео на час запису, але ви завжди можете відкрити нове вікно і відтворити його</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxNo video during recording, but you can always open a new window and play itxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">录制时没有视频，但您可以随时打开一个新窗口并播放视频</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">錄影途中不會有影片，但你永遠皆可開啟新視窗播放</li>
      <li>Broadcasting, http streaming, using ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">البث، تدفق http، باستخدام ffserver / ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Difusió, flux de dades per «http», usa «ffserver»/«ffmpeg»</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Difusió, flux de dades per «http», utilitza «ffserver»/«ffmpeg»</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Broadcasting und HTTP-Streaming mit ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Μετάδοση, ροή http, με χρήση ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Broadcasting, http streaming, using ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Emisión y retransmisión HTTP, mediante el uso de ffserver/ffmpeg.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Levitamine, HTTP-voogesitus ffserver'i/ffmpeg abil</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Emankizunak, http korronteak, ffserver/ffmpeg erabiliz</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">lähetys ja HTTP-suoratoisto ffserverillä/ffmpegillä</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Diffusion, streaming http, grâce à ffserver / ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Emisión regular e por https usando ffserver ou ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Menyiarkan, http streaming, menggunakan ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Trasmissione, trasmissione http, utilizzando ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">ffserver/ffmpeg를 사용한 방송 및 HTTP 스트리밍</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Uitzending, http-streaming, met ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Kringkasting/HTTP-strauming med ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Rozsyłanie sygnału, strumieniowanie http, używa ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Difusão, transmissão por HTTP, usando o 'ffserver/ffmpeg'</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Broadcasting, streaming via HTTP usando o ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vysielanie, http streamovanie, mocou ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Oddajanje, pretakanje http, z uporabo programov ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Utsändning, HTTP-strömning med användning av ffserver och ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">ffserver/ffmpeg kullanarak yayın yapma ve http akışı</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">трансляція відео, потоків відеоданих http за допомогою ffserver/ffmpeg</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxBroadcasting, http streaming, using ffserver/ffmpegxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">使用 ffserver/ffmpeg 进行广播和 http 推流</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">使用 ffserver 或 ffmpeg 廣播和 HTTP 串流</li>
      <li>For TV sources, you need v4lctl (part of the xawtv package)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">بالنسبة لمصادر التلفاز ، تحتاج إلى v4lctl (جزء من حزمة xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Per a les fonts de TV, cal «v4lctl» (part del paquet «xawtv»)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Per a les fonts de TV, cal «v4lctl» (part del paquet «xawtv»)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Für TV-Quellen brauchen Sie die Bibliothek v4lctl, die im Paket xawtv enthalten ist</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Για πηγές TV, χρειάζεστε v4lctl (τμήμα του πακέτου xmltv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">For TV sources, you need v4lctl (part of the xawtv package)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Para las fuentes de TV necesita v4lctl (que es parte del paquete xawtv).</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Teleallikate kasutamiseks läheb vaja v4lctl'i (see kuulub tarkvarapaketti xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">TB iturrietarako, v4lctl behar duzu (xawtv paketearen zati bat da)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">TV-lähteisiin tarvitaan v4lctl (osa xawtv-pakettia)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Pour les sources TV, vous aurez besoin de v4lctl (qui fait partie du paquet xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Para fontes de TV necesita v4lctl (parte do paquete xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Untuk sumber TV, kamu perlu v4lctl (bagian dari paket xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Per le sorgenti TV, hai bisogno di v4lctl (parte del pacchetto xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">TV를 보려면 v4lctl이 필요합니다(xawtv 패키지에 포함됨)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Voor tv-bronnen, u hebt v4lctl nodig (onderdeel van het pakket xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">For TV-kjelder treng du v4lctl (del av «xawtv»-pakken)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dla źródeł TV, potrzebujesz v4lctl (część pakietu xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Para fontes de TV, precisa do 'v4lctl' (parte do pacote 'xawtv')</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Para fontes de TV você precisa do v4lctl (parte do pacote xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Pre TV zdroje potrebujete v4lctl (časť balíka xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Za TV vire potrebujete program v4lctl (del paketa xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">För tv-källor behövs v4lctl (som ingår i xawtv-paketet)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">TV kaynakları için v4lctl gereklidir (xawtv paketinin bir parçası)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">для джерел телевізійного сигналу вам знадобиться v4lctl (частина пакунка xawtv)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFor TV sources, you need v4lctl (part of the xawtv package)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">对于电视来源，需要使用 v4lctl (v4lctl 是 xawtv 软件包的一部分)</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">若為 TV 來源，則需要 v4lctl（xawtv 軟體包的一部分）</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmplayer</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kmplayer</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kmplayer/kmplayer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmplayer</binary>
  </provides>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.12.0b" date="2016-09-24" />
    <release version="0.12.0a" date="2016-07-10" />
    <release version="0.12.0" date="2016-06-02" />
    <release version="0.11.5b" date="2016-07-10" />
    <release version="0.11.5a" date="2016-06-02" />
    <release version="0.11.5" date="2015-12-20" />
    <release version="0.11.4" date="2015-09-19" />
  </releases>
</component>
