<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.electrum.electrum</id>
  <name>Electrum</name>
  <developer_name>spesmilo</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.spesmilo.Electrum.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <summary>Lightweight Bitcoin client</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Main features are:
      <ul>
	<li>- Encrypted wallet: the file that contains bitcoin private keys is protected with a password, and never leaves the user's computer</li>
	<li>- Deterministic key generation: If you lose your wallet file, you can recover it from its seed. You are protected from your own mistakes</li>
	<li>- Instant on: by default the client does not download the blockchain, it requests that information from a server. No delays, always up-to-date</li>
	<li>- Transactions are signed locally: Your private keys are not shared with the server. You do not have to trust the server with your money</li>
	<li>- Cold storage: Keeping private keys offline is supported. Has a watch-only mode for online use</li>
	<li>- Multisignature: Dividing the power to spend coins between multiple wallets is supported</li>
	<li>- Hardware wallet integration: Many leading hardware wallets can interface with Electrum</li>
	<li>- Redundancy: You are not tied to a particular server, and the server does not need to know you. One server going down doesn't cause user downtimes</li>
	<li>- No single point of failure: The server code is open source, anyone can run a server. Private keys can be exported and imported into other wallets</li>
	<li>- Firewall friendly: The client does not need to open a port, it simply polls the server for updates</li>
	<li>- Free software: MIT License. Anyone can audit the code</li>
	<li>- Written in Python. The code is short, and easy to review</li>
	<li>- Add-ons: third-party plugins are supported</li>
	<li>- Support for Bitcoin URIs, signed URIs and Bitcoin aliases.</li>
      </ul>
    </p>
  </description>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://electrum.org/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>https://en.bitcoin.it/w/images/en/f/fc/Capture-Electrum.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release date="2019-01-26" version="3.3.8"/>
  </releases>
  <update_contact>electrumdev@gmail.com</update_contact>
</component>
