<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.standardnotes.standardnote</id>

  <name>Standard Notes</name>
  <summary>A simple and private place for your notes, thoughts, and life's work</summary>

  <developer_name>Standard Notes Ltd.</developer_name>
  <agreement type="privacy" version_id="1.0">
    <agreement_section>
      <name>What we collect and how we use the collected data</name>
      <description>
        <p>We respect your privacy.</p>
        <p>We do not under any form collect, store, or share any personal imformation from users of the app.</p>
        <p>If you use a self-hosted or third-party RSS service with this app, the service may be able to see your activities through the API.</p>
        <p>A temporary cookies session that would be destoyed when the app closes is used to minimize third-party tracking when displaying third party contents.</p>
      </description>
    </agreement_section>
  </agreement>

  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>AGPL-3.0</project_license>

  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>

  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>TextTools</category>
  </categories>

  <description>
    <p>Standard Notes is a simple and private notes app. It syncs your notes securely across all your devices, including
      your Android devices, Windows, iOS, Linux, and Web.</p>

    <p>Private means your notes are end-to-end encrypted, so only you can read your notes. Even we can't read the contents
      of your notes.</p>

    <p>Simple means it does one job and does it well. Standard Notes is a safe and lasting place for your life's work. Our
      focus is making it easy to write notes wherever you are and syncing them with encryption to all your devices.</p>

    <p>Our users love us for:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Personal Notes</li>
      <li>Tasks &amp; Todos</li>
      <li>Passwords &amp; Keys</li>
      <li>Code &amp; Technical Procedures</li>
      <li>Private Journal</li>
      <li>Meeting Notes</li>
      <li>Cross-platform Scratchpad</li>
      <li>Books, Recipes, &amp; Movies</li>
      <li>Health &amp; Fitness Log</li>
    </ul>

    <p>Standard Notes comes free with:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Seamless sync across all your devices, with easy to use applications on Android, Windows, Linux, iPhone, iPad,
          Mac,
          and web browsers.</li>
      <li>Offline access, so you can access your downloaded notes even without a connection.</li>
      <li>No limit on number of devices.</li>
      <li>No limit on number of notes.</li>
      <li>Passcode lock protection, along with fingerprint protection.</li>
      <li>A tagging system to organize your notes (like #work, #ideas, #passwords, #crypto).</li>
      <li>The ability to pin, lock, protect, and move notes to trash, which allows you to recover deleted notes until the
          trash is emptied.</li>

    </ul>
    <p>Standard Notes is completely open-source, which means when we say your notes are encrypted with AES-256 encryption,
      and that only you can read your notes, you don't have to take our word for it. Our code is open to the world to
      audit.</p>

    <p>We made Standard Notes simple because longevity is important to us. We want to make sure we're here, protecting your
      notes, for the next hundred years. You shouldn't have to find a new notes app every year.</p>

    <p>To sustain our development, we offer an optional paid program called Standard Notes Extended. Extended gives you
      access to powerful tools including:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Productivity editors (like Markdown, Code, Spreadsheets)</li>
      <li>Beautiful themes (like Midnight, Focus, Solarized Dark)</li>
      <li>Powerful cloud tools including daily backups of your encrypted data delivered to your email inbox every day, or
          backed up to your cloud provider (like Dropbox and Google Drive).</li>
    </ul>
    <p>You can learn more about Extended at standardnotes.org/extended.</p>

    <p>We're always happy to talk, whether it be a question, thought, or issue. Please feel free to email us any time at
      help@standardnotes.org. When you take the time to send us a message, we'll be sure to do the same.</p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.standardnotes.standardnotes.desktop</launchable>

  <url type="homepage">https://standardnotes.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/standardnotes/desktop/issues/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://github.com/sponsors/standardnotes</url>
  <url type="help">https://standardnotes.org/help</url>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2019/11/Screenshot_1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2019/11/Screenshot_2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2019/11/Screenshot_3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2019/11/Screenshot_4.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="v3.5.18" date="2021-01-27" />
  </releases>
</component>