<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020 TLauncher Inc. -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.tlauncher.TLauncher</id>
  <name>TLauncher</name>
  <summary>The launcher for Minecraft</summary>
  <developer_name>TLauncher Inc.</developer_name>

  <description>
    <p>Today not many good launcher for the game Minecraft, but they are
    still there, and one of them TLauncher.</p>

    <p><em>All official versions, from Alpha to Snapshots:</em>The launcher
    is equipped with all available versions of the game developers, at any
    time, you will be able to install one of them, even the newest Minecraft
    version 1.15. They had not made any changes, all files are downloaded
    from the server developers, and that means you get perfectly clean
    Minecraft.</p>

    <p><em>Install Forge, OptiFine one click:</em> Thanks TLauncher, you have
    it is possible to install a modified version of the game: Forge is
    required to work with mods Optifine - to optimize the game and increase
    FPS. All of this can be installed separately, but we'll have to search
    and suffer from the widest setting, the same launcher will do everything
    for you, you need to choose only the necessary version. Imagine how much
    time you'll save, and in fact quite.</p>

    <p><em>Our own system skins:</em> At our website, you will be able to set
    your own skin, which will see all the users TLauncher, and I can assure
    you, the majority use our launcher. System skins is not inferior to the
    official, even has several advantages: the installation of cloak and HD
    skins.</p>

    <p><em>Login with a licensed account:</em> Do not stop to play through
    your license account, use all its advantages: a License server, the
    system skins, your nickname and all the best parties TLauncher, it is
    enough to log in under your email and password. Of course requests are
    sent straight to the developers server in encrypted form, no one will
    ever get access to your account only maximum security!</p>

    <p><em>Launcher with mods:</em> Create your own builds with mods in one
    click, with our new mod-pack system! A huge catalog of mods, maps,
    resource packs with full description and screenshots is already waiting
    for you. The system helps to avoid various errors, as it checks for
    compatibility of each mod installed by you. There is a system of backup
    and manual installation. Plus, everything is absolutely free, without any
    restrictions on our part. Enjoy yourself and do not forget to recommend
    to friends our launcher with mods!</p>

    <p><em>Reliability and support:</em> We continuously improve our product,
    so bugs stay in your Minecraft, in principle, can not be - they are all
    fixed! Of course, thanks to our players who contact us via the website or
    directly launcher and report all their problems. We can help everyone, so
    don't be afraid to write!</p>

    <p><em>Competitiveness:</em> Clearly, you've never seen one launcher for
    the game, but obviously found a lot of flaws and not improvements, so
    you're here to get the maximum emotion from Minecraft, because of the
    huge amount of content and functions provided by us. We are a step ahead
    of many and always will be, because the development TLauncher does not
    stop not for one day!</p>
  </description>

  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>

  <url type="homepage">https://tlauncher.org/en/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://tlauncher.org/en/send-bug-tlauncher.html</url>
  <url type="donation">https://tlauncher.org/en/premium.html</url>
  <url type="help">https://tlauncher.org/en/help.html</url>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.mojang.Minecraft/master/screenshots/minecraft1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/com.mojang.Minecraft/master/screenshots/minecraft2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>

  <releases>
    <release date="2020-02-27" version="2.69">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added the Shaders tab to the Mod-pack system. Improving the appearance of the game has become much easier!</li>
          <li>Improvements and fixes for the stability of the program.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.tlauncher.TLauncher.desktop</launchable>
  <update_contact>jurf_at_riseup.net</update_contact>
</component>
