<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Kevin Degeling -->

<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.yamagi.YamagiQ2</id>
  <name>Yamagi Q2</name>
  <summary>Yamagi Quake II is an alternative client for id Softwares Quake II</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>

  <developer_name>Yamagi team</developer_name>
  <update_contact>gnome@kevindegeling.nl</update_contact>

  <url type="homepage">https://ezquake.github.io/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/ezQuake/ezquake-source</url>
  <url type="help">https://ezquake.github.io/manual.html</url>
  <url type="contact">https://www.quakeworld.nu/forum</url>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.ezQuake.desktop</launchable>

  <description>
    <p>
      Welcome to the home of ezQuake, a modern QuakeWorld client focused on competitive online play. Combining the features of modern QuakeWorld® clients, ezQuake makes QuakeWorld® easier to start and play. The immortal first person shooter Quake® in a brand new skin with superb graphics and extremely fast gameplay.
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Modern Graphics: Particle explosions, shaft beam, gunshots, nails, rocket and grenade trails, blood, and others, MD3 models, fog, water effects, killing spree messages, rain</li>
      <li>Modern competitive gaming features: Fullbright skins, forcing team/enemy colors, advanced weapon handling, teamplay messages, auto game recording, automated screenshots and console logging</li>
      <li>Graphics customization: Customize your HUD, colors of walls and liquids, turn superfluous graphics effects off, change world textures, crosshair, sky picture, console background, game font</li>
      <li>Independent Physics: Get the smoothest experience possible without being limited by server or network settings</li>
      <li>Integrated Server Browser: Easy searching and filtering of online servers</li>
      <li>Enhanced demo/QTV playback: View recorded games from multiple points of view, watch action on radar, all player stats in a handy table, autotrack the strongest player</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
     Commercial data files are required to run the supported games. These can be aquired though a multitude of sources. See the manual for more info on this.
    </p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://ezquake.github.io/screenshots/armor_battle.png</image>
      <caption>Battle for armor</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://ezquake.github.io/screenshots/bloom.jpg</image>
      <caption>Bloom effect</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://ezquake.github.io/screenshots/shambler_cutf_bluefog.jpg</image>
      <caption>Special effects</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="3.1.0" date="2019-09-24">
      <description>
        <p>First release of ezQuake on Flatpak.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">moderate</content_attribute>
    <!-- Full multiplayer functionality with voicechat support -->
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>

