<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.ktouch.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ktouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKTouchxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KTouch</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">打字練習_KTouch</name>
  <summary>Touch Typing Tutor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">Intruktor kucanja na tastaturi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Tutor de mecanografia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Tutor de mecanografia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Výuka psaní na stroji</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Schreibmaschinenkurs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Touch Typing Tutor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Lernilo por la tajpado</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Tutor de mecanografía al tacto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Klaviatuuri treening</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Konekirjoituksen harjoitteluohjelma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Formateur en dactylographie KTouch</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Titor de mecanografía</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Tutorial Pengetikan Setuh</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Istruttore di dattilografia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">타자 연습</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Treniruoklė aklajam teksto rinkimui</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Schriefmaschien öven</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Typcursus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Tastaturøving</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Nauczyciel bezwzrokowego pisania</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Professor de Dactilografia</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Aulas de digitação</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Клавиатурный тренажёр</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Výuka písania na stroji</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Učenje slepega tipkanja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Maskinskrivningsträning</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">On Parmak Öğretici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Навчання комп’ютерного набору</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxTouch Typing Tutorxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">触摸打字教程</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">觸摸輸入輔助教學</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KTouch is a typewriter trainer for learning to touch type. It provides you with text to train on and adjusts to different levels depending on how good you are. It displays your keyboard and indicates which key to press next and which is the correct finger to use. You learn typing with all fingers, step by step, without having to look down at the keyboard to find your keys. It is convenient for all ages and the perfect typing tutor for schools, universities, and personal use. KTouch ships with dozens of different courses in many languages and a comfortable course editor. Different keyboard layouts are supported and new user-defined layouts can be created. During training, KTouch collects comprehensive statistical information to help you or your teacher to analyze your progress.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">KTouch je trener za učenje kucanja na pisaćoj mašini. On vam pruža tekst za trenirati i prilagođava na različite nivoe zavisno od toga koliko ste dobri. On prikazuje tastaturu i ukazuje na to koji taster pritisnuti sljedeći i koji je ispravan prst za korištenje. Učite kucanje sa svim prstima, korak po korak, bez da pogledom dolje na tastaturi pronađete svoje tastere. On je pogodan za sve uzraste i savršen učitelj kucanja za škole, univerzitete i osobnu upotrebu. KTouch dolazi s desecima različitih kurseva za mnoge jezike i udobnim urednikom kurseva. Različite tastature su podržane i novi korisnički definirani rasporedi mogu biti kreirani. Tokom treninga, KTouch prikuplja sveobuhvatne statističke podatke koji će pomoći vama ili vašem učitelj da analizirate vaš napredak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KTouch és un entrenador mecanogràfic per aprendre mecanografia. Proporciona text per entrenar i s'ajusta a diferents nivells en funció del vostre nivell. Mostra el teclat i indica la tecla següent a prémer i quin és el dit correcte a utilitzar. Aprendreu mecanografia amb tots els dits, pas a pas, sense haver de mirar el teclat per cercar les tecles. És apropiat per a totes les edats i és el tutor de mecanografia perfecte per escoles, universitats i ús personal. El KTouch es distribueix amb dotzenes de cursos diferents en molts idiomes i un editor còmode de cursos. S'accepten diferents disposicions de teclat i es poden crear noves disposicions definides per l'usuari. Durant l'entrenament, el KTouch acumula informació estadística global per ajudar-vos a analitzar el progrés.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KTouch és un entrenador mecanogràfic per aprendre mecanografia. Proporciona text per entrenar i s'ajusta a diferents nivells en funció del vostre nivell. Mostra el teclat i indica la tecla següent a prémer i quin és el dit correcte a utilitzar. Aprendreu mecanografia amb tots els dits, pas a pas, sense haver de mirar el teclat per cercar les tecles. És apropiat per a totes les edats i és el tutor de mecanografia perfecte per escoles, universitats i ús personal. El KTouch es distribueix amb dotzenes de cursos diferents en molts idiomes i un editor còmode de cursos. S'accepten diferents disposicions de teclat i es poden crear noves disposicions definides per l'usuari. Durant l'entrenament, el KTouch acumula informació estadística global per ajudar-vos a analitzar el progrés.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KTouch is a typewriter trainer for learning to touch type. It provides you with text to train on and adjusts to different levels depending on how good you are. It displays your keyboard and indicates which key to press next and which is the correct finger to use. You learn typing with all fingers, step by step, without having to look down at the keyboard to find your keys. It is convenient for all ages and the perfect typing tutor for schools, universities, and personal use. KTouch ships with dozens of different courses in many languages and a comfortable course editor. Different keyboard layouts are supported and new user-defined layouts can be created. During training, KTouch collects comprehensive statistical information to help you or your teacher to analyse your progress.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KTouch estas trejnilo por lerni tajpadon. Ĝi enhavas diversajn tekstojn por trejni per malsamaj niveloj laŭ via sperto. Ĝi montras vian klavaron kaj indikas kiun klavon premi  kaj kiun fingron uzi. Vi lernas tajpi per ĉiuj fingroj, paŝo post paŝo, sen rigardi la klavaron por trovi vian klavon. Ĝi estas oportuna por ĉiuj aĝoj kaj ĝi estas  perfekta lernilo por infanoj, plenkreskuloj, por lerneja celo, universitata celo kaj por persona uzo. KTouch disponeblas kun dekoj da malsamaj kursoj en multaj lingvoj kaj facile uzeblan redaktilon. Diversaj klavaranĝoj estas apogitaj kaj novaj aranĝoj kreeblas. Dum trejnado, KTouch kolektas multampleksajn statistikojn  por helpi vin analizi vian progreson.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KTouch es un entrenador de mecanografía para aprender a mecanografiar al tacto. Proporciona texto para entrenar y se adapta a diferentes niveles dependiendo del que tenga el usuario. Muestra el teclado actual e indica qué tecla hay que pulsar a continuación y cuál es el dedo que hay que utilizar para hacerlo. Se aprende a mecanografiar con todos los dedos, paso a paso, sin tener que mirar el teclado para encontrar las teclas. Es adecuado para todas las edades y el tutor de mecanografía perfecto para los colegios, universidades y uso personal. KTouch viene con docenas de cursos diferentes en muchos idiomas y un cómodo editor de cursos. Admite varias disposiciones de teclado y se pueden definir más.  Durante el entrenamiento, KTouch recopila información estadística exhaustiva para ayudar al usuario o a su profesor a analizar el progreso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KTouch on rakendus, mis aitab omandada masinkirjaoskust. See pakub harjutamiseks tekste ning kohandab tasemeid vastavalt sellele, millised on sinu oskused. Rakendus näitab klaviatuuri ning vihjab, millist klahvi ja millise sõrmega järgmisena vajutada. Tasapisi omandad rakenduse abil oskuse kirjutada kõigi kümne sõrmega, ilma et peaksid klaviatuurile vaatamagi. KTouch sobib igas vanuses õppurile ning sobib ühtmoodi hästi kasutada nii koolides, ülikoolides kui ka kodus. Rakendusega on kaasa kümneid kursuseid paljudes keeltes ning mugav kursuseredaktor. Toetatud on paljud klaviatuuripaigutused ja luua saab ka uusi, kasutaja enda määratud paigutusi. Harjutamise käigus kogub KTouch põhjaliku statistika, mis aitab sul endal või su õpetajal edenemist hinnata ja analüüsida.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KTouch on ohjelma kymmensormijärjestelmän harjoittelemiseen. Se tarjoaa harjoitustekstiä ja säätää vaikeustason riippuen käyttäjän taidoista. Se näyttää näppäimistö ja ilmaisee, mitä näppäintä painaa seuraavaksi ja millä sormella. Opit kirjoittamaan kaikilla sormilla, vaihe vaiheelta, katsomatta näppäimistöön etsimään näppäimiä. KTouch sopii kaikenikäisille omaan, koulujen ja yliopistojen käyttöön. KTouchin mukana tulee kymmeniä kursseja eri kielille ja kurssimuokkain, jota on mukava käyttää. Se tukee useita näppäimistöasetteluita ja käyttäjä voi luoda uusia. Harjoituksen aikana KTouch kerää kattavat tilastot, jotka auttavat harjoittelijaa tai hänen opettajaansa analysoimaan edistymistä.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KTouch est un programme d'entraînement pour la dactylographie. Il vous fournit du texte à recopier et s'adapte à votre niveau. Il affiche votre clavier et indique sur quelle touche appuyer et avec quel doigt. Vous apprenez à taper avec tous les doigts, étape par étape, sans avoir à regarder le clavier pour trouver les touches. Il convient à tous les âges et constitue un formateur parfait pour les écoles, les universités et les particuliers. KTouch est livré avec des dizaines de leçons différentes dans de nombreuses langues, ainsi qu'un éditeur de leçon. Différentes dispositions de clavier sont prises en charge et de nouvelles dispositions peuvent être créées par l'utilisateur. Pendant l'entraînement, KTouch collecte des informations statistiques complètes pour vous aider à analyser vos progrès.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KTouch é un adestrador de mecanografía. Fornécelle texto para adestrar e permite varios niveis dependendo da súa habilidade. Mostra o teclado e indica que tecla ten que premer a continuación e cal é o dedo correcto que debería usar. Aprende a mecanografar con todos os dedos, paso a paso, sen ter que mirar para o teclado para atopar as teclas. Está adaptado para todas as idades, e é perfecto para escolas e universidades, ou para uso persoal. KTouch inclúe ducias de cursos en varios idiomas e un cómodo editor de cursos. Permítese usar varias disposicións de teclado distintas, e pódense crear disposicións de teclado definidas polo usuario. Durante o adestramento, KTouch recolle información estatística para axudalo a vostede ou ao seu mestre a analizar o seu progreso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KTouch adalah pelatih mesin ketik untuk belajar mengetik. Ini memberimu teks untuk berlatih dan menyesuaikan ke tingkat yang berbeda tergantung pada seberapa baik kamu. Ini menampilkan keyboard-mu dan menunjukkan tombol mana yang harus ditekan berikutnya dan yang merupakan jari yang tepat untuk digunakan. Kamu belajar mengetik dengan semua jari, langkah demi langkah, tanpa harus melihat ke bawah pada keyboard untuk menemukan tutsmu. Ini nyaman untuk segala usia dan tutorial mengetik yang sempurna untuk sekolah, universitas, dan penggunaan pribadi. KTouch memberikan banyak kursus berbeda dalam banyak bahasa dan editor kursus yang nyaman. Tataletak keyboard yang berbeda didukung dan tataletak yang ditentukan pengguna dapat dibuat. Selama pelatihan, KTouch mengumpulkan informasi statistik komprehensif untuk membantumu atau gurumu menganalisis kemajuanmu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KTouch è un allenatore di dattilografia per imparare a dattilografare. Ti fornisce del testo con cui esercitarti, sceglie il livello adatto alle tue capacità; ti mostra anche il prossimo tasto da premere ed il dito corretto da usare. Ti insegna a scrivere con tutte le dita, passo dopo passo, cosicché non dovrai più guardare la tastiera ogni volta per cercare i tasti giusti: questo rallenta di parecchio la tua velocità di battitura. È utile a tutte le età, ed è un perfetto insegnante di battitura nelle scuole, nelle università e per uso personale. KTouch ti viene fornito con dozzine di corsi diversi in molte lingue, e con un comodo editor di corsi. Supporta diverse mappature di tastiera, ed altre possono essere create dall'utente. Durante l'allenamento KTouch raccoglie delle informazioni statistiche complete, che aiutano te o il tuo insegnante ad analizzare i tuoi progressi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">KTouch is en Programm, mit dat Du Schriefmaschien schrieven lehren kannst. Dat stellt Di de Öövtexten praat un passt de Sworheit dor na an, wo goot Du al büst. Dat wiest Dien Tastatuur, de Tast, de Du drücken schallst un den richtigen Finger dor för. Du lehrst dat Tippen mit all Fingers Schritt för Schritt, un ok, ahn dat Du na nerrn op de Tasten un Dien Fingers kieken muttst. Dat is goot för jünger un ok för öller Lüüd un en goot Tipplehrer för Scholen un Universiteten. Dor sünd KTouch en Barg verscheden Lexen in vele Spraken bi un en kommood Lexeneditor. dat ünnerstütt verscheden Tastanornen, Du kannst ok Dien egen Anornen opstellen. Bi't Öven sammelt KTouch Statistikinformatschonen, mit de Du oder Dien Lehrer Dien Vörankamen bekieken kannst.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KTouch is een oefenprogramma voor blindtypen. Het geeft u oefenteksten en past het oefenniveau aan aan uw huidige vaardigheid. Het toetsenbord wordt getoond, en de volgende toets die u moet aanslaan, en met welke vinger. U leert met alle vingers te typen, stap voor stap, zonder dat u op het toetsenbord naar de toetsen kijkt. Het is voor alle leeftijden geschikt, en perfect om te leren typen op school, de universiteit, of thuis. KTouch komt met tientallen verschillende cursussen in vele talen, en bevat een handige cursusbewerker. Diverse toetsenbordindelingen worden ondersteund, en u kunt ook nieuwe zelf aanmaken. Tijdens de oefeningen verzamelt KTouch uitvoerige statistische informatie, voor het beoordelen van uw vorderingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KTouch jest trenerem bezwzrokowego pisania na klawiaturze. Dostarcza teksty do ćwiczeń i dostosowuje się do poziomu użytkownika. Wyświetla klawiaturę, wskazuje, które klawisze nacisnąć i jakim palcem. Dzięki programowi uczysz się pisać wszystkimi palcami. Jest wygodny dla użytkowników w różnym wieku i idealny do ćwiczenia pisania w szkołach, uniwersytetach i czasie prywatnym. KTouch jest dostarczany z wieloma kursami w różnych językach oraz wygodnym edytorem kursów. Obsługiwane są różne układy klawiatury, można także dodawać układy stworzone przez użytkownika. Podczas ćwiczeń, KTouch zbiera wiele informacji statystycznych, aby pomóc tobie lub twojemu nauczycielowi analizować twój postęp.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KTouch é um treinador de dactilografia que o ensina a escrever à máquina. Oferece-lhe algum texto para treinar e ajusta-se a diferentes níveis, dependendo de quão bom você é. Ele mostra o seu teclado e indica a tecla a carregar a seguir e qual o dedo correcto a usar. Você aprende a escrever com todos os dedos, passo-a-passo, sem ter de olhar para baixo para o teclado e descobrir as suas teclas. É conveniente para todas as idades e é o tutor de escrita perfeito para escolas, universidades e uso pessoal. O KTouch vem com dezenas de exercícios diferentes em várias línguas e tem um editor de exercícios confortável. São suportados diferentes formatos de teclado e poderá criar novos formatos definidos pelo utilizador. Durante o exercício, o KTouch recolhe alguma informação estatística completa para o ajudar ou ao seu professor a analisar o seu progresso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KTouch é um programa que ensina a usar um teclado para digitação. Ele disponibiliza alguns textos para treinar e ajusta-se a diferentes níveis, dependendo da sua habilidade. Ele mostra o seu teclado e indica a próxima tecla a pressionar e qual o dedo correto a ser usado. Você aprende a digitar com todos os dedos, passo a passo, sem precisar olhar para o teclado e encontrar as teclas. É conveniente para todas as idades e é o tutor de digitação perfeito para escolas, universidades e uso pessoal. O KTouch vem com dezenas de exercícios diferentes em vários idiomas e tem um confortável editor de exercícios. São suportados diferentes layouts de teclado e novos layouts podem ser criados pelo usuário. Durante o treino, o KTouch recolhe informações estatísticas para ajudar você ou seu professor a analisar o seu progresso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KTouch je tréner písacieho stroja na výuku písania na stroji. Poskytuje vám texty na tréning a úpravu na rôzne úrovne v závislosti od vašej pokročilosti. Zobrazuje klávesnicu a ukazuje, ktoré klávesy treba najbližšie stlačiť a ktorý je správny prst na použitie. Naučíte sa písať všetkými prstami, krok za krokom bez nutnosti pozerať sa dolu na klávesnicu, aby ste našli klávesy. Je vhodný pre všetky vekové skupiny a výborný program pre školy, univerzity a osobné použitie. KTouch obsahuje mnoho rôznych kurzov v mnohých jazykoch a komfortný editor kurzov. Podporuje rôzne rozloženia klávesnice a umožňuje vytvoriť vlastné rozloženia. Počas tréningu zbiera štatistické informácie, aby vám pomohol analyzovať váš postup.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KTouch je program za učenje slepega tipkanja. Vključena ima besedila na katerih se lahko učite in jih sproti prilagaja vašim sposobnostim. Prikazuje tudi vašo tipkovnico in na njej označi katero tipko je treba pritisniti naslednjo in s katerim prstom. Korak za korakom se boste naučili tipkati z vsemi prsti, brez da bi morali gledati tipkovnico in na njej iskati tipke. Primeren je za vse starosti in je odlično orodje za učenje tipkanja v šoli, na univerzah ali doma. KTouch vsebuje številne tečaje v raznolikih jezikih in tudi urejevalnik tečajev. Podprte so različne razporeditve tipk, ustvarite pa lahko tudi lastne. Med vadbo KTouch zbira statistične podatke, ki lahko vam oz. vašem učitelju pomagajo pri preučevanju vašega napredka.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ktouch är ett program för att lära sig maskinskrivning. Det tillhandahåller en text att öva på, och justeras till olika nivåer, beroende på hur bra du är. Det visar tangentbordet och vilken tangent som ska tryckas ner härnäst, och det riktiga fingret som ska användas. Man lär sig att skriva med alla fingrar, steg för steg, utan att behöva titta ner på tangentbordet hela tiden för att hitta rätt tangenter. Det är bekvämt för alla åldrar och är perfekt för skrivmaskinsövning på skolor, universitet och vid personlig användning. Ktouch levereras med dussintals kurser på många språk och en bekväm kurseditor. Olika tangentbordslayouter stöds och nya användardefinierade layouter kan skapas. Under övningar samlar Ktouch in omfattande statistisk information för att hjälpa dig eller din lärare att analysera dina framsteg.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KTouch, on parmak yazma çalıştıran bir daktilo eğitmenidir. Ne kadar iyi olduğunuza bağlı olarak farklı seviyelerde eğitim almanız için metin hazırlar ve ayarlar. Klavyenizi görüntüler ve bir sonraki tuşa hangi klavye tuşunun kullanılacağını belirtir. Tuşları bulmak için klavyeye bakmanıza gerek kalmadan, adım adım ilerleyerek tüm parmaklarınızla yazmayı öğrenirsiniz. Her yaşa uygun, okullar, üniversiteler ve kişisel kullanım için mükemmel derecede yazmayı öğrenmek için uygundur. KTouch birçok dilde düzinelerce farklı ders ve kolay bir ders düzenleyiciyle birlikte geliyor. Farklı klavye düzenlerini destekler ve yeni kullanıcı tanımlı düzenler oluşturulabilir. Eğitim sırasında, KTouch size veya öğretmeninin ilerlesini analiz etmede size yardımcı olacak kapsamlı istatistiki bilgileri de toplar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KTouch — програма для навчання машинопису. Ви вводитимете навчальний текст, а програма визначатиме рівень складності цього тексту, залежно від ваших навичок. У вікні програми ви зможете бачити клавіатуру, підсвічування для клавіш, які слід натискати, та рекомендації щодо пальця, яким це слід робити. Ви зможете навчитися десятипальцевому набору, крок за кроком, не дивлячись на клавіатуру і не шукаючи на ній потрібних вам клавіш. Програму пристосовано для користувачів будь-якого віку, вона є чудовим засобом навчання для шкіл, університетів та особистих потреб. Разом з KTouch постачаються десятки різних курсів багатьма мовами, а також зручний редактор курсів. Передбачено підтримку різних розкладок клавіатур та можливість визначення власних розкладок. Під час навчання KTouch збирає статистичні дані, які допоможуть вам та вашому наставнику проаналізувати поступ навчання.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKTouch is a typewriter trainer for learning to touch type. It provides you with text to train on and adjusts to different levels depending on how good you are. It displays your keyboard and indicates which key to press next and which is the correct finger to use. You learn typing with all fingers, step by step, without having to look down at the keyboard to find your keys. It is convenient for all ages and the perfect typing tutor for schools, universities, and personal use. KTouch ships with dozens of different courses in many languages and a comfortable course editor. Different keyboard layouts are supported and new user-defined layouts can be created. During training, KTouch collects comprehensive statistical information to help you or your teacher to analyze your progress.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KTouch 是一套打字訓練程式。它可以訓練您打字，並依您的程度來調整訓練等級。它會顯示您的鍵盤，並指引您下一個要按下什麼鍵，以及該使用哪個指頭。您可以學習使用所有的指頭來打字，一步步，不需要看鍵盤來找鍵。所有的年齡層、所有程度的學校都適用，包括個人練習也可以。KTouch 中有多種不同的語言課程，並且提供了課程編輯器。它也支援不同的鍵盤佈局，也可以建立使用者自訂的鍵盤佈局。在訓練課程中，KTouch 會收集統計資料，協助您與您的老師分析追蹤您的進度。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://edu.kde.org/ktouch/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ktouch</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdeedu/ktouch/index.html</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=ktouch&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Training with KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Entrenant amb el KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Entrenant amb el KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Übungen mit KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Training with KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Entrenando con KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Entraînement sur KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Adestrando con KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Berlatih dengan KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Allenamento con KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Oefenen met KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Ćwiczenie w KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Exercício com o KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Treinando com o KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Tréning s KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Övning med Ktouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вправляння у KTouch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTraining with KTouchxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">使用 KTouch 训练</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">用 KTouch 訓練</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/ktouch/ktouch.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>ktouch</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0" />
  <releases>
    <release version="2019.08.0" date="2019-08-15"/>
  </releases>
</component>
