<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.freedesktop.LinuxAudio.Plugins.Ratatouille</id>
  <name>Ratatouille</name>
  <summary>Neural Model loader and mixer</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>BSD-3-Clause</project_license>
  <developer>
    <name>brummer10</name>
  </developer>
  <extends>org.freedesktop.LinuxAudio.BaseExtension</extends>
  <description>
    <p>
      Ratatouille is a Neural Model loader and mixer for Linux/Windows.
    </p>
    <p>
      It can load two models, which can be *.nam files with the Neural Amp Modeler module, or *.json or .aidax files with the RTNeural module.
    </p>
    <p>
      You can also load just a single model file, in that case the "Blend" control will do nothing. When you've loaded a second model, the "Blend" control will blend between the two models and mix them to simulate your specific tone.
    </p>
    <p>
      Ratatouille using parallel processing for the neural models, so, loading a second neural model wouldn't be remarkable on the dsp load.
    </p>
    <p>
      The "Delay" control could add a small delay to the second model to overcome phasing issues, or to add some color/reverb to the sound.
    </p>
    <p>
      To round up your sound you can load two Impulse Response Files and mix them to your needs. IR-files could be normalised on load, so that they didn't influence the loudness.
    </p>
    <p>
      Ratatouille.lv2 supports resampling when needed to match the expected sample rate of the loaded models. Both models and the IR Files may have different expectations regarding the sample rate.
      Neural network emulator for guitar amplifiers. LV2 plugin.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Plugin GUI</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/brummer10/Ratatouille.lv2/v0.8/Ratatouille.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/brummer10/Ratatouille.lv2</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/brummer10/Ratatouille.lv2/issues</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/brummer10/Ratatouille.lv2</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.8" date="2024-08-05">
      <url>https://github.com/brummer10/Ratatouille.lv2/releases/tag/v0.8</url>
      <description>
        <p>
          Ratatouille allow to load up to two neural model files and mix there output. Those models could be *.nam files or *.json or .aidax files. So you could blend from clean to crunch for example, or, go wild and mix different amp models, or mix a amp with a pedal simulation.
        </p>
        <p>
          Ratatouille using parallel processing to process the second neural model and the second IR-File to reduce the dsp load.
        </p>
        <p>
          The "Delay" control could add a small delay to the second model to overcome phasing issues, or to add some color/reverb to the sound.
        </p>
        <p>
          To round up the sound it allow to load up to two Impulse Response files and mix there output as well. You could try the wildest combinations, or, be conservative and load just your single preferred IR-File.
        </p>
        <p>
          Each neural model may have a different expected Sample Rate, Ratatouille will resample the buffer to match that. Impulse Response Files will be resampled on the fly to match the session Sample Rate.
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
