<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2024 Jobin Rezai -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.lvnauth.LVNAuth</id>
  
  <name>LVNAuth</name>
  <summary>Create and play visual novels</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>

  <developer id="tld.vendor">
    <name>Jobin Rezai</name>
  </developer>
  
  <description>
    <p>
      LVNAuth is a desktop application that lets you create and view visual novels.
      Manage your visual novel, from beginning to end, using LVNAuth&apos;s GUI editor. A command system: You can start or stop actions in your visual novel by using some simple commands. A built-in Wizard window will guide you with using commands so you don&apos;t have to memorize the commands. No programming experience required. LVNAuth is made for story writers. Chapters and Scenes: You can have multiple scenes within a chapter. Simple Animations: Ability to apply character and object animations, such as fade, movement, rotate, and scale.
    </p>
    <p>
      Support for backgrounds, characters, including the ability to change a character&apos;s image to show a different facial expression, and object images. Images in .png format are recommended.
    </p>
    <p>
      Support for Font Sprite Sheets and Font Kerning. There is also a built-in bitmap font tracing tool to convert variable width font sprite sheets to a fixed width.
    </p>
    <p>
      Compile your story into a single .lvna file, which can be opened using LVNAuth. Your viewers will need LVNAuth to view your visual novel.
    </p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.lvnauth.LVNAuth.desktop</launchable>

  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#b3afff</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#5c3f5b</color>
  </branding>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

  <url type="homepage">https://lvnauth.org/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://lvnauth.org/pages/donate.html</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/jrezai/lvnauth/</url>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://lvnauth.org/images/screenshots/lvnauth_story_1.png</image>
      <caption>A visual novel made with LVNAuth</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://lvnauth.org/images/screenshots/lvnauth_story_2.png</image>
      <caption>A visual novel made with LVNAuth</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://lvnauth.org/images/screenshots/lvnauth_wizard_1.png</image>
      <caption>The wizard window lists all the commands that LVNAuth can use in a visual novel.</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="0.5" date="2024-03-09">
    <url type="details">https://lvnauth.org/blog/lvnauth-0.5.html</url>
      <description>
        <p>Release description</p>
          <ul>
            <li>Added text support for sprites. You can now show text on character sprites, object sprites, and dialog sprites. The purpose of showing text on sprites is to make way for eventually being able to create buttons in a future version. Click on the 'Wizard' button and choose the Font category to see the new sprite text-related commands.</li>
            <li>The screen for a visual novel is now updated all at once on each frame instead of multiple rectangular areas. This should help improve performance and make it easier to maintain the code.</li>
            <li>Added Flatpak support.</li>
            <li>Fixed bug: when a non-animating scale or rotate was applied to a sprite and then a gradual fade was applied, it lost the scale/rotate values.</li>
            <li>Fixed bug with commands such as character_show not swapping out a sprite that is queued to become visible. In some cases, this caused two sprites with the same alias to appear on the screen.</li>
          </ul>
      </description>
     </release>
   </releases>
</component>