<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.squeakland.Etoys</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>Apache-2.0 OR MIT</project_license>
  <name>Etoys</name>
  <developer_name>Squeak Community</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.squeakland.Etoys.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <summary>Learn with visual programming</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تَعلَم بالبرمجة المرئية</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bn">ভিজ্যুয়াল প্রোগ্রামিংয়ের সাহায্যে শিখুন</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Programmieren lernen durch zeichnen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Aprende con programación visual</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Apprenez avec la programmation visuelle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">वीजुअल प्रोग्रामिंग सीखें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Belajar dengan programming visual</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Aprenda com programação virtual</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Invata cu programare vizuala</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="th">เรียนรู้กับการเขียนโปรแกรมภาพ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Học tập lập trình ảo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">学习可视化编程</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">學習視覺化程式設計</summary>
  <description>
    <p>This app is a great way for kids to learn how to program while learning other disciplines and having a lot of fun! Create interactive drawings, stories, models and games with a drag-and-drop interface that helps to prevent syntax errors that are often frustrating to new learners. This app encourages curiosity and exploration, and can be used to create anything from simple drawings to complex models of the physical world. While originally designed for students who are 8 - 13 years old, teachers have found that this app has helped students of all ages, from young learners to college-aged students alike!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="ar">
    <p>هذا التطبيق هو وسيلة رائعة للأطفال لتعلم كيفية البرمجة بينما يتعلمون العلوم الأخرى مع الحصول على الكثير من المرح! إنشاء رسومات تفاعلية، وقصص، ونماذج والألعاب مع واجهة السحب والإفلات التي تساعد على منع أخطاء في بناء الجملة التي غالباً ما تكون مُحبِطة للمُتعلِمين الجُدد. هذا التطبيق يشجع حب الإستطلاع والإستكشاف، ويمكن إستخدامه في إنشاء أي شيء من رسومات بسيطة لنماذج معقدة من العالم المادي. في حين صممت أصلاً للطلاب الذين تترواح أعمارهم بين 8-13 سنة، وقد وجد المُعلمين أن هذا التطبيق قد ساعد الطلاب من جميع الأعمار، من المتعلمين الصغار للطلاب  في سن الكلية على حد سواء!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="bn">
    <p>অন্যান্য বিভাগ শেখার সাথে সাথে মজা করার মাধ্যমে প্রোগ্রামিং শিখতে বাচ্চাদের জন্য এই এ্যাপটি দারুণ! একটি টেনে-নিয়ে-ফেলে দেয়ার মতো ইন্টারফেসের সাহায্যে তৈরি করুন মিথষ্ক্রিয়ামূলক অঙ্কন, গল্প, মডেল এবং খেলা যেখানে সিনট্যাক্স ভুলগুলো হওয়া প্রতিরোধ করা হয় যা কিনা নতুন শিক্ষানবিশদের জন্য প্রায়ই বিরক্তিকর। এই এ্যাপ কৌতুহল ও অনুসন্ধানকে উৎসাহ দেয় এবং এটা ব্যবহার করে সহজ অঙ্কন থেকে জটিল মডেলও তৈরি করা যায়। মূলতঃ 8 - 13 বছর বয়সী ছাত্রদের জন্য তৈরি করা হলেও, শিক্ষকরা আবিষ্কার করেছেন যে এই এ্যাপটি কিশোর শিক্ষানবিশ থেকে বয়স্ক পর্যন্ত সকল বয়সের ছাত্রদের জন্যই যথাযথ!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="es">
    <p>Con este programa, niños podrán aprender a programar mientras que aprenden otras disciplinas - ¡y se divertirán mucho haciéndolo! Podrán crear dibujos interactivos, cuentos, modelos y juegos con solo arrastrar y soltar las cosas que quieran. Esto previene errores de sintaxis que pueden ser frustrantes para los nuevos estudiantes de programación. Este programa estimula la curiosidad y la exploración, y se puede utilizar para crear casi cualquier cosa, desde dibujos simples a modelos complejos del mundo físico. Aunque originalmente fue diseñado para estudiantes entre 8 y 13 años de edad, maestros han encontrado que este programa ha ayudado a estudiantes de todas edades, ¡desde niños chicos hasta estudiantes en la universidad!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="fr">
    <p>Cette app est pour les enfants une façon géniale d'apprendre à programmer en apprenant d'autres disciplines et en s'amusant ! Créez des dessins interactifs, des histoires, des modèles et des jeux avec une interface glisser-déposer qui aide à empêcher les erreurs de syntaxe, souvent frustrantes pour de nouveaux apprenants. Cette app encourage la curiosité et l'exploration, et peut être utilisée pour tout créer, depuis des dessins simples jusqu'à des modèles complexes du monde physique. Alors qu'elle était à l'origine destinée à des élèves de 8-13 ans, les enseignants ont trouvé que cette app avait aidé des élèves de tous les âges, depuis les plus jeunes apprenants jusqu'aux étudiants !</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="hi">
    <p>यह ऐप बच्चों के लिए अन्य विषयों को सीखने के साथ-साथ प्रोग्रामिंग सीखने और भरपूर मनोरंजन का एक बेहतर माध्यम है! संवादात्मक चित्रों, कहानियों, मॉडल्स और गेम्स का निर्माण ड्रैग-एंड-ड्रॉप्स इंटरफेस के साथ करें जिससे सिंटेक्स एरर को रोकने में मदद मिलती है जो नए प्रशिक्षुओं को परेशान करते हैं। यह ऐप जिज्ञासा और अन्वेषण को बढ़ावा देता है, और इसका इस्तेमाल भौतिक जगत की किसी भी चीजों, साधारण ड्रॉइंग से लेकर जटिल मॉडल्स तक का निर्माण करने के लिए किया जा सकता है। हालांकि इसे 8 – 13 वर्ष के बच्चों के लिए बनाया गया है, लेकिन शिक्षकों के अनुसार यह ऐप सभी आयु, छोटे प्रशिक्षु से लेकर कॉलेज उम्र के छात्रों के बच्चों के लिए उपयोगी है! </p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="id">
    <p>Aplikasi ini adalah cara yang bagus bagi anak-anak untuk belajar cara memprogram sembari mempelajari mata pelajaran yang lain dan bergembira! Ciptakan gambar, cerita, model, dan permainan interaktif dengan antarmuka seret-dan-letakkan yang membantu mencegah kesalahan syntax yang seringkali menjengkelkan programer pemula. Aplikasi ini mendorong rasa ingin tahu dan kebiasaan eksplorasi, dan dapat digunakan untuk membuat segala sesuatu dari gambar sederhana hingga model dunia nyata yang rumit. Meskipun pada awalnya dirancang untuk siswa yang berumur 8 - 13 tahun, para guru telah mendapati bahwa aplikasi ini telah membantu siswa dari segala umur, dari siswa muda hingga pelajar di perguruan tinggi!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="pt_BR">
    <p>Este aplicativo é uma ótima maneira para que as crianças aprendam de uma maneira muito divertida como programar enquanto aprendem outras disciplinas. Criar desenhos interativos, estórias, modelos e jogos com uma interface simples onde você só precisa arrastar e soltar as coisas, e que ainda ajuda a prevenir erros de sintaxe que são muitas vezes frustrante para quem está aprendendo. Este aplicativo encoraja a curiosidade, e pode ser utilizado para criar de desenhos simples à modelos de um mundo físico. Mesmo tendo sido criado para estudantes de 8 - 13 anos de idade, professores descobriram que esse aplicativo tem ajudado estudantes de todas as idades, de jovens à estudantes universitários. </p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="ro">
    <p>Aceasta aplicatie este o modalitate foarte bună pentru copii să învețe cum să programeze  în timp ce intata alte discipline și aibe parte de  distracție! Creați desene interactive, povestiri, modele și jocuri cu o interfață de tip trage si lipeste, care ajută la prevenirea erorilor de sintaxă, care sunt de multe ori frustrante pentru noi cursanți. Această aplicație încurajează curiozitatea și explorare, și pot fi folosite pentru a crea  de la desene simple la modele complexe ale lumii fizice. În timp ce inițial a fost conceput pentru studenții de 8 - 13 ani, profesorii au constatat că această aplicație a ajutat elevii de toate vârstele!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="th">
    <p>แอพนี้เป็นวิธีที่ดีสำหรับเด็กที่จะเรียนรู้วิธีการเขียนโปรแกรมในขณะที่การเรียนรู้สาขาวิชาอื่น ๆ และมีอะไรสนุกมากมาย! สร้างภาพวาดแบบโต้ตอบ เรื่องราว แบบจำลองและเกมกับอินเตอร์เฟซการลากและวางที่ช่วยในการป้องกันข้อผิดพลาดทางไวยากรณ์ที่มักเป็นปัญหาของผู้เรียนใหม่ แอพนี้จะช่วยกระตุ้นความอยากรู้และการสำรวจและสามารถนำมาใช้ในการสร้างอะไรจากภาพวาดที่เรียบง่ายรูปแบบที่ซับซ้อนของโลกทางกายภาพ ขณะที่ออกแบบมาสำหรับนักเรียนที่มีอายุ 8 - 13 ปี ครูได้พบว่า แอพนี้ได้ช่วยให้นักเรียนทุกเพศทุกวัยตั้งแต่ผู้เริ่มเรียนจนถึงนักเรียนระดับวิทยาลัย!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="vi">
    <p>Ứng dụng này mang đến một cách thức tuyệt để trẻ em học cách lập trình trong khi vẫn học các môn khác và tận hưởng niềm vui! Tạo ra các bản vẽ tương tác, những câu chuyện, các mô hình và các trò chơi với giao diện kéo và thả giúp ngăn ngừa các lỗi cú pháp gây bực bội cho người mới học. Ứng dụng này khuyến khích sự tò mò và khám phá và có thể được sử dụng để tạo ra bất cứ điều gì, từ bản vẽ đơn giản đến mô hình phức tạp của thế giới vật chất. Tuy thiết kế ban đầu chỉ dành cho học sinh từ 8 - 13 tuổi, ngay cả nhiều giáo viên cũng đã khám phá ra rằng ứng dụng này hữu ích cho sinh viên ở mọi độ tuổi, từ trẻ nhỏ cho đến sinh viên đại học!</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="zh_CN">
    <p>这个app可以让小孩在学习其他学科和享受乐趣的同时学习如何编程！用拖放界面创建交互式绘图、故事、模型和游戏，让孩子避免犯新手常犯的语法错误，这个app提倡好奇心与探索精神，可以创建任何东西，不管是简单的绘图，还是复杂的物理世界模型。虽然最初设计对象是8—13岁的学生，但是教师也可以用这个app来帮助各个年龄段的学生，不管是年轻学生还是大龄学生！</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="zh_TW">
    <p>這款應用程式非常適合孩子們在學習其他學科之餘，學習如何快樂地進行程式設計！使用拖放式介面建立互動式繪圖、故事、模型和遊戲，這種拖放式介面有助於避免做出新學習者經常感到困擾的語法錯誤。這款應用程式鼓勵人們探索和擁有好奇心，並且可以用來建立任何東西，從簡單的繪畫到物理世界的複雜模型皆可。這款遊戲最初是專為 8 至 13 歲的學生所設計，但教師發現這款遊戲幫助了所有年齡層的學生，從年輕學生到大學年齡的學生都有！</p>
  </description>
  <releases>
    <release version="5.0.2408" date="2012-07-01">
      <ul>
        <li>Updated translation: da, de, bn, hy, hus, zh_CN</li>
        <li>Added translation: en_GB</li>
        <li>Move ScratchClient to 'Tools' category</li>
        <li>Revert addition of graph-location watcher items to Morph's extras menu. The viewer is a better way to get watchers.</li>
      </ul>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/C/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot1.jpg</image>
      <image type="source" xml:lang="es">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/es/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot1.jpg</image>
      <image type="source" xml:lang="pt">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/pt/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot1.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/C/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot2.jpg</image>
      <image type="source" xml:lang="es">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/es/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot2.jpg</image>
      <image type="source" xml:lang="pt">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/pt/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot2.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/C/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot3.jpg</image>
      <image type="source" xml:lang="es">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/es/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot3.jpg</image>
      <image type="source" xml:lang="pt">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.squeakland.Etoys/pt/org.squeakland.etoys-screenshot3.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <metadata>
    <value key="GnomeSoftware::popular-background">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/thumbnails/org.squeakland.Etoys/org.squeakland.etoys-thumb.jpg</value>
  </metadata>
  <url type="homepage">http://www.squeakland.org/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.paypal.com/donate/?token=3RnmjSwRZGIXEr5CKwfMwCq-cvnWds0wyY_q5_0p5d8v051TtiKje6zf_jfowUVmIeH8dW</url>
  <url type="help">http://www.squeakland.org/tutorials/</url>
</component>
