<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>org.gtaf.quran</id>

    <name>Al Quran (Tafsir &amp; By Word)</name>
    <summary>Study the Quran through Word by Word Analysis, Colored Tajweed, Tafsir &amp; Audio
    </summary>
    <url type="homepage">https://gtaf.org/apps/quran/</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://gtaf.canny.io/quran/</url>
    <url type="donation">https://gtaf.org/donate/</url>

    <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
    <project_license>LicenseRef-Proprietary</project_license>
    <developer_name>Greentech Apps Foundation</developer_name>

    <supports>
        <control>pointing</control>
        <control>keyboard</control>
        <control>touch</control>
    </supports>

    <description>
        <p>Start your journey to a deeper understanding of the Quran!</p>
        <p>Alhamdulillah! Introducing Al Quran (Tafsir &amp; by Word), the ultimate Quran study tool
            for all. With features such as a robust audio system with repeat functions to aid in
            Quran hifz, word-by-word analysis and translations, Tafsir Ibn Kathir, colour-coded
            tajweed, Quran topics list, bookmark and note-taking with sync, a powerful search, and
            multiple translations and tafsirs in various languages, this app is packed with
            everything you need to deepen your understanding of the Quran. Download now and start
            your journey to a deeper understanding of the Quran with the Al Quran (Tafsir &amp; by
            Word).
        </p>
        <p>You can Enjoy:</p>
        <p>Several Translations &amp; Tafsirs, Word by Word Analysis &amp; Translations, Bookmarks,
            Search &amp; Quran Index, Quran Audio, Various Customization Options &amp; Others,
            Localization
        </p>

        <ul>
            <li>Understand the Quran by studying 90+ Translations &amp; Tafsirs of the Quran in 60+
                languages: Bangla, Chinese, English, French, Hindi, German, Indonesian, Italian,
                Malay, Russian, Spanish, Urdu and many more!
            </li>
            <li>Study Tafsir Ibn Kathir in multiple languages</li>
            <li>8 Arabic Tafsirs (including Tafseer Ibn Kathir, Tafseer Tabari, etc.) along with
                Arabic E3rab, Word Meaning, Asabun Nuzool
            </li>
            <li>Study different Translations &amp; Tafsirs simultaneously</li>
            <li>Read Word by Word translations of the Quran in Bangla, English, German, Hindi,
                Indonesian, Ingush, Malay, Russian, Tamil, Turkish and Urdu
            </li>
            <li>Study and Analyse Word by Word Root / Lemma Information, Grammar Details and Verb
            </li>
            <li>Forms to dive in more depth. Helpful to learn &amp; understand Arabic</li>
            <li>Check the occurrences of the word, root and lemma in different forms</li>

            <li>Bookmark ayahs to your own Collections and keep track of the last read ayah using
                Pins
            </li>
            <li>Start reading from where you left off using automatic Last Reads</li>

            <li>Powerful Search with Highlights</li>
            <li>Surah Search along with advanced search tips to quickly find what you are looking
                for
            </li>
            <li>Explore by Topics &amp; read all ayahs related to a topic together</li>

            <li>Listen to several recitations by 30+ reciters (downloadable for offline use)</li>
            <li>Reciter Options: Sheikh Mishary Al Afasy, Sheikh Husary (Muallim), Shaykh Ayman
                Suwaid, Sheikh Abdur Rahman As-Sudais and many others
            </li>
            <li>Robust Audio System with repeat, group playback of verses function to aid in Quran
                Memorization Quran Hifz
            </li>
            <li>Reciters tagged based on recitation types: Murattal, Mujawwad, WBW, Translation</li>
            <li>English Quran Audio Translation and Arabic Audio Commentary</li>
            <li>Word by Word Audio Playback</li>

            <li>Read in Uthmanic / Indopak script</li>
            <li>Read Tafsirs in Tafsir view</li>
            <li>Quran Dictionary</li>
            <li>Various fonts and multiple themes, including Night mode</li>
            <li>Autoscroll feature</li>
            <li>Copy &amp; Share the verses</li>
            <li>Quran App User Interface localized in 20+ Languages: Arabic, English, Bangla,
                German, French, Bahasa Indonesia / Malay, Russian, Spanish, Tagalog, Turkish, Urdu,
                and more
            </li>
            <li>All feature supports offline (Quran offline)</li>
            <li>And the next features that are in development</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Download now and start your journey to a deeper understanding of the Quran! Share and
            recommend this beautiful Quran app to your friends and family. May Allah bless
            us in this world and hereafter.
        </p>

        <p>
            "Whoever calls people to right guidance will have a reward like that of those
            who follow
            him..." - Sahih Muslim, Hadith 2674

        </p>
        <p>Developed by
            Greentech Apps Foundation
        </p>
        <p>Website: https://gtaf.org</p>
        <p>Follow us on Social Media: http://facebook.com/greentech0,
            https://twitter.com/greentechapps
        </p>
    </description>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">org.gtaf.quran.desktop</launchable>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Simple UI with useful feature</caption>
            <image>
                https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.14414.14497699918764450.bc9d91c0-96d6-4fd9-85e9-53359041c447.a5526af2-1db6-4eef-9fc0-bd320756fe48
            </image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Search in translation and tafsir</caption>
            <image>
                https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.15824.14497699918764450.bc9d91c0-96d6-4fd9-85e9-53359041c447.5edbc40d-30d6-4c71-b21a-fb85ccd22b75
            </image>
        </screenshot>
        <screenshot>
            <caption>Translation, Word by Word, Tafsir &amp; more</caption>
            <image>
                https://store-images.s-microsoft.com/image/apps.36988.14497699918764450.bc9d91c0-96d6-4fd9-85e9-53359041c447.fccc9f1c-f0db-46da-9d68-2b9320d7f6f2
            </image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
    <releases>
        <release date="2023-12-30" version="0.5.7" />
        <description>
            <p>Initial Release</p>
        </description>
    </releases>
</component>