<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2022 Endless OS Foundation LLC -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.apache.directory.studio</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.apache.directory.studio.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>
  <name>Apache Directory Studio</name>
  <summary>A complete directory tooling platform</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Apache Directory Studio is a complete directory tooling platform intended to be used with any LDAP server however it is particularly designed for use with ApacheDS. It is an Eclipse RCP application, composed of several Eclipse (OSGi) plugins, that can be easily upgraded with additional ones.</p>
    <p>The LDAP Browser has been designed to work with almost any LDAP server available. It not only permits to read and display the tree of your LDAP Server but also allows you to modify it by creating, editing or removing entries.</p>
    <p>The LDIF Editor is a tool for editing LDIF files. It provides syntax highlighting and content assistance.</p>
    <p>The Schema Editor has been designed to edit the schema files in the OpenLDAP format. It allows you to edit easily attribute types and object classes for Apache Directory Server and OpenLDAP.</p>
    <p>Apache Directory Studio bundles the latest version of the LDAPV3 certified ApacheDS. Creating and launching a new LDAP server now takes less than 10 seconds!</p>
    <p>The ApacheDS Configuration Editor can be used to edit the server configuration ('server.xml' and 'config.ldif' files) of an Apache Directory Server installation.</p>
    <p>The ACI Editor allows you to define, for an entry or a set of entries, graphically or manually (in souce code mode), an ACI (Access Control Information) item specification for Apache Directory Server.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>LDAP Browser</caption>
      <image type="source" width="1062" height="818">https://directory.apache.org/studio/screenshots.data/LDAP_Browser_Plugin.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <developer_name>Apache Software Foundation</developer_name>
  <update_contact>wjt@endlessos.org</update_contact>
  <releases>
    <!-- https://directory.apache.org/studio/news.html -->
    <release version="2.0.0.v20210717-M17" date="2021-07-24">
      <p>The Apache Directory Team is pleased to announce the release of Apache Directory Studio 2.0.0-M17, the next milestone release of the version 2.0 of its Eclipse based LDAP Browser and Directory client.</p>
      <url>https://directory.apache.org/studio/changelog.html#apache-directory-studio-version-200-m17-july-24th-2021</url>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <url type="homepage">https://directory.apache.org/studio/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">http://issues.apache.org/jira/browse/DIRSTUDIO</url>
  <url type="faq">https://directory.apache.org/studio/faqs.html</url>
  <url type="help">https://directory.apache.org/studio/users-guide.html</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.apache.org/foundation/contributing.html</url>
  <url type="translate">https://directory.apache.org/contribute.html</url>
  <url type="contact">https://directory.apache.org/mailing-lists-and-irc.html</url>
  <!-- Translations are neither gettext nor qt so can't be extracted automatically. -->
  <languages>
    <lang percentage="95">fr</lang>
    <lang percentage="95">de</lang>
  </languages>
</component>
