<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>org.kde.kdiamond</id>
    <name>KDiamond</name>
    <name xml:lang="ar">كيدايموند</name>
    <name xml:lang="bn">কেডায়মন্ড</name>
    <name xml:lang="es">Diamantes</name>
    <name xml:lang="hi">केडायमंड</name>
    <name xml:lang="pt_BR">KDiamante</name>
    <summary>Create lines of three diamonds</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ar">أنشئ اسطر من ثلاث ماسات</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="bn">তিনটি ডায়মন্ডের সারি তৈরি করুন</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="es">Crea líneas de tres diamantes</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="fr">Créez des lignes de trois diamants</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="hi">तीन डायमंड्स की लाइनें तैयार करें</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="id">Buat garis dari tiga intan</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Crie linhas de três diamantes</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ro">Creeaza linii cu trei diamante</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="th">สร้างเส้นของเพชรสามเม็ด</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="vi">Xếp ba viên kim cương thành đường thẳng</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">将三颗以上同样的宝石连成一条线</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">建立三顆鑽石連線</summary>
    <description><p>In this fast-paced game, your job is to build lines of three diamonds of the same type. Simply swap diamonds with their neighbors to make your lines. Better do it quickly, so you can build as many lines as possible before the round is over! This is an easy and highly entertaining game you can play for just a little while, or for hours on end. It’s fun, fast, and great for many age levels.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ar"><p>في هذه اللعبة سريعة الوتيرة، تكمن مهمتك في تشكيل أسطر من ثلاث ماسات من نفس النوع. ببساطة قم بمبادلة الماس مع الأسطر المجاورة لتشكيل خطوطك. وأفضل شيء أن تقوم بذلك بسرعة وذلك حتى تتمكن من بناء العديد من لأسطر قبل انتهاء الجولة! هذه لعبة سهلة ومسلية للغاية و يمكن أن تلعبها لوقت قصير، أو لساعات طويلة. إنها ممتعة وسريعة ورائعة لكثير من المستويات العمرية.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="bn"><p>এই দ্রুতগতির খেলাটিতে আপনার কাজ হবে তিনটি একই ধরনের ডায়মন্ডের সারি তৈরি করা। সারি তৈরির জন্য ডায়মন্ডগুলোকে পাশেরটির সাথে বদলান। যত দ্রুত এ কাজটি সফলভাবে করতে পারবেন তত বেশি সারি আপনার পালা ফুরোবার আগেই করতে পারবেন। এটি খুবই সোজা এবং বেশ মজার। অল্প সময়েও যেমন খেলতে পারবেন তেমনি ব্যস্ত থাকতে পারবেন ঘন্টার পর ঘন্টা। সকল বয়সীদের জন্যই এটি মজাদার আর দ্রুতগতির চমৎকার একটি গেম।</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="es"><p>¡Este juego es verdaderamente de ritmo rápido! Debes crear líneas de tres diamantes de la misma clase en cuestión de segundos. Sólamente puedes cambiar los diamantes con sus vecinos para formar tus líneas, ¡y tendrás que formar tantas líneas como puedas antes de que se te acabe el tiempo! Este es un juego fácil y muy entretenido que podrás jugar sólo por un poco de tiempo, o por horas en extremo. ¡Es divertido, rápido y genial para personas de todas edades!</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="fr"><p>Dans ce jeu rythmé, votre job est de construire des lignes de trois diamants du même type. Inversez simplement les diamants avec leurs voisins pour créer vos lignes. Mieux vaut le faire rapidement, afin que vous puissiez construire autant de lignes que possible avant que le tour ne soit fini ! C’est un jeu facile et très distrayant auquel vous pouvez jouer pour juste quelques instants, ou pour des heures entières au final. C’est amusant, rapide, et parfait pour de nombreuses tranches d’âge.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="hi"><p>इस तेज चाल वाले गेम में, आपको एक ही प्रकार के तीन डायमंड्स की लाइनें बनानी है। बस अगल-बगल के डायमंड्स को आपस में स्वैप करते हुए अपनी लाइनें बनाएं। इसे तेजी के करें, ताकि राउंड खत्म होने से पहले आप अधिक से अधिक लाइनें बना सकें! यह एक आसान और मनोरंजन से भरपूर गेम है जिसे आप थोड़े समय के भी खेल सकते हैं, या अंत तक पहुंचने के लिए घंटों खेल सकते हैं। यह मनोरंजक, तेज, और सभी उम्र के लोगों के लिए शानदार गेम है।</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="id"><p>Dalam permainan serba cepat ini, tugas Anda adalah untuk membuat garis tiga berlian dari jenis yang sama. Tukarkan berlian dengan sebelah mereka untuk membuat garis. Lebih baik Anda melakukannya dengan cepat, sehingga Anda dapat membuat garis sebanyak mungkin sebelum ronde berakhir! Ini adalah permainan yang mudah dan sangat menghibur yang dapat Anda mainkan sebentar, atau selama berjam-jam. Permainan ini menyenangkan, cepat, dan bagus untuk berbagai tingkatan usia.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR"><p>Neste jogo rápido, seu trabalho é construir linhas de três diamantes iguais. Basta trocar diamantes com seus vizinhos para fazer suas linhas. Faça isso com rapidez para construir o máximo de linhas possível antes do final da rodada! Este é um jogo fácil que você pode jogar por pouco tempo, ou por horas seguidas. É divertido, rápido e ótimo para todas as idades.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ro"><p>În acest joc , munca ta este de a construi linii de trei diamante de același tip. Pur și simplu fa schimb de diamante cu vecinii lor pentru a face liniile. Mai bine fă-o repede, astfel încât să poți construi cât mai multe linii, inainte ca runda sa se termine! Acesta este un joc ușor și foarte distractiv puteți juca doar pentru puțin timp, sau ore în șir. Este distractiv, rapid, și  pentru mai multe nivele de vârstă.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="th"><p>ในเกมที่รวดเร็วนี้ งานของคุณคือการสร้างแถวของเพชรสามเม็ดในประเภทเดียวกัน เพียงแค่สลับเพชรกับข้าง ๆ ของพวกมันที่จะทำแถวของคุณ จะดีกว่าถ้าจะทำมันได้อย่างรวดเร็วเพื่อให้คุณสามารถสร้างเส้นแถวมากที่สุดเท่าที่เป็นไปได้ก่อนที่จะหมดรอบ! นี่เป็นเกมที่ง่ายและสนุกมาก คุณสามารถเล่นได้เพียงเล็กน้อย หรือเป็นชั่วโมง มันสนุก รวดเร็วและดีสำหรับทุกระดับวัย</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="vi"><p>Trong trò chơi có nhịp độ nhanh này, việc của bạn là xếp ba viên kim cương cùng loại thành một hàng. Đơn giản là chỉ cần tráo vị trí các viên kim cương với nhau để tạo thành một hàng. Bạn nên thực hiện thật nhanh, để tạo càng nhiều hàng càng tốt trước khi hết màn chơi! Đây là một trò chơi dễ và mang tính giải trí cao,  bạn có thể chơi trong ít phút hoặc bỏ ra hàng giờ. Trò chơi này rất thú vị, đòi hỏi tốc độ nhanh và tuyệt vời dành cho nhiều độ tuổi.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_CN"><p>在这个快节奏游戏中，您的任务就是通过变换相邻两颗宝石的位置，将三颗同样的宝石连成一条线。只有速度足够快，您才能在一轮游戏结束前完成尽量多的连线。这个游戏简单但是非常有趣，适合各年龄的玩家。您既可以把它当作消遣玩意一小会，也可以把它当作挑战玩到最后。</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_TW"><p>在這個快節奏的遊戲中，你要做的事情就是將相同類型的三顆鑽石組成一條線。只要將相鄰的兩顆鑽石交換來形成一條線就好了。最好動作快一點，這樣就可以在關卡結束前盡可能地建立多一點的線！這是一款非常簡單且極度有趣的遊戲，你可以玩一下，或玩好幾個小時。它非常有趣、快速，適合所有年齡層的玩家。</p></description>
    <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/</url>
    <screenshots>
      <screenshot type="default">
        <image type="source" xml:lang="es">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Kdiamond/es/org.kde.kdiamond-screenshot1.jpg</image>
        <image type="source" xml:lang="pt">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Kdiamond/pt/org.kde.kdiamond-screenshot1.jpg</image>
        <image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Kdiamond/C/org.kde.kdiamond-screenshot1.jpg</image>
      </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
		<release version="18.08.0" date="2018-08-16"/>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  </component>