<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
	<id>org.featherwallet.Feather</id>
	<metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
	<project_license>BSD-3-Clause</project_license>
	<name>Feather</name>
	<summary>Monero desktop wallet</summary>

	<description>
		<ul>
			<li>
				Easy-to-use, small and fast - Feather
				runs well on any modern hardware, including virtual machines
				and live operating systems.
			</li>
			<li>
				Beginner friendly, but also caters to advanced Monero
				users by providing a feature set that is on par with the official CLI.
			</li>
			<li>
				Ships with sane defaults that suit most users, but
				can also be configured for high or uncommon threat models.
			</li>
			<li>
				Serves as a testing grounds for experimental features
				that may later be adopted in the reference wallets.
			</li>
		</ul>
	</description>

	<launchable type="desktop-id">org.featherwallet.Feather.desktop</launchable>

	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Home: Fiat price display, CCS proposals and /r/Monero posts</caption>
			<image>https://featherwallet.org/img/home_monero_light.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>History view: Export as CSV, Rebroadcast failed transactions and Create transaction proofs</caption>
			<image>https://featherwallet.org/img/history_txinfo_light.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>Nodes screen: Overview of nodes, switch and maintain your own list</caption>
			<image>https://featherwallet.org/img/feather_node_switch.png</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>

	<url type="homepage">https://featherwallet.org/</url>
	<url type="help">https://docs.featherwallet.org</url>
	<url type="contact">https://docs.featherwallet.org/guides/report-an-issue</url>
	<url type="donation">https://docs.featherwallet.org/guides/donate</url>
	<url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/feather-wallet/feather</url>

	<releases>
		<release version="2.4.4" date="2023-03-23">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>RISC-V builds are now available</li>
					<li>Fixed an issue that caused importing keyimages to take longer than necessary</li>
					<li>It is now possible to select any file when importing keyimages or outputs</li>
					<li>Settings: the proxy host should no longer reset back to localhost when the settings dialog is reopened</li>
					<li>Build system improvements</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="2.4.3" date="2023-03-15">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>AppImages for Tails / Whonix / Prestium no longer bundle a Tor binary, shaving ~3 MB off the binary size</li>
					<li>the built-in updater should now work on macOS</li>
					<li>macOS builds are once again shipped as application bundles, instead of .DMG files (due to superior UX and smaller download size)</li>
					<li>Receive: added a column that shows the subaddress index</li>
					<li>opening more than 3 wallets will no longer cause the application to freeze</li>
					<li>new wallets should now always start syncing from the current blockheight</li>
					<li>typing composed characters (e.g. ‘e -> é) now works</li>
					<li>nodes: the IP range 100.64/10 is now considered local</li>
					<li>DebugInfo: added Proxy information</li>
					<li>stack trace: added version and OS info to log output</li>
					<li>Fixed a few issues that could cause application crashes</li>
					<li>Fixed a build issue on Qt 5</li>
					<li>Update unbound to 1.15.0</li>
					<li>Update polyseed to 2.0.0</li>
					<li>Update OpenSSL to 3.0.8</li>
					<li>minimum glibc version is now 2.27 (this drops support for Ubuntu 16.04)</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="2.1.0" date="2022-08-12">
			<description>
				<ul>
					<li>Sweeping or sending all spendable balance to an integrated address should no longer throw an error</li>
					<li>Fixed an issue that could cause the built-in updater to fail to install Feather (Windows installer)</li>
					<li>Importing a transaction should no longer hang the UI</li>
					<li>Updated Monero to v0.18.1.0</li>
				</ul>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>
</component>
