<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright 2020 Flathub maintainers -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.srb2.SRB2</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Sonic Robo Blast 2</name>
  <summary>A 3D Sonic the Hedgehog fangame based on a modified version of Doom Legacy</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Sonic Robo Blast 2 is a free 3D Sonic the Hedgehog fan-game built using
      a modified version of the Doom Legacy source port of Doom. SRB2 is
      closely inspired by the original Sonic games from the Sega Genesis, and
      attempts to recreate their design in 3D.
    </p>
    <p>
      SRB2’s features include, but are not limited to:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Beautiful 3D Enviroment, with free movement in all directions.</li>
      <li>Old-school platforming, complete with rings, springs, hazards, reversible gravity and other obstacles.</li>
      <li>Three playable characters: Sonic, Tails, Knuckles – each with their own unique abilities.</li>
      <li>Over 20 levels to play, featuring a variety of locations, from green meadows, to deep underwater ruins, mines, mountains and space stations…</li>
      <li>Fast-paced multiplayer fun with 2 player splitscreen or up to 32 players online in nine different game modes.</li>
      <li>Configurable graphics and control options – play with a modern WSAD + Mouse FPS control setup, a relaxed gamepad setup, or anything in between!</li>
      <li>Original Soundtrack produced by some of the best Sonic music artists on the Internet.</li>
      <li>Customization: SRB2 includes the ability to create your own levels, characters, game modes, and with knowledge of programming, even a whole new game.</li>
      <li>…and so much more!</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.srb2.SRB2.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.srb2.org/wp-content/uploads/srb2-title.png</image>
      <caption>Title screen</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.srb2.org/wp-content/uploads/21-gfz2.png</image>
      <caption>Singleplayer (Sonic)</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.srb2.org/wp-content/uploads/21-dsz2.png</image>
      <caption>Singleplayer (Tails)</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.srb2.org/wp-content/uploads/21-thz2.png</image>
      <caption>Singleplayer (Knuckles)</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.srb2.org/media_data/coop1.png</image>
      <caption>Multiplayer</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.srb2.org</url>
  <provides>
    <binary>srb2</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.2.3" date="2020-05-10" />
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
