<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.freedesktop.LinuxAudio.Plugins.Guitarix</id>
  <extends>org.freedesktop.LinuxAudio.BaseExtension</extends>
  <name>Guitarix LV2</name>
  <summary>Guitarix LV2 plugins</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Guitarix is a virtual guitar amplifier for Linux running on Jack
      Audio Connection Kit.
    </p>
    <p>
      Guitarix takes the signal from your guitar as any real amp would
      do: as a mono-signal from your sound card. The input is processed
      by a main amp and a rack-section. Both can be routed separately
      and deliver a processed stereo-signal via Jack. You may fill the
      rack with effects from more than 25 built-in modules including
      stuff from a simple noise gate to brain-slashing modulation f/x
      like flanger, phaser or auto-wah.
    </p>
    <p>
      Your signal is processed with minimum latency. On any properly
      set-up Linux-system you don't have to wait more than 10ms until
      your sound is processed by guitarix.
    </p>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <url type="homepage">http://guitarix.org/</url>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <update_contact>hub_AT_figuiere.net</update_contact>
  <releases>
   <release version="0.42.0" date="2020-12-20">
     <description>
       <p>For this release Damien Zammit from ZamAudio has reworked
       our tube emulation.  This improved beside the overall sound,
       the dynamic responses of the different tube simulations.  Be
       aware please, that this may break your existing presets, but,
       we believe that the improvement in sound is it worse to force
       you to readjust your presets to match the new tube sims.</p>
       <p>Further news are:</p>
       <ul>
         <li>Reworked French translation by Olivier Humbert</li>
         <li>Add DC-Blocker on the Input</li>
         <li>Add Output Limiter</li>
         <li>Add Volume controls for the Power Amp plugin</li>
         <li>Fix version checks for needed packages</li>
         <li>Fix several small Bugs and hopefully don't introduce to
         much new ones</li>
       </ul>
     </description>
   </release>
    <release version="0.41.0" date="2020-07-17">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add Slovak translation by Jozef Riha</li>
          <li>Fix issue #104 lv2 plugins contains executable stack, patch by Alexander Tsoy</li>
          <li>Fix issue #105 Compile error on 0.40.0</li>
          <li>Fix issue #109 cannot initialize a variable of type 'char ' with an rvalue of type 'void '</li>
          <li>Fix issue #110 error: unknown type name 'va_list'</li>
          <li>Add NSM support</li>
          <li>Add midi out for tuner</li>
          <li>Add low/high cut filter before tuner</li>
          <li>GxTuner set to use same precision then the tuner in guitarix</li>
          <li>Use tab-box for LV2 plugs with to much controls</li>
          <li>Disable GxVibe, because it is broken</li>
          <li>Fix several Bug's and hopefully don't introduce to much new one's</li>
        </ul>
     </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.40.0" date="2020-05-27">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Port GUI and underlying libs (gxw/gxwmm) to GTK3 (gtkmm3)</li>
          <li>Port LV2 plugin GUIs to X11/cairo</li>
          <li>Add Midi feedback support</li>
          <li>Add new PowerAmp module</li>
          <li>Fix several Bug's and hopefully don't introduce to much new ones</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.39.0" date="2020-01-14" />
  </releases>
</component>
