<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.delugetorrent.Deluge</id>
  <name>Deluge</name>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <translation type="gettext">deluge</translation>
  <developer_name>Deluge Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Deluge arbetsgruppen</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Команда Deluge</developer_name>
  <summary>Deluge is a lightweight, Free Software, cross-platform BitTorrent client.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Deluge är en lätt, fri, plattformsoberoende BitTorrent-klient.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Deluge - легкий, вільний, крос-платформенний BitTorrent клієнт.</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.deluge-torrent.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://dev.deluge-torrent.org</url>
  <description>
    <p>Deluge contains the common features to BitTorrent clients such as Protocol Encryption, DHT, Local Peer Discovery (LSD), Peer Exchange (PEX), UPnP, NAT-PMP, Proxy support, Web seeds, global and per-torrent speed limits. As Deluge heavily utilises the libtorrent library it has a comprehensive list of the features provided.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Deluge innehåller de vanliga funktionerna för BitTorrent-klienter som protokollkryptering, DHT, Local Peer Discovery (LSD), Peer Exchange (PEX), UPnP, NAT-PMP, Proxy-stöd, webbdelning, globala och per torrent hastighetsgränser. Eftersom Deluge utnyttjar biblioteket libtorrent har den en omfattande lista över funktionerna.</p>
    <p>Deluge has been designed to run as both a normal standalone desktop application and as a client-server. In Thinclient mode a Deluge daemon handles all the BitTorrent activity and is able to run on headless machines with the user-interfaces connecting remotely from any other platform.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Deluge har utformats för att köras som både en vanlig fristående stationär applikation och som en klient-server. I tunt klientläge hanterar en Deluge-demon alla BitTorrent-aktiviteter som kan köras på huvudlösa maskiner med användargränssnitt som fjärransluts från någon annan plattform.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/Deluge-torrent.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
        <release version="2.0.3" date="2019-06-12">
            <description>
                <ul>
                  <li>Gtk UI</li>
                  <li>  - Fix errors running on Wayland (#3265).</li>
                  <li>  - Fix Peers Tab tooltip and context menu errors (#3266).</li>
                  <li>Web UI</li>
                  <li>  - Fix TypeError in Peers Tab setting country flag.</li>
                  <li>  - Fix reverse proxy header TypeError (#3260).</li>
                  <li>  - Fix request.base 'idna' codec error (#3261).</li>
                  <li>  - Fix unable to change password (#3262).</li>
                  <li>Extractor plugin</li>
                  <li>  - Fix potential error starting plugin.</li>
                  <li>Documentation</li>
                  <li>  - Fix macOS install typo.</li>
                  <li>  - Fix Windows install instructions.</li>
               </ul>
          </description> 
      </release>
  </releases>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.delugetorrent.Deluge.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
