<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
    <id>org.kde.knetwalk</id>
    <name>KNetwalk</name>
    <name xml:lang="ar">كي نتووك</name>
    <name xml:lang="bn">কেনেটওয়াক</name>
    <name xml:lang="es">Cables</name>
    <name xml:lang="hi">केनेटवॉक</name>
    <summary>Make the right cable connections and win</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ar">أنجز توصيلات الكابلات الصحيحة وحقق الفوز</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="bn">যথাযথ তারগুলো সংযুক্ত করে খেলা জিতুন</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="es">Haz las conexiones correctas para ganar</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="fr">Faites la bonne connexion de câbles pour gagner</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="hi">सही केबल कनेक्शन कीजिए और जीतिए</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="id">Buatlah koneksi kabel yang tepat untuk menang</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Conecte os cabos corretamente e vença</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="ro">Conecteaza corect cablurile ca sa castigi</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="th">ทำการเชื่อมต่อเคเบิลให้ถูกต้องและชนะ</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="vi">Nối đúng cáp để giành chiến thắng</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">连接正确电报以获胜</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="zh_TW">進行正確的接線並獲勝</summary>
    <description><p>Who knew building computer networks could be fun? You&apos;ll need to create the right connections in as few turns as possible to win - so get ready to move the wires and figure out the puzzle quickly! Once you’ve succeeded, you’ll find a high score list, allowing you to find competitors! This app helps you understand how computer networks work, but more importantly, it’s an enjoyable and competitive game you’ll love to play.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ar"><p>من كان يعلم أن بناء شبكات حاسوبية يمكن أن يكون أمرا ممتعاً؟ حيث تحتاج للفوز إلى إنشاء الروابط الصحيحة بأقل عدد ممكن من النقلات. لذا تجهز لتحريك الاسلاك و اكتشاف هذه اللعبة الأحجية  بسرعة! عند نجاحك، ستظهر لك قائمة النتائج الأعلى حتى تعرف من هم منافسيك! و يساعدك هذا التطبيق على فهم كيف عمل الشبكات الحاسوبية، و ما هو أهم من ذلك فهي لعبة ممتعة و تنافسية  ستعشق لعبها.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="bn"><p>কে জানতো কম্পিউটার নেটওয়ার্ক তৈরি করাও এত মজা হতে পারে? জেতার জন্যে যতো কম চালে সম্ভব আপনাকে সঠিক সংযোগটি তৈরি করতে হবে - তাই তারগুলো সরিয়ে ধাঁধার সমাধান করার জন্য দ্রুত তৈরি হয়ে যান! আপনি যখন সফল হবেন তখন আপনি উচ্চ স্কোরের তালিকা পাবেন যেখানে প্রতিদ্বন্দ্বীদের নাম খুঁজে পাবেন! এই এ্যাপ আপনাকে কম্পিউটার নেটওয়ার্ক কীভাবে কাজ করে তা বুঝতে সাহায্য করবে, তবে আরো গুরুত্বপূর্ণ যেটা, এটা একটি উপভোগ্য ও প্রতিদ্বন্দ্বিতামূলক খেলা যা আপনার পছন্দ হবেই।</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="es"><p>¿Quién sabía que crear redes informáticas sería tan divertido? Tendrás que crear las conexiones adecuadas en el menor número de turnos posible para ganar, ¡así que prepárate para mover los hilos y solucionar el rompecabezas rápidamente! Una vez que has tenido éxito, encontrarás una lista de puntuación para encontrar competidores. Esta aplicación te ayudará a entender cómo funcionan las redes de computadoras, pero más importante aún, es un juego divertido y competitivo que te encantará jugar.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="fr"><p>Qui aurait cru que la construction de réseaux informatiques pouvait être amusante ? Vous devrez créer la bonne connexion en aussi peu de tours que possible pour gagner — soyez donc prêt à déplacer les câbles et résolvez le puzzle rapidement ! Une fois que vous avez réussi, vous trouverez une liste des meilleurs scores, vous permettant de trouver des adversaires ! Cette application aide à comprendre comment les réseaux informatiques fonctionnent, mais surtout, c’est un jeu amusant et compétitif auquel vous adorerez jouer.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="hi"><p>किसे पता था कि कम्यूटर नेटवर्क बनाना इतना मजेदार हो सकता है? जीतने के लिए आपको यहां सही कनेक्शन बनाने होंगे- यानी आपको वायर लेकर पहेली का तेजी से हल निकालने के लिए तैयार होना होगा। सफल होने पर आपको हाई स्कोर लिस्ट मिलेगी, जिससे आपको प्रतियोगी खोजने में मदद मिलेगी। यह ऐप आपको कम्प्यूटर नेटवर्क के काम करने के तरीके के बारे में समझने में मदद करता है, पर उससे भी अहम है कि यह काफी मजेदार और प्रतियोगी खेल है जो आपको खूब पसंद आएगा।</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="id"><p>Siapa sangka membangun jaringan komputer itu menyenangkan? Agar menang Anda perlu membuat sambungan yang tepat menggunakan langkah sesedikit mungkin. Jadi bersiaplah untuk memindahkan kabel-kabel dan memecahkan teka-teki dengan cepat! Setelah berhasil, Anda akan melihat daftar skor tertinggi, sehingga Anda dapat menemukan pesaing! Aplikasi ini membantu Anda memahami cara kerja jaringan komputer, tetapi yang lebih penting, ini adalah permainan yang menyenangkan dan kompetitif yang akan Anda sukai.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR"><p>Quem diria que a construção de redes de computadores pode ser divertida? Você vai precisar criar conexões com a menor quantidade de voltas possível, então esteja pronto para mover os cabos e descobrir o enigma rapidamente. Se conseguir, você encontrará uma lista de pontuações altas, permitindo-lhe encontrar concorrentes. Este programa te ajuda a entender como funcionam as redes de computadores mas, o mais importante, é um jogo agradável e competitivo que você vai adorar.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="ro"><p>Cine a stiut ca pentru a construi retele de calculatoare ai nevoie si de distractie?Va trebui să creați conexiunile potrivite în cât mai puține ture posibil pentru a câștiga - deci pregătiți-vă pentru a muta fire și ghiciti puzzle-ul repede! După ce ați reușit, veți găsi o listă de mare cu scor, permițându-vă să găsiți concurenți! Această aplicație vă ajută să înțelegeți modul în care rețelele de calculatoare  lucreaza, dar mai important, este un joc plăcut și competitiv.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="th"><p>ใครจะรู้ว่าเครือข่ายคอมพิวเตอร์ในอาคารจะสนุกได้ คุณจะต้องสร้างการเชื่อมต่อที่ถูกต้องให้น้อยรอบที่สุดเท่าที่จะเป็นไปได้เพื่อที่จะชนะ - เตรียมตัวให้พร้อมที่จะย้ายสายไฟและคิดออกปริศนาอย่างรวดเร็ว! เมื่อคุณประสบความสำเร็จคุณจะพบกับรายการคะแนนสูง ช่วยให้คุณสามารถพบคู่แข่ง! แอพนี้จะช่วยให้คุณเข้าใจวิธีการทำงานของเครือข่ายคอมพิวเตอร์ แต่ที่สำคัญมันเป็นเกมที่สนุกและมีการแข่งขันที่คุณจะรักที่จะเล่น</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="vi"><p>Ai biết được rằng việc xây dựng mạng máy tính cũng có nhiều điều vui nhộn? Bạn sẽ phải nối đúng trong vài lượt chơi để có thể giành chiến thắng - vì thế hãy sẵn sàng nối dây và giải quyết câu đố thật nhanh! Khi thành công, bạn sẽ thấy danh sách người chơi đạt điểm cao để bạn có thể tìm ra đối thủ của mình! Ứng dụng này giúp bạn hiểu về cách hoạt động của hệ thống mạng máy tính, nhưng quan trọng hơn, đây là trò chơi hào hứng và tranh tài mà bạn sẽ thích chơi.</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_CN"><p>你们知道构建计算机网络其实很有趣吗？你需要创建正确的链接，越少越好，这样才会赢。所以，准备移动电线，尽快解答题目！一旦你成功，你就会发现一个高分列表，允许你找到竞争对手。这个程序可以帮助你了解计算机网络，更重要的是，你还可以享受一个愉快且具有竞争力的游戏。</p></description>
    <description xml:lang="zh_TW"><p>誰想得到建立電腦網路會很有趣呢？你必須在越少越好的回合數內建立正確的連線以獲得勝利 - 所以準備移動電線並快速解決謎題吧！成功以後可以看到一個高分列表讓你找到對手！此 app 能協助你了解電腦網路的運作方式，但更重要的是，這是個愉快而有競爭性的遊戲，你會愛上它的。</p></description>
    <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/</url>
    <screenshots>
      <screenshot type="default">
        <image type="source" xml:lang="pt">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Knetwalk/pt/org.kde.knetwalk-screenshot1.jpg</image>
        <image type="source" xml:lang="es">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Knetwalk/es/org.kde.knetwalk-screenshot1.jpg</image>
        <image type="source">https://d3lapyynmdp1i9.cloudfront.net/screenshots/org.kde.Knetwalk/C/org.kde.knetwalk-screenshot1.jpg</image>
      </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
		<release version="18.08.0" date="2018-08-16"/>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>