<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.freedesktop.weston</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>Weston</name>
  <summary>A lightweight and functional Wayland compositor</summary>

  <description>
    <p>
      Weston is the reference implementation of a Wayland compositor, as well as a
      useful environment in and of itself.
    </p>
    <p>
      Out of the box, Weston provides a very basic desktop, or a full-featured
      environment for non-desktop uses such as automotive, embedded, in-flight,
      industrial, kiosks, set-top boxes and TVs. It also provides a library allowing
      other projects to build their own full-featured environments on top of Weston's
      core.
    </p>
    <p>
      The core focus of Weston is correctness and reliability. Weston aims to be lean
      and fast, but more importantly, to be predictable. Whilst Weston does have known
      bugs and shortcomings, we avoid unknown or variable behaviour as much as
      possible, including variable performance such as occasional spikes in frame
      display time.
    </p>
    <p>
      A small suite of example or demo clients are also provided: though they can be
      useful in themselves, their main purpose is to be an example or test case for
      others building compositors or clients.
    </p>
    <p>
      If you are after a more mainline desktop experience, the
      GNOME and KDE projects provide
      full-featured desktop environments built on the Wayland protocol. Many other
      projects also exist providing Wayland clients and desktop environments: you are
      not limited to just what you can find in Weston.
    </p>
  </description>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />

  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.freedesktop.weston.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Weston</caption>
      <image>https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/wayland/weston/-/raw/main/doc/wayland-screenshot.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.freedesktop.org/wayland/weston</url>

  <releases>
    <release version="10.0.0" date="2022-02-01">
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
