<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.cryptomator.Cryptomator</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Cryptomator</name>
  <summary>Free client-side encryption for your cloud files</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Cryptomator provides transparent, client-side encryption for your cloud. Protect your documents from unauthorized
      access. Cryptomator is free and open source software, so you can rest assured there are no backdoors.
    </p>
    <p>
      Cryptomator encrypts file contents and names using AES. Your passphrase is protected against bruteforcing attempts
      using scrypt. Directory structures get obfuscated. The only thing which cannot be encrypted without breaking your
      cloud synchronization is the modification date of your files.
    </p>
    <p>
      Cryptomator is a free and open source software licensed under the GPLv3. This allows anyone to check our code. It
      is impossible to introduce backdoors for third parties. Also we cannot hide vulnerabilities. And the best thing
      is: There is no need to trust us, as you can control us!
    </p>
    <p>
      Vendor lock-ins are impossible. Even if we decided to stop development: The source code is already cloned by
      hundreds of other developers. As you don't need an account, you will never stand in front of locked doors.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.cryptomator.Cryptomator.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cryptomator.org/img/featured-image.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cryptomator.org/img/screenshots/app1.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cryptomator.org/img/screenshots/app2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/cryptomator/cryptomator/issues/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://cryptomator.org/#payment-modal</url>
  <url type="faq">https://community.cryptomator.org/c/kb/faq</url>
  <url type="help">https://community.cryptomator.org/</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://cryptomator.org/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://poeditor.com/join/project/bHwbvJmx0E</url>
  <developer_name>Skymatic</developer_name>
  <update_contact>https://skymatic.de/en/contact/</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release type="stable" date="2019-04-24" version="1.4.8" />
  </releases>
</component>
