<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
	<id>se.cendio.tlclient</id>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">se.cendio.tlclient.desktop</launchable>
	<name>ThinLinc Client</name>
	<developer_name>Cendio AB</developer_name>
	<summary>The Linux remote desktop server built on open source technology</summary>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://www.cendio.com/thinlinc/docs/legal/eula</project_license>
	<url type="homepage">https://www.cendio.com</url>
	<description>
		<p>
			The ThinLinc Client is a remote desktop client used to connect to a ThinLinc
			Server. With ThinLinc you are able to get access to Linux desktops and
			applications.
		</p>
		<p>
			You can use the ThinLinc Client to connect to an existing ThinLinc Server. You
			can also set up your own ThinLinc Server. The ThinLinc Server can be downloaded
			for free from https://www.cendio.com for Linux machines. The ThinLinc Server is
			free to use for a limited amount of concurrent users per organization.
		</p>
		<p>
			ThinLinc is a software that enables organizations to implement a
			Linux server-based computing (SBC) infrastructure. By centralizing
			computing resources in the data center rather than distributing them
			amongst end-users, IT systems become more efficient, secure, and
			accessible. End-users' desktops and applications are published from
			a central location, providing a seamless and familiar environment
			regardless of which device the user is connecting from, or the user
			location. Redundancy, inherent in a server-based solution, increases
			the availability as well.
		</p>
		<p>
			ThinLinc combines the tools and infrastructure required for
			Linux-based SBC into a mature, stable, and fully-supported package.
			It consists of both server-side components (session-broker,
			load-balancer, administration interface, etc.) and end-user
			components (client software, customization tools, etc.) to provide a
			complete solution.
		</p>
		<p>
			NOTE: This package is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported
			by Cendio AB.
		</p>
	</description>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Linux remote desktop client — Access Linux desktops and applications from any device</caption>
			<image type="source" width="2560" height="1440">https://www.cendio.com/resources/images/screenshots/thinlinc/linux-en-intro.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Easy file access — Work with local files on the remote desktop</caption>
			<image type="source" width="2560" height="1440">https://www.cendio.com/resources/images/screenshots/thinlinc/linux-en-local-drives.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Access your Linux desktop in fullscreen — For a seamless desktop experience</caption>
			<image type="source" width="2560" height="1440">https://www.cendio.com/resources/images/screenshots/thinlinc/linux-en-fullscreen-mode.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Customize your experience — Set up choices of different desktops or applications</caption>
			<image type="source" width="2560" height="1440">https://www.cendio.com/resources/images/screenshots/thinlinc/linux-en-profile-chooser.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Login in your ThinLinc server — Authenticate with for example OTP, Kerberos or a regular password</caption>
			<image type="source" width="2560" height="1440">https://www.cendio.com/resources/images/screenshots/thinlinc/linux-en-login-window.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<caption>Graphics acceleration for demanding tasks — Server-side GPU acceleration via VirtualGL</caption>
			<image type="source" width="2560" height="1440">https://www.cendio.com/resources/images/screenshots/thinlinc/linux-en-graphics-acceleration.png</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1">
		<content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
	</content_rating>
	<releases>
		<release version="4.14.0-2324" date="2022-03-07"/>
		<release version="4.13.0-2172" date="2021-09-02"/>
	</releases>
	<custom>
		<value key="Purism::form_factor">workstation</value>
	</custom>
</component>
