<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>space.coin.wallet</id>

  <name>Coin Wallet</name>
  <summary>Coin Wallet — self-custodial multicurrency crypto wallet</summary>

  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>

  <url type="homepage">https://coin.space/</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/CoinSpace/CoinSpace</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/CoinSpace/CoinSpace/issues</url>

  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>Finance</category>
  </categories>

  <icon type="stock">space.coin.wallet</icon>

  <supports>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </supports>

  <description>
    <p>
      Trusted by over 24 million users in over 170 countries, Coin Wallet is the most popular and secure cryptocurrency and bitcoin wallet.
    </p>
    <p>
      Use your Coin Wallet to easily buy, sell, and exchange Bitcoin (BTC), Bitcoin cash (BCH), Ethereum (ETH), Ethereum Classic (ETC), Solana (SOL), Litecoin (LTC), Dogecoin (DOGE), Dash (DASH), Ripple (XRP), Stellar (XLM), EOS, Monero (XMR), Binance Smart Chain (BNB), Avalanche (AVAX), Cardano (ADA), Polygon (MATIC), TRON (TRX), Arbitrum One (ARB), Toncoin (TON), Optimism (OP), Fantom (FTM), Sui (SUI), and over 2000 ERC20, BEP20, ARC20, TRC20, SPL, Polygon, Arbitrum, Optimism, Sui tokens or DeFi tokens!
    </p>
    <p>
      With over $120B transacted in cryptocurrency, the Coin Wallet app for Linux is the simplest, most secure way to purchase and protect your bitcoin wallet and cryptocurrency.
    </p>
    <p>
      BITCOIN WALLET APP
    </p>
    <p>
      Get started in seconds on our user-friendly cryptocurrency wallet app! No registration or sign ups required to start your bitcoin wallet. Easily exchange, sell, hold or buy bitcoin BTC, BCH, ETH, ETC, SOL, BNB, XRP, DASH, LTC, DOGE, XMR, ADA, MATIC, TRX, ARB, TON, OP, FTM, SUI, and other cryptocurrency. Using our wallet app, you can also access Web 3 Decentralized Applications (DApps) powered by Ethereum and Binance Smart Chain smart contracts!
    </p>
    <p>
      EASILY BUY BITCOIN, BITCOIN CASH, ETHEREUM
    </p>
    <p>
      Coin Wallet makes it simple to buy bitcoin and other cryptocurrency with a credit card, checking account, cash, or another cryptocurrency! Trade BTC, Bitcoin cash (BCH), Ethereum (Ether ETH), Binance Coin (BNB) and over 2000 popular ERC20 and BEP20 tokens instantly with other cryptocurrencies or tokens in your Coin Wallet.
    </p>
    <p>
      SECURE DIGITAL WALLET
    </p>
    <p>
      Store all your valuable cryptocurrency in one place in your pocket - All cryptocurrency is protected on your own device utilizing industry-leading hardware encryption. Coin Wallet provides a simple and secure wallet where only you have access to your private keys and your crypto!
    </p>
    <p>
      BITCOIN WALLET SECURITY &amp; PRIVACY
    </p>
    <p>
      No need to create an account or signup - Coin Wallet connects directly to blockchain networks for maximum security and privacy! Our server-free environment fully localizes each installed application. With our wallet app, you are in total control of your privacy and crypto wallet!
    </p>
    <p>
      FAST BITCOIN WALLET APP SUPPORT
    </p>
    <p>
      Get all your bitcoin wallet app questions answered in less than 2 hours. Our global support team is ready to help everyone, from first-time bitcoin wallet buyers to longtime cryptocurrency wallet holders.
    </p>
    <p>
      DESIGNED FOR WALLET BEGINNERS AND EXPERTS
    </p>
    <p>
      The Coin Wallet is easy for everyone, from crypto wallet beginners to seasoned bitcoin wallet experts. You&apos;ll see how easy it is to exchange, sell, and buy any cryptocurrency in your bitcoin wallet.
    </p>
    <p>
      CRYPTO PAYMENTS
    </p>
    <p>
      Quickly send cryptocurrency payments to anyone, anywhere in the world.
    </p>
    <p>
      For feedback and assistance, you can reach us at support@coin.space You can also find us on Twitter: @CoinAppWallet
   </p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">space.coin.wallet.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2024/05/Mac_-_1-1717079199.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2024/05/Mac_-_4-1717079199.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://dashboard.snapcraft.io/site_media/appmedia/2024/05/Mac_-_5-1717079199.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="6.8.0" date="2025-02-24" />
  </releases>
</component>
