<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019 Codethink Ltd -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>io.trustable.stpadocumentationtool</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.trustable.stpadocumentationtool.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>BSD-3-Clause</project_license>
  <name>Stpa-documentation-tool</name>
  <summary>A System Theoretic Process Analysis tool - that facilitates STPA and automates documentation</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      STPA is a powerful tool for improving the safety and stability of
      critical systems. This tool facilitates the storage of analysis data
      and automates the production of analysis documentation.
    </p>
    <p>
      As systems increase in size and complexity, their analysis also increases
      in complexity. Quickly, the documentation can become a time consuming
      distraction from the analysis itself.
    </p>
    <p>
      This tool allows the user to enter data in the standard format described
      in the Massachusetts Institute of Technology 'STPA Handbook'. This includes
      Losses, Hazards, Unsafe Control Actions, and Scenarios including True Statements,
      and other information. The user can use these types to build their
      preferred analysis structure.
    </p>
    <p>
      The tool automatically handles reference numbers for all items in the
      analysis, and data items can be linked and cross-referenced in the
      structure. This reduces effort, and automates all numbering. Items
      can be renumbered easily, and all links and cross-references are 
      updated automatically.
    </p>
    <p>
      Stpa Documentation Tool is 100% free and open source software based on
      open source licensing from Qt Company. Please refer to the Gitlab
      repository LICENSE.md at https://gitlab.com/trustable/stpa-documentation-tool.
      Contributions to this project are welcome and encouraged!
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://gitlab.com/trustable/stpa-documentation-tool</url>
  <developer_name>Codethink Ltd</developer_name>
  <update_contact>stpa-documentation-tool@codethink.co.uk</update_contact>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0" date="2019-08-14">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Version 1.0, for flathub release</li>
          <li>Supports links, references, arbitrary hierarchy, yaml save files</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
</component>

