<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>uk.co.agilemde.agileuml</id>
  <name>AgileUML</name>
  <summary>Use Model-Driven Engineering to rapidly develop software with UML for various software platforms</summary>
  <developer_name>Kevin Lano and contributors</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">uk.co.agilemde.agileuml.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>EPL-2.0</project_license>
  <categories>
    <category>Development</category>
    <category>Building</category>
    <category>IDE</category>
    <category>ComputerScience</category>
    <category>Java</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>development</keyword>
    <keyword>programming</keyword>
    <keyword>modelling</keyword>
    <keyword>code</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">MDE</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">MDD</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">UML</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">OCL</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">Java</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">C++</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">C</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">C#</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">Python</keyword>
    <keyword translate="no">Swift</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <description>
    <p>
      The AgileUML Toolset provides rapid automated construction of software systems (in Java, C, JSP/Servlets, Python, Swift, Android, iOS, Go, C# or C++) from high-level UML specifications (class diagrams, use cases, state machines and activities). It also enables re-engineering of legacy systems written in COBOL, VB, C, Java, JavaScript and Python, via reverse-engineering to UML/OCL.
    </p>
    <p>
      AgileUML can be used as part of software development to reduce coding costs, time and errors, and to ensure a greater consistency between system components written in multiple languages. It can ensure the correct and consistent implementation of business data and logic in multiple system components.
    </p>
    <p>
      AgileUML is currently an Eclipse incubation project. It is cheifly developed by Kevin Lano. However, this Flatpak is unofficial and is not chiefly maintained by Lano or the Eclipse Foundation. For issues with this Flatpak that cannot be reproduced outside of the Flatpak sandbox, please open an issue in the Flatpak manifest's GitHub repository: https://github.com/flathub/uk.co.agilemde.agileuml/issues/
    </p>
    <p>
      AgileUML supports:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Specification of systems using UML class diagrams, use cases, OCL, and a pseudocode activity language</li>
      <li>Synthesis of complete functional code in Java, C++, C, C#, Python and Swift</li>
      <li>Synthesis of Android and iOS mobile apps from specifications: we are the first to offer synthesis of SwiftUI apps from specifications</li>
      <li>Synthesis of web service and EIS code from specification</li>
      <li>Synthesis of test cases and test harnesses from specifications</li>
      <li>Tools to assist in writing new code generators for further implementation languages</li>
      <li>Abstraction from Java, C, VB6, COBOL, Python and JavaScript code to UML/OCL</li>
      <li>Verification and quality analysis tools</li>
      <li>Support for model transformations, including QVT-R, ATL and ETL</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      Mobile app synthesis for Android and iOS can be done with the AgileUML toolset:
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Specification in UML/OCL</li>
      <li>Synthesis of XML UI code and Java functional code for Android Studio</li>
      <li>Synthesis of Swift 5 code and SwiftUI Views for iOS</li>
      <li>Model-View-Controller and Model-View-ViewModel architectures</li>
      <li>Component libraries for authentication, cloud and local datastores, graphics and file management</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://agilemde.co.uk/app5synth.jpg</image>
      <caption>Mobile app synthesis for Android and iOS</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://agilemde.co.uk/</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/eclipse/agileuml</url>
  <url type="contact">https://agilemde.co.uk/links.html</url>
  <url type="help">https://www.researchgate.net/publication/367167873_The_Agile_UML_Manual</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/eclipse/agileuml/issues</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="v2.3" date="2023-12-20">
      <description>
        This version adds new facilities for reverse-engineering Python and Pascal code to create models, and to refactor specifications to remove flaws such as excessive statement nesting depth and excessive parameter lists. A powerful type-inference facility is added to support the translation of Python and JS code to typed languages such as Java. The CSTL/CGTL language for defining code generators and abstractors has been further developed. A significant application is the MathApp (mathapp.jar) for financial specification and implementation, using CSTL for algebraic simplification. Output of models in PlantUML format is also added.
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <update_contact>zishanfrahman_AT_outlook.com</update_contact>
</component>
