<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">

  <!-- Copyright 2019 Adam Ellery <a.ellery@uq.edu.au> -->
  <id>au.edu.uq.esys.escript</id>
  <metadata_license>Apache-2.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>Apache-2.0</project_license>
  <name>esys-escript</name>
  <summary> 
    esys-escript is a programming tool for implementing mathematical models in python using the finite element method (FEM) 
  </summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      esys-escript is a programming tool for implementing mathematical models in python using the finite element method (FEM). As users do not access the data structures it is very easy to use and scripts can run on desktop computers as well as highly parallel supercomputer without changes. Application areas for escript include earth mantle convection, geophysical inversion, earthquakes, porous media flow, reactive transport, plate subduction, erosion, and tsunamis. esys-escript is designed as an easy-to-use environment for implementing mathematical models based on non-linear, coupled, time-dependent partial differential equations. It uses the finite element method (FEM) for spatial discretization and data representation. Escript is used through python and is suitable for rapid prototyping (e.g for a student project or thesis) as well as for large software projects. Scripts are executed in parallel using MPI, OpenMP and hybrid mode processing over 50 million unknowns on several thousand cores on a parallel computer.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">uq.esys.escript.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://launchpad.net/escript-finley/</url>
  <releases>
    <release date="2019-01-01" version="5.3">
      <description>
        <p>
          eScript version 5.3. (Initial flatpak release.)
        </p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <developer_name>University of Queensland</developer_name>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://launchpad.net/escript-finley/</url>
  <url type="help">https://launchpad.net/escript-finley/</url>
  <update_contact>a.ellery@uq.edu.au</update_contact>
</component>
