<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright Dion © 2025 -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>vc.dion.Dion</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">vc.dion.Dion.desktop</launchable>
  <name>Dion</name>
  <developer id="vc.dion.Dion">
    <name>dion.vc</name>
  </developer>
  <summary>Corporate communications platform</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Платформа корпоративных коммуникаций</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary=https://diongo.ru/pdfs/license_agreement_DION.pdf</project_license>
  <url type="homepage">https://dion.vc/</url>
  <url type="help">https://faq.dion.vc/</url>
  <update_contact>support@dion.vc</update_contact>
  <description>
    <p>Video conferencing service with a hybrid cloud infrastructure.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Сервис видеоконференцсвязи с гибридной облачной инфраструктурой.</p>
    <ul>
      <li>A full-featured video conferencing system from DION with extensive capabilities for comfortable communication: high-quality audio and video, support for up to 5,000 users, guaranteed security, and much more.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Полноценная ВКС-система от DION с широкими возможностями для комфортного общения: высокое качество звука и видео, доступно до 5000 пользователей, гарантированная безопасность и многое другое.</li>
      <li>A custom corporate social video network with channels, communication, and video sharing. Create, share, and engage users in a secure and controlled environment. Meeting recordings are stored on a video hosting platform, where any call can be automatically transcribed and recorded in just a few clicks.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Собственная корпоративная социальная видеосеть с каналами, общением и шерингом видео. Создавайте контент, обменивайтесь им и привлекайте к нему пользователей в безопасной и контролируемой среде. Записи встреч хранятся на видеохостинге, где в пару кликов любой звонок можно автоматически транскрибировать и составить протокол.</li>
      <li>Full-fledged chats for personal and group communication with extensive functionality: from editing to forwarding messages.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Полноценные чаты для личного и группового общения с широкой функциональностью: от редактирования до пересылки сообщений.</li>
      <li>A solution from DION that lets you host events of any size. Get all the features you need: quick and easy event creation, inviting guests using a variety of scenarios, and live streaming.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Решение от DION, с которым вы можете проводить события любого масштаба. Получите все возможности: быстрое и легкое создание мероприятия, приглашение гостей по разным сценариям и проведение трансляций.</li>
      <li>A meeting room booking and management system that will replace expensive imported alternatives. Create, modify, and cancel bookings, and conduct meetings with a single solution from DION.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Система бронирования и управления встречами в переговорных комнатах, которая заменит дорогостоящие импортные аналоги. Создавайте, изменяйте и отменяйте брони, а также проводите собрания с единым решением от DION.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>This package is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by dion.vc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Этот пакет не проверен, не связан и не поддерживается dion.vc.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Conferences</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Конференции</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/flathub/13bd4747a6d4ce37e101cb0c63a5dbfee9d0e017/conf.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Video hosting</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Видеохостинг</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/flathub/13bd4747a6d4ce37e101cb0c63a5dbfee9d0e017/video.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Chats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Чаты</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/flathub/13bd4747a6d4ce37e101cb0c63a5dbfee9d0e017/chats.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Broadcasts</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Трансляции</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/flathub/13bd4747a6d4ce37e101cb0c63a5dbfee9d0e017/translations.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Rooms</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Комнаты</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/flathub/flathub/13bd4747a6d4ce37e101cb0c63a5dbfee9d0e017/rooms.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
    <category>InstantMessaging</category>
    <category>VideoConference</category>
    <category>Telephony</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <requires>
    <internet>always</internet>
  </requires>
  <releases>
    <release version="5.27.1" date="2025-11-06">
      <description>
        <p>When clicking on a conference link, the conference window did not open in the desktop application.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">При переходе по ссылке конференции, окно конференции не открывалось в десктоп-приложении.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
