<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>io.github.wxmaxima_developers.wxMaxima</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>wxMaxima</name>
  <summary>A graphical user interface for Maxima, a powerful computer algebra system</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      wxMaxima is a graphical user interface for the computer algebra system Maxima:
      a program that solves mathematical problems by manipulating
      equations (and outputting the resulting formula), instead of just
      calculating a number. wxMaxima eases the use of Maxima by making
      most of its commands available through a menu system and by
      providing input dialogs for commands that require more than one
      argument. It also implements its own display engine that outputs
      mathematical symbols directly instead of depicting them with
      ASCII characters. 
    </p>
    <p>
      wxMaxima also features 2D and 3D inline plots, simple animations,
      mixing of text and mathematical calculations to create documents,
      exporting of input and output to TeX, document structuring and a
      browser for Maxima's manual including command index and full text
      searching.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://wxMaxima-developers.github.io/wxmaxima/images/linux_1.jpg</image>
      <caption>An example of a plot embedded in a work sheet</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://wxMaxima-developers.github.io/wxmaxima/images/linux_2.jpg</image>
      <caption>Another example of a plot embedded in a work sheet</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://wxMaxima-developers.github.io/wxmaxima/images/linux_3.jpg</image>
      <caption>wxMaxima provides wizards for the most important functions of Maxima</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/wxMaxima-developers/wxmaxima/issues</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://wxMaxima-developers.github.io/wxmaxima/</url>
  <url type="help">https://wxmaxima-developers.github.io/wxmaxima/help.html</url>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>HighContrast</kudo>
    <kudo>UserDocs</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.wxmaxima_developers.wxMaxima.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
    <release version="18.12.0" date="2018-12-25">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Use C++'s strong typing for more enums.</li>
          <li>Another big SpeedUp.</li>
          <li>Now we make sure that the Manifest telling wxMaxima is high-DPI aware is the only manifest packaged with the .exe file.</li>
          <li>Tried to simplify the display code</li>
          <li>Source file and function names that more closely their current meaning.</li>
          <li>Many bug fixes.</li>
          <li>Now we pass the canonical locale name to Maxima, not the short one.</li>
          <li>We no more try to set Maxima's locale if it doesn't differ from the system's default one.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.11.4" date="2018-11-26">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Speeding up the display by not trying to display things that aren't in the region that is currently redrawn on the screen broke printing =&gt; Disable the speed-up whilst printing.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.11.3" date="2018-11-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>A user found a bug that is able to corrupt wxmx files and that was present since wxMaxima 18.10.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.11.2" date="2018-11-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Better horizontal spacing of cells that are wider than lines</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.11.1" date="2018-11-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Better horizontal spacing of headings.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.11.0" date="2018-11-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>GTK3 Compatibility</li>
          <li>Worked around C compiler bugs that truncated the beginning of long strings</li>
          <li>Zoom gestures for more computers</li>
          <li>A better lisp mode</li>
          <li>Limit cells now can be broken into lines if they are too wide for the window</li>
          <li>Major performance improvements</li>
          <li>Several appearance improvements</li>
          <li>Many additional bug fixes</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.10.2" date="2018-10-22">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>A more stable Enhanced Metafile output for Windows. Fixes a crash multiple users have experienced.</li>
          <li>Translation uodates.</li>
          <li>Better cleanup on restarting Maxima.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.10.1" date="2018-09-26">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Corrected the version number wxMaxima identifies itself with. Everything else is identical to 18.10.0.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.10" date="2018-09-26">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Defer any try to change Maxima's configuration until all questions are answered.</li>
          <li>A menu item that sets the autosubscript feature for the current worksheet.</li>
          <li>A menu allowing to switch floats to engineering format.</li>
          <li>Maxima can now pass the values of variables to wxMaxima.</li>
          <li>Autocompletion for functions from lisp-only packages and for all of Maxima's built in functions.</li>
          <li>A context-sensitive "draw" sidepane.</li>
          <li>We now allow a packet from Maxima to end in the middle of an unicode codepoint.</li>
          <li>If the name of a lisp function is known it now is displayed.</li>
          <li>A right-click menu that copies an animation to the clipboard.</li>
          <li>A new default value for the current MathJaX release.</li>
          <li>A "recent packages" menu for packages loaded from load() or from the menu.</li>
          <li>Advertise the current file and the file's state to the Operating System</li>
          <li>Copy as Enhanced Metafile (Windows only).</li>
          <li>Code simplifications.</li>
          <li>A dockable panel for the debug messages.</li>
          <li>A more modern theme.</li>
          <li>Draw: A right-click menu allowing to open images from the current session as interactive gnuplot sessions.</li>
          <li>Migrate the config file to a XDG-compatible location if wxWidgets is new enough to support it.</li>
          <li>A "Tip of the day" dialogue that allows for resizing, scrollbars and work while it is still open.</li>
          <li>Matrices can now be displayed using round and square brackets.</li>
          <li>Various High-DPI enhancements.</li>
          <li>Enhancements for low-resolution screens.</li>
          <li>Many bug fixes.</li>
          <li>Reduced the number of autogenerated files, installed files and external dependencies to a minimum.</li>
          <li>Big performance improvements, again.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="18.02" date="2018-02-17">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>More tooltips</li>
          <li>A menu containing the most important commands for lists.</li>
          <li>TableOfContents: A right-click menu item that allows to toggle display of section numbers</li>
          <li>The size of images can now be restricted to any amount of centimeters.</li>
          <li>On a few operating systems: The network indicator icon now knows how much CPU power Maxima uses.</li>
          <li>Autocompletion now suggests the names of built-in packages for load(), batch() and batchload().</li>
          <li>Autocompletion now suggests the names of built-in demos for demo().</li>
          <li>wxMaxima can now handle requests to display raw lisp elements.</li>
          <li>A drop-down box for changing cell styles</li>
          <li>If an input cell is hidden and has no output it now is no more displayed as a blank vertical space.</li>
          <li>wxMaxima no more requires the icon files, tooltips and autocompletion files to be shipped as separate files, which makes creating a ready-to-install package of wxMaxima easier and less error-prone.</li>
          <li>Autosave is now enabled by default on new installs.</li>
          <li>Big code cleanups.</li>
          <li>Many bugfixes</li>
          <li>Many performance improvements</li>
          <li>Dropped the autotools as the cmake build of wxMaxima is way more powerful.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="17.10.1" date="2017-10-22"/>
    <release version="17.10" date="2017-09-30">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Jump to the char containing the error on encountering unmatched parenthesis.</li>
          <li>Try to place the cursor near the error in all other cases.</li>
          <li>Attempt to mark the whole error message in red. This is bound to fail in some cases as Maxima sometimes only sends part of an error message through the error() command. But it is better than nothing.</li>
          <li>Detect and mark most warnings.</li>
          <li>A "evaluate cells below" right-click-menu item.</li>
          <li>Autosave now even works for unsaved documents adding them to the "recent documents" list if needed.</li>
          <li>Big parenthesis are now drawn using unicode characters, if available.</li>
          <li>Nicer integral, Product and Sum signs, optionally including antialiassing even if no font provides them.</li>
          <li>MouseOver tooltips for some of the more exotic worksheet items.</li>
          <li>A "Copy as svg" function that is as good as wxSVGFileDc allows us to be.</li>
          <li>Worksheet objects now can provide their own ToolTips.</li>
          <li>Config Dialogue: An editor for the startup file.</li>
          <li>It is now possible to select which formats "Ctrl+C" should place data on the clipboard in.</li>
          <li>Now multiple animations can run concurrently and can be told to autostart.</li>
          <li>A menu entry that allows to select 1D and ASCII Art Maths</li>
          <li>Recent files that currently don't exist are grayed out now.</li>
          <li>A command-line switch that triggers evaluation on startup of wxMaxima</li>
          <li>Many Bug Fixes and Performance improvements.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="17.05.1" date="2017-06-26">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>This release mainly fixes some issues related to Mac OS.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="17.05" date="2017-05-23">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>A config item that allows to disable printing of Cell brackets.</li>
          <li>Cell brackets of inactive cells can now be hidden.</li>
          <li>Due to popular demand we can now suppress the output of automatic labels.</li>
          <li>The option to use a Minus instead of a Hyphen.</li>
          <li>Table of Contents: Folded items are now grayed out.</li>
          <li>Table of Contents: A right-click menu.</li>
          <li>Copy-and-paste now includes hidden cells and folded items.</li>
          <li>Eye Candy: An indicator that shows when Maxima and wxMaxima exchange data. Double-clicking this indicator opens up the network monitor.</li>
          <li>Autocompletion now collects words from the current code cell, too.</li>
          <li>Better indentation of if clauses and loops.</li>
          <li>If the number is too long to display it now is still possible to copy it.</li>
          <li>Documented that box() highlights text in Maxima's output.</li>
          <li>the with_slider type of commands now uses wxstatusbar() in order to provide</li>
          <li>progress information for the user.</li>
          <li>Several scrolling fixes, again.</li>
          <li>Two concurrent wxMaxima instances now no more overwrite each other's "Recent files" list.</li>
          <li>If a error message or question arises or Maxima finishes calculating and the window currently isn't active the operating system is asked to notify the user in a non-disrupting way. For the case of the end of a calculation this can be turned off.</li>
          <li>The notification can be activated for the case that the window isn't active and Maxima finishes calculating, too.</li>
          <li>Invalid XML tags are now handled more gracefully</li>
          <li>Deduplicated the code for saving .wxm files</li>
          <li>content.xml files that have been extracted from a broken .wxmx file (e.G. using a text editor as UTF8-encoded TeXt without BOM can now be loaded by wxMaxima in order to reconstruct the worksheet.</li>
          <li>MacOs: Upgrading from a previous version should no more cause crashes due to font issues.</li>
          <li>MathJaX export can now be configured to instruct the html export to download MathJaX from a different URL: They moved the URL one can use and might do so again somewhere in the future.</li>
          <li>Maximum number of digits and if we use user-defined labels now are no more hardcoded into the worksheet at evaluation time.</li>
          <li>Anwers to Maxima's questions are now remembered across sessions.</li>
          <li>CMake is now our main build system: It is supported under MSVC, XCode, Code::Blocks, its output looks much nicer than the one from the autotools and setting it up uses much more straightforward constructs. The recipe to build a debian package using cmake can be found at https://code.launchpad.net/~peterpall/wxmaxima/packaging</li>
          <li>Massive speed-ups</li>
          <li>File/Open can now import .mac and .out files from Xmaxima</li>
          <li>Many additional bug fixes and stability enhancements.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="16.12.2" date="2017-01-25"/>
    <release version="16.12.1" date="2017-01-24"/>
    <release version="16.12" date="2016-12-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Not a change in wxMaxima, but useful: In Maxima >5.38 the load() command can load .wxm files like it would load .mac files.</li>
          <li>Better detection and diagnosis for Maxima process that terminate unexpectedly even if the OS fails to notify us that the network connection with Maxima has dropped.</li>
          <li>Incremental search</li>
          <li>Automatic line wrap</li>
          <li>Bullet lists now use real bullets.</li>
          <li>Markdown: Block quote support</li>
          <li>A button that temporarily hides all code cells</li>
          <li>Massive speedups in the drawing code.</li>
          <li>Added a wxstatusbar() command that allows a long-ranging block() to send a string about its progress to the status bar.</li>
          <li>Support for cells that are >5000 pixels wide</li>
          <li>Better High-DPI support</li>
          <li>A Kabyle Translation for users of wxWidgets >= 3.0.1</li>
          <li>Holding the "evaluate" key now evaluates all cells of the document one-by-one</li>
          <li>.wxm files now include image cells</li>
          <li>Drag-and-drop now handles image cells</li>
          <li>Copy bitmap now can generate higher-resolution bitmaps</li>
          <li>The application we drag-and-drop to now can select a format to get the data in including RTF, MathML, wxm, bitmap and plain text.</li>
          <li>A new "copy as plain text" right-click menu item that copies the input and output of a cell.</li>
          <li>An all-new manual and improved documentation of the source code.</li>
          <li>More unicode characters in the symbols pane</li>
          <li>Several content assistent enhancements for platforms that support it.</li>
          <li>Corrected a few scrolling bugs.</li>
          <li>Shift+Click now selects text or cells.</li>
          <li>Several small editor enhancements.</li>
          <li>Even if we scrolled away from evaluation wxMaxima now scrolls back to the cell if an error occurs.</li>
          <li>Integrals should now always be saved correctly.</li>
          <li>Errors in xml from Maxima or in the output cells of .wxmx files now result in error messages, not in silently discarded math elements.</li>
          <li>Many additional bug fixes and performance improvements.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="16.04.2" date="2016-05-11"/>
    <release version="16.04.1" date="2016-04-06"/>
    <release version="16.04" date="2016-04-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>A TeX-like subscript notation: A_1 is now by default shown as an A with an 1 as subscript</li>
          <li>High-quality icons for high-dpi screens.</li>
          <li>Some broken .wxmx files generated with wxMaxima 13.04 and older will now automatically be repaired</li>
          <li>Tried to make communication with Maxima more stable</li>
          <li>Debug: A monitor for the xml communication between Maxima and wxMaxima</li>
          <li>Leading White-space in front of a character that has to be escaped in XML is no more ignored.</li>
          <li>jpeg-encoded images are now no more converted to much larger png files on saving .wxmx files and on exporting.</li>
          <li>Images will now actually be converted to the target format.</li>
          <li>Bumped the minor version of the .wxmx format: Some old versions of wxMaxima will replace .jpg files embedded in .wxmx files by a placeholder on load</li>
          <li>Increased both speed and memory-efficiency of image handling</li>
          <li>Save the zoom factor at exit and reload it on opening a new file</li>
          <li>An option that makes wxMaxima use user-defined labels instead of %o where an user-defined label exists. Works well together with unchecking the "export code cells" config item.</li>
          <li>A separate text style for user-defined labels.</li>
          <li>The "evaluate all cells" and "evaluate till here" now start with a fresh instance of Maxima</li>
          <li>TeX export now should work with most unicode chars we have ESC sequences for.</li>
          <li>An auto-repair functionality that repairs most .wxmx files wxMaxima 13.04 was not able to open again.</li>
          <li>A few new ESC sequences and markdown commands.</li>
          <li>"#" now is shown as a "not equal" sign as a "not equal" sign already would be interpreted as "#".</li>
          <li>Teach CCL on Windows how to deal with unicode variable names like ü and α. For SBCL the necessary change has been done on the Maxima side.</li>
          <li>Sidebars for symbols</li>
          <li>Printing text cells now works again</li>
          <li>The &lt;ESC&gt; key now works as a shortcut that closes the search dialogue.</li>
          <li>A copy-to-MathML feature</li>
          <li>Many bug, usability and performance fixes</li>
          <li>Most importantly: If it is a cursor it now blinks.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="15.08.2" date="2015-09-08"/>
    <release version="15.08.1" date="2015-09-01"/>
    <release version="15.08" date="2015-08-19">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Compatibility with Maxima 5.37.0</li>
          <li>MathJAX now provides scalable equations and extended drag-and-drop for the html export.</li>
          <li>The table-of-contents-sidebar now shows the current cursor position</li>
          <li>Fixed a few instances of cursors jumping out of the screen</li>
          <li>Fixed a few instances of cursors jumping to the beginning or end of the worksheet</li>
          <li>Better detection which cell Maxima is processing and if it still is doing so</li>
          <li>Regression: Hiding the toolbar didn't work on some systems</li>
          <li>Markdown support for &lt;=, &gt;=, &lt;=&gt;, &lt;-, -&gt;, &lt;-&gt;, =&gt; and +/- symbols.</li>
          <li>An option to not export Maxima's input as well as the output.</li>
          <li>An option to use High-resolution bitmaps for the HTML export.</li>
          <li>Images that are too big for the window now are displayed in a scaled-down version.</li>
          <li>Fixed the support for out-of-tree-bulds that was broken in 15.04</li>
          <li>Meaningful ALT texts for the HTML export to provide accessibility</li>
          <li>An option to include the .wxmx file in the .html export</li>
          <li>Performance fixes that are espectionally effective for MSW</li>
          <li>Unification of some platform-specific code</li>
          <li>bash autocompletion</li>
          <li>A fourth sectioning level</li>
          <li>Made entering uppercase greek letters easier and documented how to input special unicode symbols</li>
          <li>Syntax highlighting in code cells</li>
          <li>Automatic highlighting of text equal to the currrently selected one.</li>
          <li>A batch mode that pauses evaluation if Maxima asks a question.</li>
          <li>A "halt on error" feature</li>
          <li>Now evaluation of a new command is only triggered if evaluation of the last command has finished. This means that output from Maxima is always appended to the right cell.</li>
          <li>Un-broke error and question handling for multiple commands per cell. Sincewe now send Maxima's input command-per-command this means a cell with multiple commands is no more evaluated faster than multiple cells with single commands each.</li>
          <li>If ever a end-of-evaluation marker gets lost there is a new "trigger evaluation" menu entry in the Maxima menu.</li>
          <li>On wxGtk autocompletion was replaced by a content assistant that is based on the surprisingly powerful autocompletion feature.</li>
          <li>Ctrl+Tab now launches the autocompletion (or content assistant, if available)</li>
          <li>Tab and Shift+Tab now indent and unindent regions.</li>
          <li>Ctrl+Mouse wheel and Ctrl++/- now zoom in and out of the worksheet.</li>
          <li>Allow Extending selection from part of a single cell to multiple cells.</li>
          <li>A Autoindent functionality.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="15.04.0" date="2015-04-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>wxWidgets 3.0 is now a mandatory requirement</li>
          <li>Various bugfixes</li>
          <li>Loads of stability and performance fixes</li>
          <li>Adjustable framerate for animations</li>
          <li>A version-control friendly flavour of the wxmx format</li>
          <li>A mimetype marker at the beginning of wxmx files</li>
          <li>Better desktop integration</li>
          <li>An offline manual</li>
          <li>Autodetection of Maxima's working directory on Mac and Windows</li>
          <li>Use gnuplot_postamble instead of gnuplot_preamble</li>
          <li>Dropped the hard dependency of TeXinfo</li>
          <li>Translation updates</li>
          <li>LaTeX: Use centered dots for multiplications</li>
          <li>LaTeX: Added an option to select if superscripts should be placed above or after subscripts</li>
          <li>LaTeX: Allow the user to add additional commands to the preamble.</li>
          <li>Export of animations to pdf (via a pdfTeX file run) and html</li>
          <li>Now complex conjugates are drawn as overstrike text.</li>
          <li>bumped the minor version number of .wxmx: overstrike text is a new feature and therefore a file containing it cannot be read by old wxMaxima versions.</li>
          <li>An autosave functionality that makes Maxima work more like a mobile app whose documents are always saved.</li>
          <li>A table-of-contents pane for faster navigation</li>
          <li>It is now possible to scroll away from a running evaluation for arbitrary lengths of time and to choose to follow the evaluation process again.</li>
          <li>Now TeX scales down images that are obviously too big for the page.</li>
          <li>An undo for cell deletes and for adding cells.</li>
          <li>Autocompletion for units from ezUnits</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
