<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component>
  <id type="desktop">org.fdroid.Repomaker.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC-BY-SA-4.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>AGPL-3.0</project_license>
   <releases>
    <release date="2018-11-03" version="0.0.5"/>
  </releases>
  <name>Repomaker</name>
  <provides>
    <binary>repomaker</binary>
  </provides>
  <summary>Create your own F-Droid repositories</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
    F-Droid is an installable catalogue of FOSS (Free and Open Source
    Software) applications for the Android platform. The client makes it
    easy to browse, install, and keep track of updates on your device.
    </p>
    <p>
    F-Droid.org is just a repo out of hundreds of repos created by
    individuals all around the globe. With the tools of F-Droid,
    everyone can create their own repo. So whether you are a musician
    who wants to publish their music or a developer who wants to serve
    nightly builds of their app, you are free to create your own repo
    and share it with other people independently of F-Droid.org.
    </p>
    <p>
    In the past, creating a repo has been difficult because you had to
    have knowledge on the command line, needed to edit text files to
    edit your packages’ store details and had to paste screenshots in a
    special system of directories to have them served well inside the
    F-Droid app.
    </p>
    <p>
    This all got easier now: with Repomaker, you are able to create your
    own repo and do not need to have any special knowledge to do so.
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default" height="1080" width="1920">
      <image>https://f-droid.org/assets/repomaker-screenshots/repo-details.png</image>
      <caption>Your repo can serve all types of media</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="1080" width="1920">
      <image>https://f-droid.org/assets/repomaker-screenshots/package-details.png</image>
      <caption>Editing your package store details never was easier</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="1080" width="1920">
      <image>https://f-droid.org/assets/repomaker-screenshots/create-repo.png</image>
      <caption>Creating a repo just takes you two clicks</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot height="1080" width="1920">
      <image>https://f-droid.org/assets/repomaker-screenshots/add-storage.png</image>
      <caption>You have many possibilities where to upload your repo</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://f-droid.org</url>
  <url type="translate">https://f-droid.org/docs/Translation_and_Localization/</url>
  <update_contact>team@f-droid.org</update_contact>
  <developer_name>F-Droid Team</developer_name>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gitlab.com/fdroid/repomaker/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://f-droid.org/about/</url>
  <url type="help">https://f-droid.org/docs/FAQ_-_General/</url>
</component>
