<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>com.github.tglima.Myfluttercrypto</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>MIT License</project_license>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
    <developer_name>Thiago Lima de Sousa</developer_name>
    <categories>
        <category>Utilities</category>
    </categories>
    <name>MyFlutterCrypto</name>
    <summary>MyFlutterCrypto is a cross-platform application that allows you to encrypt and decrypt texts in a simple way.</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">MyFlutterCrypto é um aplicativo multiplataforma que permite criptografar e descriptografar textos de forma simples.</summary>
    
    <description>
        <p>Quite simply, MyFlutterCrypto uses a keyword to scramble/unscramble the entered text, this keyword can be changed in the application's settings. Without the exact keyword it is not possible to unscramble text that has been scrambled before. Whenever the application is closed, the keyword goes back to its initial value, preventing them from discovering the keyword you use to scramble your texts.</p>
        <p>Language support: English, portuguese and spanish</p>
        <p>If your device's language isn't Portuguese or Spanish, the app will load in English automatically.</p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="pt_BR">
        <p>De forma bem simples, o MyFlutterCrypto utiliza uma palavra chave para embaralhar/desembaralhar o texto informado, essa palavra chave pode ser alterada nas configurações da aplicação. Sem a palavra chave exata não é possível desembaralhar o texto que foi embaralhado antes. Sempre que a aplicação é fechada a palavra chave volta para seu valor inicial, impedindo assim que descubram a palavra chave que você usa para embaralhar seus textos.</p>
        <p>Idiomas suportados pela aplicação: inglês, português e espanhol.</p>
        <p>Caso o idioma do seu dispositivo não seja português nem espanhol, a aplicação será carregada em inglês automaticamente</p>        
    </description>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">com.github.tglima.Myfluttercrypto.desktop</launchable>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>A screenshot of the MyFlutterCrypto. The navigation menu is on the left.</caption>
            <image>https://github.com/tglima/myfluttercrypto/raw/main/docs/images/app_linux_desktop.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <url type="homepage">https://github.com/tglima/myfluttercrypto</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/tglima/myfluttercrypto/issues</url>

    <releases>
        <release version="1.0.20211012" date="2021-10-12">
            <description>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add spanish language support</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
    
    <icon type="remote" height="64" width="64">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tglima/myfluttercrypto/77e6dd08bafc2cf688d826f9884256c4c0eedb95/docs/images/myfluttercrypto.svg</icon>
    <icon type="remote" height="128" width="128">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tglima/myfluttercrypto/77e6dd08bafc2cf688d826f9884256c4c0eedb95/docs/images/myfluttercrypto.svg</icon>
    
    <update_contact>tglimatech@outlook.com</update_contact>    
</component>
