<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>com.clashcross.clashcross</id>

  <name>ClashCross</name>
  <summary>ClashCross is a debugging application built on the Clash core, supporting Linux.</summary>

  <metadata_license>MIT</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>

  <description>
    <p>
      ClashCross is a proxy debugging application built on the Clash core. We do not provide any services for it, so please refrain from giving feedback on any issues not related to the application&apos;s own usage. This is an all-in-one network assistant! It can provide you with secure local HTTP/HTTPS/SOCKS servers, ensuring the safety of your authentication.
    </p>
    <p>
      But that&apos;s not all, it also supports protocols like VMess, Shadowsocks, Trojan, Snell, and more. This means you can easily connect remotely to various servers, no matter which protocol you need!
    </p>
    <p>
      It doesn&apos;t stop at just connections. This tool comes with a built-in DNS server, which minimizes the impact of DNS pollution attacks and supports DoH/DoT upstream and fake IP functionality, making your network even more secure and reliable.
    </p>
    <p>
      And wait, there&apos;s more! You can set up rules based on domains, GEOIP, IPCIDR, or processes, enabling intelligent packet forwarding to different nodes for more efficient network traffic.
    </p>
    <p>
      Moreover, if you need further customization, you can use remote groups to implement powerful rules such as automatic fallback, load balancing, or even automatic node selection based on closing latency—everything you need!
    </p>
    <p>
      There&apos;s still more to come! Say goodbye to hardcoding node lists in configurations, as this tool supports remote providers, allowing you to effortlessly fetch node lists remotely.
    </p>
    <p>
      For added convenience in deployment, it also supports Netfilter TCP redirection, making it easy to deploy Clash on your Internet gateway using iptables.
    </p>
    <p>
      Last but not least, it even offers a comprehensive HTTP RESTful API controller, allowing you to control various functions through APIs. It&apos;s incredibly powerful!
    </p>
    <p>
      In summary, this all-around network assistant provides full functionality, helping you establish a secure and efficient network environment. It&apos;s an indispensable and reliable tool for your online life!
    </p>
    <p>To run on Flathub, you must manually set up the system proxy. This is determined by the Flathub mechanism.</p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">com.clashcross.clashcross.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://github.com/shipinbaoku/clashcross/blob/master/docs/screenshot/photo_2023-07-27_05-03-12.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/shipinbaoku/clashcross/blob/master/docs/screenshot/photo_2023-07-27_05-03-34.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://github.com/shipinbaoku/clashcross/blob/master/docs/screenshot/photo_2023-07-27_05-04-13.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.3" date="2023-08-01"/>
  </releases>
</component>