<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021 Nicola Corna <nicola@corna.info> -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.github.corna.Vivado</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <name>Xilinx Vivado Design Suite</name>
  <summary>Xilinx Design Suite for hardware development</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Vivado Design Suite is a software suite designed by Xilinx for the design, synthesis and analysis of HDL for its line of FPGAs and SoCs. Vivado Design Suite includes many tools, like Vivado, Vitis, Vitis HLS and many others. This package provides a flatpak wrapper over an official installation. As the Xilinx tools are not redistributable, this package does not contain any Xilinx-licensed material, which is instead downloaded on-the-fly through the official Xilinx installer. To install it, install the flatpak package, then run any Xilinx launcher and follow the instructions. To uninstall, just remove the flatpak package to remove this wrapper. Note that this does not remove the Xilinx installation; to remove it, run the launcher "Uninstall Xilinx Design Tools or Devices" (or run "flatpak uninstall com.github.corna.Vivado --delete-data" to wipe everything in in "~/.var/app/com.github.corna.Vivado/").</p>
    <p>Why can't I see some of my files in Vivado? - All the Xilinx tools handled by this wrapper run in a sandbox with limited filesystem access, only your documents and desktop folders are visibile. Either work in those directories or override the default permission (with "flatpak override com.github.corna.Vivado --filesystem=&lt;path_here&gt;").</p>
    <p>I get an error "Can't open project [...]. Please verify that the project still exist.", why? - Same as before, make sure that the project is in one of the allowed folders.</p>
    <p>I have created a project outside Desktop or Documents: where are they? - You can find the sandboxed filesystem in "~/var/app/com.github.corna.Vivado/".</p>
    <p>I can not access the hardware devices. - Have you installed the "cable drivers" (which are just udev rules) at the end of the installation? To install them, run: "cd ~/.var/app/com.github.corna.Vivado/data/xilinx-install/Vivado/&lt;version&gt;/data/xicom/cable_drivers/lin64/install_script/install_drivers/ &amp;&amp; sudo ./install_drivers &amp;&amp; sudo udevadm control --reload", then re-connect any hardware device.</p>
    <p>Can I deny internet access to the Xilinx tools? - Yes, just remove the corresponding permission with: "flatpak override com.github.corna.Vivado  --unshare=network". Note that the license manager uses your MAC addresses, so you may experience issues with non free components.</p>
    <p>How can I install additional components? - Run the launcher "Add Xilinx Design Tools or Devices".</p>
    <p>Can I install an additional version of the Xilinx tools? - Yes, run "flatpak run --command=xilinx_install com.github.corna.Vivado".</p>
    <p>How can I remove a particular version? - Run the launcher "Uninstall Xilinx Design Tools or Devices".</p>
    <p>NOTE: This wrapper is not verified by, affiliated with, or supported by Xilinx, Inc.</p>
  </description>
  <categories>
    <category>Development</category>
    <category>IDE</category>
  </categories>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.xilinx.com/</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/corna/com.github.corna.Vivado</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/corna/com.github.corna.Vivado/issues</url>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <developer_name>Xilinx, Inc.</developer_name>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    <content_attribute id="social-info">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-advertising">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
    <release date="2021-3-15" version="1.0.0"/>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/ab/XilinxVivado_2014.jpg</image>
      <caption>Xilinx Vivado Block Design view</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
