<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>work.worklog.desktop</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
    <name>Work Log</name>
    <summary>Track your work sessions with hierarchical time organization</summary>
    <description>
        <p>Work Log is a native KDE application designed to help you track and organize your work sessions with a focus on simplicity and local data control. Whether you're a freelancer tracking billable hours, a developer logging coding sessions, or anyone who wants to maintain a detailed record of their work, Work Log provides an intuitive interface for capturing what you've accomplished.</p>
        <p>The application organizes your work sessions in a hierarchical tree structure (Year → Month → Week → Day), making it easy to browse your work history and see patterns over time. Each session can include the time spent (in half-hour increments), a description of what you worked on, detailed notes in Markdown format, and what you plan to do next.</p>
        <p>All data is stored locally in a SQLite database on your computer, giving you complete control and privacy. The application is built with Qt and KDE Frameworks, providing a responsive and native experience on Linux desktops.</p>
        <p>Features:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>Hierarchical navigation by year, month, week, and day for easy browsing</li>
            <li>Record work sessions with time (0.5 hour increments), description, notes, and next planned stage</li>
            <li>Organize sessions with custom tags for categorization</li>
            <li>View statistics including total hours per day, week, and month</li>
            <li>Calendar popup for easy date selection</li>
            <li>SQLite database for reliable local storage with no cloud dependencies</li>
        </ul>
    </description>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">work.worklog.desktop.desktop</launchable>
    <developer id="io.github.macsplit">
        <name>Lee Hanken</name>
    </developer>
    <url type="homepage">https://github.com/macsplit/Work.Log</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/macsplit/Work.Log/issues</url>
    <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/macsplit/Work.Log</url>
    <provides>
        <binary>worklog-desktop</binary>
    </provides>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>Main window showing hierarchical session navigation and session details</caption>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/macsplit/Work.Log/main/screenshots/desktop-main.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
        <release version="1.0.0" date="2024-11-29">
            <description>
                <p>Initial release of Work Log Desktop</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Hierarchical work session tracking by year, month, week, and day</li>
                    <li>Session management with time tracking, descriptions, notes, and planning</li>
                    <li>Tag system for organizing and categorizing work sessions</li>
                    <li>Statistics and totals for daily, weekly, and monthly hours</li>
                    <li>Calendar date picker for easy date selection</li>
                    <li>Local SQLite database storage</li>
                </ul>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
